<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: SouthIndian | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/southindian/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-08T18:28:53-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chakram]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2014/01/03/Chakram.html"/>
    <updated>2014-01-03T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2014/01/03/Chakram</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/70RkR0GoDwQ/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Chakram"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/70RkR0GoDwQ/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Chakram"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/70RkR0GoDwQ/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Chakram"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/70RkR0GoDwQ/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Chakram"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Chakram is a foreign returnee and has a dream of building a hospital at Pulivendula. He is in love with his colleague, Lakshmi who studied with him abroad. But leaves her half-way through after he realizes that he was struck with cancer. Not wanting to tell her, he moves to Hyderabad and stays in place called &lsquo;Sahara Colony&rsquo;. There, he tries to solve people problem&rsquo;s in the colony. Seeing all this, another girl who is also named Lakshmi falls in love with Chakram. The rest is a heart-rending saga of the cancer-struck patient&rsquo;s love station.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70RkR0GoDwQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Khatarnak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/26/Main-Hoon-Khatarnak.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-26T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/26/Main-Hoon-Khatarnak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GHfRvzT-2ZQ/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Khatarnak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GHfRvzT-2ZQ/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Khatarnak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GHfRvzT-2ZQ/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Khatarnak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GHfRvzT-2ZQ/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Khatarnak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Dasu who is the son of a counterfeit racketeer. As his father goes to jail, Dasu becomes an orphan. He stops his education at 10th class and moves like a vagabond. On the other side, there is a smuggler who used to smuggle drugs and arms into the country. But an honest police officer hatches a plan and sends one informer into their underworld. He stays with them for sometime and passes on information to the police, with the help of which the police were able to bust the smugglers team, though not the kingpin. The don&rsquo;s assistant, who was also a lawyer advises him to play the same trick and admit one of their henchmen into the police to get information from the reverse side. However, he should not be in police records but should be crooked and cunning. The smugglers team&rsquo;s search ends with Dasu. The group threatens Dasu and make him to play like a puppet in their hands. In order to push him inside the police department, he should at least pass tenth class. So, they admit him in a school, where he falls in love with a teacher Nakshatra. However, she doesn&rsquo;t like him as he neither has good education nor good looks. After a few incidents, the don&rsquo;s right hand i.e., the lawyer tells Dasu to study well and become a police officer to win her love. Admitting the idea, Dasu turns a good student and gets through the exam. Later, he becomes a constable and gets posted in traffic. The smugglers unit hatches another plan and succeeds in pushing him in the crime police. After watching Dasu as a sincere police constable, Nakshatra too starts liking him. Soon, in a turn of events, Nakshatra&rsquo;s brother, who was a police informer, is killed in the hands of Dasu at the behest of the don. She chides Dasu and starts hating him. Dasu starts disliking his job as he became a police officer only to win her love. As he lost her love, Dasu turns against the don and finally kills him. Nakshatra learns from the lawyer that her brother actually died in the hands of the don, she reunites with Dasu and the film ends on a happy note.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GHfRvzT-2ZQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yamraaj Ek Faulad]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/20/Yamraaj-Ek-Faulad.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-20T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/20/Yamraaj-Ek-Faulad</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vTJ1OhTgDRU/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Yamraaj Ek Faulad"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vTJ1OhTgDRU/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yamraaj Ek Faulad"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vTJ1OhTgDRU/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yamraaj Ek Faulad"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vTJ1OhTgDRU/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yamraaj Ek Faulad"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story si about an orphan and good-hearted lad Simhadri is &lsquo;adopted&rsquo; and grows up under Ram Bhupal Varma&rsquo;s family care in Visakhapatnam. The bond they share is like a father and son. Kasturi is the granddaughter of Ram Bhupal Varma. Kasturi likes Simhadri a lot. Once a week, Simhadri visits a mentally challenged girl called Indu. He entertains her and provides money to her caretakers. When Ram Bhupal Varma and his wife discover Kasturi&rsquo;s wish to marry Simhadri, Ram Bhupal Varma decides to get them married. He makes a formal announcement to officially adopt Simhadri. At this time, it is revealed that Simhadri is very close to Indu. The alliance breaks off when Simhadri refuses to leave Indu. Meanwhile, two separate groups are in search of Simhadri. They find him at the banks of Godavari River along with Indu. In the ensuing confrontation between one group and Simhadri, Indu gets injured. Simhadri is helped by the second group who call him &lsquo;Singamalai Anna&rsquo;. When Indu comes back to her senses, she remembers her past and the first thing she does is stab Simhadri with an iron pole. Simhadri is hospitalized in critical condition. Then we see many buses carrying hoards of people demanding to see &lsquo;Singamalai Anna&rsquo;. The leader of the second group who was searching for Simhadri explains &lsquo;Singamalai Anna&rsquo; story in a flashback. In the flashback, it is revealed that Ram Bhupal Varma&rsquo;s oldest daughter Saraswati elopes with her lover, a Keralite named Aravind. After some harsh words and saddened over Ram Bhupal Varma&rsquo;s rejection over her choice to marry her love, they both settle in Kerala. Learning of the sadness surrounding Ram Bhupal Varma and his wife, Simhadri takes up the job of uniting the family and visits Thiruvananthapuram. He joins the medical and spiritual therapy spa operated by Saraswati and her family under the disguise of a patient. He finds that Indu is the first granddaughter of Ram Bhupal Varma. He convinces the separated family to reunite and ask for forgiveness. During this time, Saraswati is killed by a local goon Bala Nair. A don named Bhai Saab controls the mafia of Kerala. Nair and Bhai Saab belong to the same mafia. Simhadri takes law into his hands and eradicates Bala Nair and his small gang in Kerala. The local Kerala people starts calling him &lsquo;Singamalai&rsquo;. In the ensuing scenes, Simhadri finds himself developing into &ldquo;Singamalai,&rdquo; eradicating Bhai Saab&rsquo;s network and illegal activities. Indu finds herself alone and constantly worrying about him. She proposes to her father that they should return to Andhra Pradesh because she cannot stand their home without her mother and Simhadri ignores her now. Indu and Aravind decide to return to Visakhapatnam. Simhadri receives a call that Indu&rsquo;s father is carrying a bomb in his briefcase. Aravind is seen rushing to catch a moving train and Indu was about to lend him a hand. Unable to warn him, Simhadri has two choices: to let Indu&rsquo;s father die, so people on the train can live or let the bomb kill everyone on board, including the father and Indu herself. Simhadri chooses to the first option. As soon as Aravind catches the train bar handle, Simhadri shoots him in the back. Surprised at Simhadri&rsquo;s action; Indu jumps off the train to catch her falling father and she gets hit her head against a pole, causing her amnesia and become mentally challenged. After the flashback ends, people are seen and heard chanting Singamalai Singamalaioutside the hospital. Bhai Saab and his men arrive at the hospital to finish off Simhadri. But Simhadri has gained consciousness with the help of his friends, police and family (now reunited), he takes down Bhai Saab and his army</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vTJ1OhTgDRU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veerta the Power]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/17/Veerta-The-Power.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-17T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/Dubbed/2013/12/17/Veerta-The-Power</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Veerta The Power"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Neelakantam is a village elder. He has two daughters Subbalakshmi and Meenakshi. The film begins with the elopement of Subbalakshmi with one Babu of the same village and he is a friend of Krishna. The entire family of Neelakantam holes up the friends of Babu, on the presumption that they helped him. Krishna is also caught by the men of Neelakantam. Krishna makes an attempt to escape from the village but can not do so after having a look at a beautiful girl, who is none other than Meenakshi. However, he does not know that it is Neelakantam&rsquo;s younger child. Though the entire situation is quite charged, Krishna is on the look out of the girl to whom he loses his heart. Before the interval bang, the secret unravels. Neelakantam&rsquo;s brother realises that it was Krishna who helped Babu in taking away Subbalakshmi in vizag. On being questioned, Krishna takes the entire gang to Hyderabad along with Meenakshi. He tries to impress her whenever, he gets an opportunity . During the search for the girl, an incident occurs and Neelakantam comes out in open and explains Krishna how a father of an eloped girl will be broken. This turns an eye-opener for Krishna, who decides to sacrifice his love. Soon, Neelakantam and his group find Subbalakshmi and her boyfriend. But she makes it very clear that she will be happy only with her boyfriend and dares her father not to try to separate them. Then Neelakantam has challenged to do his younger daughter marriege grandly with broken heart through his elder daughter what she did,In the end, Neelakantam comes to know that Meenakshi falls in love with Krishna. However, Krishna tells Neelakantam that he is against to separate him with his daughter. But Neelakantam realizes the value of love and unites the lovers and the film ends on a happy note, in the same place of Krishna was stopped his running for beautiful girl.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/_eYQMFD474k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magadheera]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Magadheera/Movies/SouthIndian/2013/10/31/Magadheera.html"/>
    <updated>2013-10-31T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Magadheera/Movies/SouthIndian/2013/10/31/Magadheera</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dY4RWzzgivk/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Magadheera"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dY4RWzzgivk/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Magadheera"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dY4RWzzgivk/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Magadheera"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dY4RWzzgivk/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Magadheera"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The story is told in a series of flashbacks, starting with the present time, 2009. Harsha is a stunt man and ekes out his living by taking part in bike races and stunts. He happens to meet Indu and whenever he touches her, he is reminded of something that happened in the past. He falls in love with her and she reciprocates the love. Indu&rsquo;s father fights a legal battle for Udaygadh kingdom as it was his ancestral property. His brother-in-law enjoys the property illegally. The latter&rsquo;s son Raghuveer is spellbound by Indu&rsquo;s beauty and goes to their home and promises to return the entire property with the hopes of marrying Indu. Raghuveer&rsquo;s guru Ghora tells him that he cannot win Indu as long as Harsha is alive. On learning that Indu&rsquo;s father accepted her love for Harsha, Raghuveer kills the father, implicates Harsha in the murder and takes Indu away to Udaygadh. Though Harsha tries to explain the truth to Indu, she doesn&rsquo;t believe him. In the process, Harsha drops falls from a helicopter into a lake, only to be saved by Solomon. Now it is Harsha&rsquo;s turn to prove his innocence and remind Indu of their previous birth. The story then goes back four centuries to 1609 AD. There is a kingdom called Udaygadh in ruled by King Vikram Singh. Mitravinda is his only daughter. Ranadev Bhilla is her cousin. Kala Bhairava is a warrior who trains the army of the kingdom. His family has lived under the curse that no warrior will live for more than 30 years, and will not accept death until he has killed a hundred enemies in the battle. He is also the personal caretaker of the royal family. Ranadev eyes Mitravinda and wants to get the kingdom by marrying her. But the princess loses her heart to Bhairava. In order to win her hand, both Ranadev and Bhairava take part in a contest and Bhairava emerges the winner. The king, who knows about the curse, requests Kala Bhairava to reject the hand of the princess as he does not want his daughter to become a widow. Ranadev turns traitor and joins hands with Sher Khan. He invades the kingdom and kills the king. Later, Ranadev and Sher Khan reach the place where Bhairava and Mitravinda are offering prayers to Lord Siva. Sher Khan challenges Bhairava to save the princess from his men. Bhairava courageously attacks and kills 100 soldiers. Sher Khan accepts defeat and is impressed by Bhairava&rsquo;s courage. Bhairava kills Ranadev but Ranadev stabs Mitravinda. During her last moments, Mitravinda requests Bhairava to proclaim his love for her. They both fall off the cliff and the last words between them remain unsaid. The unproclaimed love of Kala Bhairava and Mithravinda and the unfulfilled wishes of Ranadev have made them take another birth four centuries later. The final showdown is more of a battle between true love and lust. Finally, Indu believes Harsha and proclaims her love for him. Solomon helps Harsha in killing Raguveer&rsquo;s accomplices. In the final fight, Harsha kills Raghuveer by cutting off his hand where he holds indu and Raghuveer Fall down from the cliff and Dies.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dY4RWzzgivk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
