<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Superhit-Romantic-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/superhit-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T01:05:53-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laila Majnu]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Laila-Majnu.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Laila-Majnu</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p6RPs6tUP1c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Laila Majnu" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic Drama movie Laila Majnu (1976) starring Rishi Kapoor &amp; Ranjeeta Kaur. The movie is directed by Harnam Singh Rawail &amp; produced by Ram B.C. &amp; Seeroo Daryani. Music composed by Madan Mohan &amp; Jaidev.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/p6RPs6tUP1c" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hero]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Hero.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Hero</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vU8oummVZd0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Hero" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Notorious criminal Pasha (Amrish Puri) has been sent to jail by the former inspector general of Police Shrikanth Mathur (Shammi Kapoor). An enraged Pasha decides to get even with Shrikanth and hence asks his trusted prot?g? Jackie (Jackie Shroff) to carry out a plan to get him released from the prison. As directed, Jackie abducts Shrikanth&rsquo;s daughter Radha (Meenakshi Shashadri) in the garb of a police officer. Radha is made to believe that Jackie and his gang of goons are her protectors and are keeping her in the jungle for her safety as her house has been taken over by bandits. As the days passed, Jackie gets increasingly drawn towards Radha and eventually both fall in love with each other. Radha discovers about Jackie&rsquo;s truth but still stays by his side. She even makes Jackie surrender which leads him to spend two years in jail. Radha meanwhile returns to her home and narrates about her love to her brother Damodar (Sanjeev Kumar).  Thwarted plans of his release makes Pasha angry and he vows to take revenge from Srikanth and Jackie. Will Jackie and Radha meet? Will their love be accepted by all? What will Pasha do to extract his revenge?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vU8oummVZd0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Duuje Ke Liye]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/x6nP3Du-Gvw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ek Duuje Ke Liye" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>This cross-culture romance between a southern Vaasu &ndash; Kamal Haasan and a northern Sapna &ndash; Rati Agnihotri epitomizes inter-caste and inter-state romance. The tragic end to the film depressed many lovers who faced similar problems in their love life. Fed up with the pressures of the society not ready to accept their union, one couple is said to have taken the course shown by the protagonists in the film. They committed suicide. Ek Duje ke Liye saw southern actor Kamal Haasan appear for the first time in a Hindi film. Rati too stepped into Bollywood with this tragic love story and went on to become the number one in the industry.The music of the film was a rage, especially &lsquo;Tere mere beech mein&rsquo;, &lsquo;Hum bane tum bane ek duuje ke liye&rsquo; and the Hindi films name based &lsquo;Mere jeevan saathi&rsquo;</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x6nP3Du-Gvw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dil Tera Aashiq]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Dil-Tera-Aashiq.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Dil-Tera-Aashiq</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/n3lu7SGzs8E/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Dil Tera Aashiq" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the superhit Bollywood romantic Hindi film &lsquo;Dil Tera Aashiq&rsquo; (1993) Starring Madhuri Dixit, Salman Khan, Anupam Kher, Kader Khan, Asrani &amp; Shakti Kapoor. Directed by Lawrence D'souza &amp; Produced by Rakesh Nath. Written by Reema Rakesh Nath &amp; Music Directed by Nadeem Shravan.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/n3lu7SGzs8E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dhaai Akshar Prem Ke]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Dhaai-Akshar-Prem-Ke.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Dhaai-Akshar-Prem-Ke</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GUGovNkyMZg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Dhaai Akshar Prem Ke" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>A young girl named Sahiba runs away from her home to evade marriage and ends up being an eye-witness to a murder. A panic stricken Sahiba finds an unexpected savior in Karan who rescues her and gets her back to her family. The family mistakes Karan to be Sahiba&rsquo;s husband and the two get entangled in a web of lies. Sahiba ends up getting attracted to Karan. But as the past catches on the game of deception fails. Sahiba and her family come to know about Nisha, Karan&rsquo;s sweetheart and Sahiba&rsquo;s marriage is arranged with Vicky. Sahiba, who has given her heart to Karan, reluctantly agrees to this marriage, only to find out that the person she is marrying is none other than the murderer who she saw. Is Sahiba&rsquo;s fate sealed with that of a killer? Can Karan save Sahiba and succeed in his love?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GUGovNkyMZg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
