<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Superhit-Romantic-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/superhit-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:19:50-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hero]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Hero.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Hero</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vU8oummVZd0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Hero" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Notorious criminal Pasha (Amrish Puri) has been sent to jail by the former inspector general of Police Shrikanth Mathur (Shammi Kapoor). An enraged Pasha decides to get even with Shrikanth and hence asks his trusted prot?g? Jackie (Jackie Shroff) to carry out a plan to get him released from the prison. As directed, Jackie abducts Shrikanth's daughter Radha (Meenakshi Shashadri) in the garb of a police officer. Radha is made to believe that Jackie and his gang of goons are her protectors and are keeping her in the jungle for her safety as her house has been taken over by bandits. As the days passed, Jackie gets increasingly drawn towards Radha and eventually both fall in love with each other. Radha discovers about Jackie's truth but still stays by his side. She even makes Jackie surrender which leads him to spend two years in jail. Radha meanwhile returns to her home and narrates about her love to her brother Damodar (Sanjeev Kumar).  Thwarted plans of his release makes Pasha angry and he vows to take revenge from Srikanth and Jackie. Will Jackie and Radha meet? Will their love be accepted by all? What will Pasha do to extract his revenge?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Duuje Ke Liye]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/x6nP3Du-Gvw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ek Duuje Ke Liye" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>This cross-culture romance between a southern Vaasu - Kamal Haasan and a northern Sapna - Rati Agnihotri epitomizes inter-caste and inter-state romance. The tragic end to the film depressed many lovers who faced similar problems in their love life. Fed up with the pressures of the society not ready to accept their union, one couple is said to have taken the course shown by the protagonists in the film. They committed suicide. Ek Duje ke Liye saw southern actor Kamal Haasan appear for the first time in a Hindi film. Rati too stepped into Bollywood with this tragic love story and went on to become the number one in the industry.The music of the film was a rage, especially 'Tere mere beech mein', 'Hum bane tum bane ek duuje ke liye' and the Hindi films name based 'Mere jeevan saathi'


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maine Pyar Kiya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Maine-Pyar-Kiya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Maine-Pyar-Kiya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-lshGX1OIWE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Maine Pyar Kiya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch Bollywood romantic superhit movie Maine Pyar Kiya (1989) starring superstar Salman Khan, Bhagyashree, Reema Lagoo, Alok Nath, Laxmikant Berde, Mohanish Behl by Rajshree Productions. Directed by Sooraj Barjatya. Music by Raam Laxman.


<p>Synopsis: Everyone falls in love with someone&hellip;somehow. One of Indian cinema&rsquo;s biggest hits, Maine Pyar Kiya is the call of two young hearts smitten with love! Prem (Salman Khan) is the son of a multimillionaire, Kishen (Rajiv Verma) and Suman (Bhagyashree) is the daughter of an ordinary motor mechanic, Karan (Alok Nath). When fate brings them together, there develops a mutual liking which soon blossoms into love. Prem and Suman sing and dance, as they dream of a beautiful tomorrow. The dreams seem to be soon turning into reality; Prem&rsquo;s mother is happy to accept Suman as her prospective daughter-in-law. But Kishen, who only knows the language of money, not only injures the loving hearts, but also insults Karan, his childhood friend.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laila Majnu]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Laila-Majnu.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Laila-Majnu</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p6RPs6tUP1c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Laila Majnu" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch Bollywood Romantic Drama movie Laila Majnu (1976) starring Rishi Kapoor & Ranjeeta Kaur. The movie is directed by Harnam Singh Rawail & produced by Ram B.C. & Seeroo Daryani. Music composed by Madan Mohan & Jaidev.


<p>Synopsis: Kaish a.k.a Majnu(Rishi Kapoor )and Laila (Ranjeeta Kaur) are born to rival clans, the Amaris and the Sharwaris. They are madly in love with each other  but the two clan heads decide to separate their children. Years later, Kaish and Laila meet again in the market place and once again rekindle their love. They start meeting each other secretly, all over again. But Laila&rsquo;s hot-tempered brother Tabrez (Ranjeet) proves to be a problem for the lovers and soon Kaish&rsquo;s father dies at the hands of Tabrez. Kaish in turn, avenges his father&rsquo;s murder by killing Tabrez. He is exiled from the town and wanders in the desert, wanting to meet his beloved Laila. Meanwhile, Laila is married off to prince, Bakhsh (Danny Denzongpa) and aches to be with Majnu. Will the star-crossed lovers unite or be separated for the rest of their lives?</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heer Raanjha]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Heer-Raanjha.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/21/Heer-Raanjha</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/1OM-gHp1xQM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Heer Raanjha" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch the superhit cult classic Hindi romantic Bollywood blockbuster movie based on the greatest classic romantic tragic love story of all time time 'Heer Raanjha' (1970), starring Raaj Kumar, Priya Rajvansh, Prithviraj Kapoor, Jeevan, Ajit, Jayant, Pran, TunTun, Ulhas, Tabassum. Directed by Chetan Anand. Music by Madan Mohan. Lyrics by Kaifi Azmi.


<p>Synopsis: Ranjha, a simple man, falls in love with Heer, an extremely beautiful woman and one who is born in a wealthy family. Heer is mesmerized by Ranjha&rsquo;s flute playing talent. They meet secretly but get caught by Heer&rsquo;s uncle. Heer is forced to marry someone else. Heartbroken by this news, Ranjha leaves town to become a nomad. How they unite and become a legend is the rest of the story.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
