<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Superhit-Romantic-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/superhit-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T00:22:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laila Majnu]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Laila-Majnu.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Laila-Majnu</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p6RPs6tUP1c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Laila Majnu" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic Drama movie Laila Majnu (1976) starring Rishi Kapoor &amp; Ranjeeta Kaur. The movie is directed by Harnam Singh Rawail &amp; produced by Ram B.C. &amp; Seeroo Daryani. Music composed by Madan Mohan &amp; Jaidev.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hero]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Hero.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Hero</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vU8oummVZd0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Hero" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Notorious criminal Pasha (Amrish Puri) has been sent to jail by the former inspector general of Police Shrikanth Mathur (Shammi Kapoor). An enraged Pasha decides to get even with Shrikanth and hence asks his trusted prot?g? Jackie (Jackie Shroff) to carry out a plan to get him released from the prison. As directed, Jackie abducts Shrikanth&rsquo;s daughter Radha (Meenakshi Shashadri) in the garb of a police officer. Radha is made to believe that Jackie and his gang of goons are her protectors and are keeping her in the jungle for her safety as her house has been taken over by bandits. As the days passed, Jackie gets increasingly drawn towards Radha and eventually both fall in love with each other. Radha discovers about Jackie&rsquo;s truth but still stays by his side. She even makes Jackie surrender which leads him to spend two years in jail. Radha meanwhile returns to her home and narrates about her love to her brother Damodar (Sanjeev Kumar).  Thwarted plans of his release makes Pasha angry and he vows to take revenge from Srikanth and Jackie. Will Jackie and Radha meet? Will their love be accepted by all? What will Pasha do to extract his revenge?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Duuje Ke Liye]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Ek-Duuje-Ke-Liye</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/x6nP3Du-Gvw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ek Duuje Ke Liye" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>This cross-culture romance between a southern Vaasu &ndash; Kamal Haasan and a northern Sapna &ndash; Rati Agnihotri epitomizes inter-caste and inter-state romance. The tragic end to the film depressed many lovers who faced similar problems in their love life. Fed up with the pressures of the society not ready to accept their union, one couple is said to have taken the course shown by the protagonists in the film. They committed suicide. Ek Duje ke Liye saw southern actor Kamal Haasan appear for the first time in a Hindi film. Rati too stepped into Bollywood with this tragic love story and went on to become the number one in the industry.The music of the film was a rage, especially &lsquo;Tere mere beech mein&rsquo;, &lsquo;Hum bane tum bane ek duuje ke liye&rsquo; and the Hindi films name based &lsquo;Mere jeevan saathi&rsquo;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maine Pyar Kiya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Maine-Pyar-Kiya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:55-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Maine-Pyar-Kiya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-lshGX1OIWE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Maine Pyar Kiya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood romantic superhit movie Maine Pyar Kiya (1989) starring superstar Salman Khan, Bhagyashree, Reema Lagoo, Alok Nath, Laxmikant Berde, Mohanish Behl by Rajshree Productions. Directed by Sooraj Barjatya. Music by Raam Laxman.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heer Raanjha]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Heer-Raanjha.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:55-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/22/Heer-Raanjha</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/1OM-gHp1xQM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Heer Raanjha" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the superhit cult classic Hindi romantic Bollywood blockbuster movie based on the greatest classic romantic tragic love story of all time time &lsquo;Heer Raanjha&rsquo; (1970), starring Raaj Kumar, Priya Rajvansh, Prithviraj Kapoor, Jeevan, Ajit, Jayant, Pran, TunTun, Ulhas, Tabassum. Directed by Chetan Anand. Music by Madan Mohan. Lyrics by Kaifi Azmi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
