<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Super-Bollywood-Action-Films | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/super-bollywood-action-films/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:04:08-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palay Khan - Bollywood Action Film - Jackie Shroff, Poonam Dhillon]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Palay-Khan---Bollywood-Action-Film---Jackie-Shroff%2C-Poonam-Dhillon.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:03:20-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Palay-Khan---Bollywood-Action-Film---Jackie-Shroff,-Poonam-Dhillon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/uEWLQrQsZH8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Palay Khan - Bollywood Action Film - Jackie Shroff, Poonam Dhillon" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>The British are in power in India. But Mandokhel is one region that they are yet to capture. Thanks to the rebels led by Palay Khan (Jackie Shroff) protecting them. All the attempts by the British to capture him have gone in vain. The British force led by Col Gulbaaz Khan manages to capture Palay Khan's best friend Amar Singh. To free him Palay Khan decides to kidnap Ellen, the daughter of the British General Bonz. But on his mother's insistence he frees her and eventually the fall in love. Palay will have to deal with strong opposition from the British. Before that he has to handle his fellow men who think the he is betraying them. Gulbaaz Khan takes advantage of the situation and lays a trap to capture Palay Khan. Will Palay Khan survive the trap to fight against the British and be with his beloved?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mission the Last War - Bollywood Action Film]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mission-The-Last-War---Bollywood-Action-Film.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:03:20-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mission-The-Last-War---Bollywood-Action-Film</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/U0THhUakcrE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mission The Last War - Bollywood Action Film" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Maharaja (Amrish Puri), a notorious criminal who controls the red light areas, abducts a college girl named Chanda and forces her into prostitution. Chanda's lover Krishna sets out to find her but his attempts are foiled by Maharaja. Krishna's brother Biju, an Airforce commander vows to find Chanda and his brother but fails to get a lead on Maharaja's location. He is joined by Succhi, a young man who's friend meets the same fate as Chanda. Both men unite to track down Maharaja's location and decimate his crime empire to rise supreme in the war against injustice.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mera Haque - Sanjay Dutt, Anita Raj - Bollywood Full Length Action Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mera-Haque---Sanjay-Dutt%2C-Anita-Raj---Bollywood-Full-Length-Action-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:03:20-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mera-Haque---Sanjay-Dutt,-Anita-Raj---Bollywood-Full-Length-Action-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pTknB77ohMs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mera Haque - Sanjay Dutt, Anita Raj - Bollywood Full Length Action Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch the Bollywood film 'Mera Haque' (1986) Starring Sanjay Dutt, Anita Raj, Raza Murad, Ramesh Deo, Gulshan Grover, Bindu & Shakti Kapoor. Directed & Written by Ajay Kashyap. Produced by Bobby Raj & Music Directed by Anu Malik.


<p>Synopsis: Aristocratic Amar Singh is the heir to his princely estate, left behind by late father, who had re-married a cruel and calculating woman, Ranimaa, and has been mismanaging the estate for her own personal gain, with the help of her brother, Dhartiprasad, her Diwan and his son. When she finds out that Amar is interfering in this process, she has him killed by planting a time-bomb in his car. After sometime, differences arise between Ranimaa and Dhartiprasad, and Dhartiprasad is asked to leave. Alone, homeless, and alcoholic, Dhartiprasad comes across a look-alike of Amar Singh, whose name is Amru Dada, a hoodlum. Dhartiprasad persuades Amru to impersonate Amar, and takes him to the palace, where both are able to prove that he is the real prince, who had somehow survived the accident. None of them know that Amru has an agenda of his own, and has not intention of sharing any of his new-found wealth and status with any one.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mard Ki Zabaan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mard-Ki-Zabaan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:03:20-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Mard-Ki-Zabaan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/z0dnE92FP68/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mard Ki Zabaan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Ram Chauhan is a poor farmer and lives with his brother, Lakshman in a small village. He falls in love with wealthy girl Lakshmi and they decide to get married. Lakshmi's father, Raghupathi objects their union and disowns her. His anger does not subside even when Lakshmi gives birth to a son, Vijay. When Raghupathi announces that his sole beneficiary is going to be his loyal servant Shrinath, Lakshman opposes this action. Shrinath is a wicked man who wants to take over Raghupathi's wealth and manages to do so by killing Ram, separating Lakshmi and her son Vijay and in the process framing Lakshman for murder. Years later, Lakshman, still in prison, is informed that Raghupathi has been conned by Shrinath and his son, Monty; and they have hired an impersonator, who has killed Raghupathi and taken over the estate. Lakshman escapes from prison and is hell-bent on taking revenge against the men responsible for destroying his family.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maati Maangey Khoon]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Maati-Maangey-Khoon.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:03:20-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Super-Bollywood-Action-Films/2014/03/21/Maati-Maangey-Khoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Jef8CI02gDI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Maati Maangey Khoon" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Hariya (Shatrughan Sinha) is an orphan, having no knowldge of his parents and lives a solitary life. He is dear friends with Balraj (Raj Babbar), nephew of the village Landlord, Balram Singh (Amjad Khan). Balram Sing is a tyrant who opresses the villager's and Hariya gets into a confrontation with Thakur's goons. He ends up mortally wonded and soon learns that his father was a farmer who got murdered by Balram in a land dispute. Hariya vows to take revenge and get back the land from Balram. To stop Hariya, Balram transfers the land in Balraj's name, plotting to create misunderstandings between the good friends. Soon a war erupts between  Hariya and Balraj which Balram fuels with his devious plans. How will Hariya exact revenge on Balram and free the village from his tyranny? How will fate orchestrate the violent tale of best friends turned sworn enemies?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
