<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Navratri-Special | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/navratri-special/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:42:28-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shakti Leela]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Shakti-Leela.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Shakti-Leela</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Vj6pFRFPNVw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Shakti Leela" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Shakti Leela is a Devotional Movie talks about various leelas of Godess.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vj6pFRFPNVw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maya Machhindra]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Maya-Machhindra.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Maya-Machhindra</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xq1F3fik_9M/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Maya Machhindra" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Maya Macchindra is the title of about six films produced in different languages in India. The story is based on the life of Matsyendranath or Machindranath one of the eighty-four Mahasiddhas.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xq1F3fik_9M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jai Santoshi Maa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Jai-Santoshi-Maa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Jai-Santoshi-Maa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/WZQSTHtAJjQ/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Jai Santoshi Maa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The film opens in Dev Lok a Hindu heaven located above the clouds, where we witness the &ldquo;birth&rdquo; of Santoshi Ma as the daughter of Ganesha, the elephant headed god of good beginnings, and his two wives Riddhi and Siddhi. A key role is played by the immortal sage Narada, a devotee of Vishnu, and a cosmic busybody who regularly intervenes to advance the film&rsquo;s two parallel plots, which concern both human beings and gods. We soon meet the maiden Satyavati, Santoshi Ma&rsquo;s greatest earthly devotee, leading a group of women in an aarti to the goddess. Through the Mother&rsquo;s grace, Satyavati soon meets, falls in love with, and manages to marry the handsome lad Birju, youngest of seven brothers in a prosperous farmer family, an artistic flute-playing type who can also render a zippy bhajan on request. Alas, with the boy come the in-laws, and two of Birju&rsquo;s six sisters-in-law, Durga and Maya are jealous shrews who have it in for him and Satyavati from the beginning. To make matters worse, Narada stirs up the jealousy of three senior goddesses, Lakshmi, Parvati, and Brahmani  the wives of the &ldquo;Hindu trinity&rdquo; of Vishnu, Shiva, and Brahma against the &ldquo;upstart&rdquo; goddess Santoshi Ma. They decide to examine her perseverance by making life miserable for her chief devotee. After a fight with his relatives, Birju leaves home to seek his fortune, narrowly escaping a watery grave through his wife&rsquo;s devotion to Santoshi Ma. Nevertheless, the divine ladies convince his family that he is indeed dead, adding the stigma of widowhood to Satyavati&rsquo;s other woes. Her sisters-in-law treat her like a slave, beat and starve her, and a local rogue attempts to rape her; Santoshi Ma, taking a human form, rescues her several times. Eventually Satyavati is driven to attempt suicide, but is stopped by Narada, who tells her about the sixteen-Fridays fast in honor of Santoshi Ma, which can grant any wish. Satyavati completes it with great difficulty and more divine assistance, and just in the nick of time: for the now-prosperous Birju, stricken with amnesia by the angry goddesses and living in a distant place, has fallen in love with a rich merchant&rsquo;s daughter. Through Santoshi Ma&rsquo;s grace, he gets his memory back and returns home laden with wealth. When he discovers the awful treatment given to his wife, he builds a palatial home for the two of them, complete with an in-house temple to the Mother. Satyavati plans a grand ceremony of udyapan and invites her in-laws. But the nasty celestials and sadistic sisters-in-law make a last-ditch effort to ruin her by squeezing lime juice into one of the dishes. All hell breaks loose  civil war between goddesses before peace is finally restored, on earth as it is in heaven, and a new deity is triumphantly welcomed to the pantheon.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/WZQSTHtAJjQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiv Puran]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Shiv-Puran.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Shiv-Puran</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Uk4yK9D4New/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Shiv Puran" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Buraiah who is a wood cutter and do not believe the existance of god. Once when he was in work, a small boy came near to him and says him that he will see lord shiva. Buraiah do not believe the kid words. After some days, some interesting things happened on the hill beside that village. People felt saitan moving on the hill, and they approaches a saint. Unexpectedly saint says that was not saitan, it&rsquo;s non other than lord shiva and Someone will be blessed to see him. Finally the grace of god blesses Buraiah as he saw the lord unfortunately. He gets shocked seeing him and turns as his devotee</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Uk4yK9D4New" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mahadev]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Mahadev.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Navratri-Special/2014/03/22/Mahadev</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kRyxaK0p-Rs/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Mahadev" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Movie describes the importance of ayyappa Deeksha and its importance. Guruswamy explains all about the Ayyappa Deeksha do&rsquo;s &amp; don&rsquo;t .</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kRyxaK0p-Rs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
