<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/bollywood-superhit-hindi-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-23T00:18:01-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Dil]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Yeh-Dil.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:16:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Yeh-Dil</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td>![Yeh Dil](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RirwT7HjgQs/hqdefault.jpg =640x480)</td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td>![Yeh Dil](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RirwT7HjgQs/1.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Yeh Dil](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RirwT7HjgQs/2.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Yeh Dil](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RirwT7HjgQs/3.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Yeh Dil is a 2003 Indian film starring Tusshar Kapoor, Natassha. This movie proved to be one of the biggest disasters of 2003.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/RirwT7HjgQs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tan Badan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Tan-Badan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:16:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Tan-Badan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td>![Tan Badan](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Sug77Ed4ulk/maxresdefault.jpg =640x480)</td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td>![Tan Badan](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Sug77Ed4ulk/1.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Tan Badan](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Sug77Ed4ulk/2.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Tan Badan](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Sug77Ed4ulk/3.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The story is centred on Ravi, a spoiled, good for nothing rich kid, the son of Deewan-saab, a successful businessman. Deewan-saab is increasingly disappointed in Ravi&rsquo;s behaviour, because all Ravi wants to do is hang out with his dodgy girlfriend Kamini, drinking, fighting, and gambling away all his father&rsquo;s money. So when Ravi shows no signs of growing up, Deewan-saab cuts him off  NO MORE GAMBLING MONEY FOR RAVI!  Gauri  the village girl is seemingly incredibly na?ve. she hangs out with a bunch of kids. Then her pregnant friend Seema arrives in the village and enlightens her a bit more as to the ways of the world telling her something about how a baby is made on the wedding night and how it involves the groom entering the bedroom and drinking a glass of milk and then BOOM, BABY. Unfortunately, that happens anyway, quite traumatically, when Gauri witnesses Seema dying violently in childbirth. So, understandably, she&rsquo;s not especially willing, when the time comes, to marry Ravi. Nor is Ravi willing to marry Gauri. Ravi is a massive spoiled brat, and is in love with Kamini, and when Deewan-saab issues Ravi with the ultimatum get married to Gauri or no paisa for you, son, Ravi&rsquo;s response is an exceedingly mature emo scream: &ldquo;If I have to marry, it&rsquo;s Kamini or NO-ONE!&rdquo;</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Sug77Ed4ulk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pyar Ka Mandir]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Pyar-Ka-Mandir.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:16:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Pyar-Ka-Mandir</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td>![Pyar Ka Mandir](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/S7IhMPG4oaY/hqdefault.jpg =640x480)</td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td>![Pyar Ka Mandir](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/S7IhMPG4oaY/1.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Pyar Ka Mandir](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/S7IhMPG4oaY/2.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Pyar Ka Mandir](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/S7IhMPG4oaY/3.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Pyaar Ka Mandir is an Indian Bollywood family-drama film directed by K. Bapaiah released on 1 April 1988. The film stars Mithun Chakraborty, Madhavi, Nirupa Roy, Raj Kiran, Shoma Anand, Kader Khan and Aruna Irani.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/S7IhMPG4oaY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joru Ka Ghulam]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Joru-Ka-Ghulam.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:16:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Joru-Ka-Ghulam</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td>![Joru Ka Ghulam](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pAnDDPCCxtk/maxresdefault.jpg =640x480)</td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td>![Joru Ka Ghulam](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pAnDDPCCxtk/1.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Joru Ka Ghulam](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pAnDDPCCxtk/2.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Joru Ka Ghulam](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pAnDDPCCxtk/3.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Dhaneshwar Pitamber, who has four daughters. All the four daughters are not ready to marry, each one having their own reason. The daughters always play mischievous tricks on the one coming with a proposal of marriage, and their gang leader is the youngest daughter Durga. Pitamber arranges for Raju Patel to come from the U.S. and marry at least one of his daughters. Unfortunately, Raju is waylaid at the airport by two con men, Raja and Kanhaiya , and his luggage, clothes, and id. is taken over by them, and he is left in barely basic clothing at the airport, and mistaken as a beggar. Pitamber mistakes Raja as Raju and take him home. They are Welcomed with open arms by Pitamber, and Raja agrees to all conditions set up by Pitamber and his duaghters in order to get married and inherit part of the vaste wealth and fortune. Later, Pitamber asks Raja to locate three other grooms for his three daughters also, otherwise no marriage will take place, as he wants all four daughters to be married at the same time. Pitamber is so desperate to get his daughters married that he is ready to give a dowry of five crores to each son-in-law. In order to get five crores Raja solves the problems of the daughters and makes them ready for getting married. How Raja solves the daughter&rsquo;s problems forms the crux of the story.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pAnDDPCCxtk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chalo Ishq Ladaye]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Chalo-Ishq-Ladaye.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:16:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Bollywood-Superhit-Hindi-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/23/Chalo-Ishq-Ladaye</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td>![Chalo Ishq Ladaye](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XbXyJ0K6Kws/hqdefault.jpg =640x480)</td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td>![Chalo Ishq Ladaye](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XbXyJ0K6Kws/1.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Chalo Ishq Ladaye](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XbXyJ0K6Kws/2.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    <tr><td>![Chalo Ishq Ladaye](https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XbXyJ0K6Kws/3.jpg =1580x100)</td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Sapna, lives a fairly isolated life, though publicly she is thronged by fans, and has taken to drinking to ease her loneliness. Intoxicated, she runs her vehicle into a young man named Pappu, who suffers minor injuries. He recognizes her and tells her that he is her number-one fan and will do anything for her. She wants him to kill her double-timing boyfriend, Rahu. He agrees to do so, provided she kills his overbearing grandmother, to which she agrees. After Pappu completes his gruesome task, he meets with Sapna, only to be told that she does not recognize him, but when presented with proof, she relents and agrees to fulfill her part of this trade. She, along with Kokibhai, arrive at the palatial home of Pappu&rsquo;s grandmother and set out to kill her. ACP Kamat already has evidence linking Pappu to Rahul&rsquo;s sudden death and has been keeping a close eye on his whereabouts. Pappu finds out his grandmother&rsquo;s will had stated that after her death Pappu would get all her property. Pappu asks for forgiveness. Meanwhile Sapna finds out that Pappu had not killed Rahul. Sapna finds out Pappu is with the police. A blackmailer tells Sapna to bring 5 crore. ACP Kamat tells his brothers about the money. Kamat told his brothers that Rahul was not killed and was still alive. Kamat&rsquo;s assistant knows that there was something wrong so he brings Pappu with him. His grandma comes and kills all the bad guys. Pappu beats up the ACP. When Paapu tells his feelings he takes her inside the theater. Sapna tells Pappu her feelings. The movie ends when she runs up to him and hugs him.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XbXyJ0K6Kws" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
