<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Classic | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/classic/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-08T18:28:53-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patanga]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/Comedy/2013/12/10/Patanga.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-10T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/Comedy/2013/12/10/Patanga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Rorj5pn7lmo/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Patanga"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Rorj5pn7lmo/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Patanga"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Rorj5pn7lmo/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Patanga"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Rorj5pn7lmo/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Patanga"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Watch the superhit black &amp; white Bollywood blockbuster classic Hindi romantic comedy full length movie Patanga (1949), starring Nigar Sultana, Yakub, Gope, Cuckoo, Ajit, Shyama, Rajendra Nath, Raj Mehra, Poornima, Ramesh Sinha, Mohana, Shashi Kapoor, Vimi, Raj Kishore, Shyam. Directed by H S Rawail. Music composed by C Ramchandra.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Rorj5pn7lmo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vishwanath]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2013/06/30/Vishwanath.html"/>
    <updated>2013-06-30T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2013/06/30/Vishwanath</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Vishwanath"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vishwanath"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vishwanath"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vishwanath"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>An honest lawyer, Vishwanath is implicated and imprisoned at the behest of powerful underworld don, GNK and his associates. After his release from prison, Vishwanath decides to seek vengeance, but finds out that it is virtually impossible to do this through due process of law. So he decides to change his identity, hire a gang of crooks and assassins, to carry out his vendetta. Not realizing that in doing this he is alienating himself from the love of his life, Soni; and making himself a wanted man by the police, leaving his crippled sister, Munni and mom, Shanti to fend for themselves, and at the mercy of GNK and his associates.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pvMrnzfvRZ4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajnabee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2012/12/26/Ajnabee.html"/>
    <updated>2012-12-26T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2012/12/26/Ajnabee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wiv0VF1OSe4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Ajnabee"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wiv0VF1OSe4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ajnabee"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wiv0VF1OSe4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ajnabee"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wiv0VF1OSe4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ajnabee"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Watch this Bollywood film Ajnabee (1974)</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wiv0VF1OSe4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/Comedy/2012/04/09/Do-Phool---Superhit-Hindi-Comedy-Film---Ashhok-Kumar-%2C-Vinod-Mehra%2C-Mehmood.html"/>
    <updated>2012-04-09T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/Comedy/2012/04/09/Do-Phool---Superhit-Hindi-Comedy-Film---Ashhok-Kumar-,-Vinod-Mehra,-Mehmood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/N4wv_GrlCGY/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/N4wv_GrlCGY/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/N4wv_GrlCGY/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/N4wv_GrlCGY/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Mummy called them two <code>phool', whilst Daddy said they were two fools! Dewan Bahadu Atal Rai believed that both his sons, Pavitra Kumar (alias Puttan) and Charitra Kumar (also known as Chuttan) were nothing better than loafers and ne'er-do-wells. Their mother Malati stubbornly pinned her faith in Chuttan and Puttan and asserted that they were still mere children. Let us find brides for them, and then watch the results! Chuttan was the younger brother. There was a proposal of marriage for him with Shaila, daughter of the lawyer Vardhraj, who was also a practicing Vaid. Puttan accompanied his younger brother, when the latter visited the house of his proposed bride. Both brothers approved of the match. Puttan had already his own plans, and his heart's desire was Poonam' daughter of Inspector Madhusudhan. Unfortunately, the path of love is never smooth, and in desperation both brothers decided to bury themselves alive in a</code>Prem Samadhi' unless Shaila and Poonam accepted their hands. This public exhibition of their love enraged their father, who took the extreme step and turned them out of his house. Still hoping to win the hearts of their beloved, Chuttan and Puttan hatch a plot. Saying that he had murdered his brother Puttan, Chuttan rushed to Shaila to seek refuge. The poor girl believed his story, and tried to shield him from prying eyes. Meanwhile, Puttan took to a disguise, which led him to a smuggler&rsquo;s den. The criminals discovered him in their midst, and after knocking him unconscious, he was thrown into a convenient lake. Now Puttan really disappeared, and to his brother Chuttan&rsquo;s ill luck a body floated in the lake on which was found Puttan&rsquo;s identification in the shape of his jacket and watch. Chuttan was wanted for murder! The joke had boomeranged. Puttan&rsquo;s father believed that his son was still alive, a faith shared by Shaila. Puttan&rsquo;s photograph was advertised widely, with a reward offered to anyone reporting his whereabouts. Now enter into the drama Mani, who bore a striking resemblance to Puttan, his mother, and his bethrothed Rukmini. Two desperados notice the resemblance, and kidnapping the protesting Mani, carry him off to Bombay to claim the rich reward from Diwan Bahadur Atal Rai. Incidents follow, fast and furious, and the story of &ldquo;Do Phool&rdquo; races towards an unexpected climax, providing exhilarating entertainment as laughs and thrills loom as large as life. Such incidents are better enjoyed upon the screen, and it is left to the viewer to decide whether Chuttan and Puttan are <code>Do Phool' or really</code>Two Fools'.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/N4wv_GrlCGY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prince]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2012/01/31/Prince.html"/>
    <updated>2012-01-31T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Classic/2012/01/31/Prince</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dG3bEy9dn-U/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Prince"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dG3bEy9dn-U/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prince"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dG3bEy9dn-U/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prince"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dG3bEy9dn-U/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prince"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Prince Shamsher Singh (Shammi Kapoor) is the only son of the local King, is an irresponsible, alcoholic, and womanizing adult, who wants everyone to bow down before him and his princely rank. One priest refuses to do so, and Shamsher pummels him mercilessly. Frustrated, he asks the priest what he should with his mundane life, and the priest tells him that he should repent, sacrifice all his palatial pleasures, and live the life of a simple and ordinary man, and hence learn the true meaning of life, for at least six months. Shamsher agrees to do so, and arranges an accident with his car, which crashes down a mountain, explodes and is blown to smithereens. Everyone in the palace believe that Shamsher is dead. He goes to a nearby village, and a blind woman there mistakes him for her long-lost son and starts calling him Sajjan Singh. Shamsher decides to play along as Sajjan. How will life treat the Prince who is set to live as a commoner?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dG3bEy9dn-U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
