<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T09:15:13-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zindagani]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Zindagani.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Zindagani</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oSW8H1v5gBw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Zindagani" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Family ties get twisted in this complex Bollywood saga centered around Sumitra (Rakhee Gulzar), an heiress whose son Anand (Mithun Chakraborty) is mistakenly raised by a foster mother, leaving Sumitra to believe that her servant&rsquo;s daughter (Rati Agnihotri) is actually her own. Now a grown man, Anand sets out to arrest the woman who killed his real father, unaware that she&rsquo;s his own mother. And things only grow more complicated from there.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oSW8H1v5gBw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zakhmi Aurat - Bollywood Movie - Prema, Neha]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Zakhmi-Aurat---Bollywood-Movie---Prema%2C-Neha.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Zakhmi-Aurat&#8212;Bollywood-Movie&#8212;Prema,-Neha</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GyucYZKcqrI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Zakhmi Aurat - Bollywood Movie - Prema, Neha" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Zakhmi Aurat &ndash; Bollywood Movie. Producer : Imran Qureshi, Director : H. Vasu, Cast :Prema, Neha.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GyucYZKcqrI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Hai Muqaddar Ka Sikandar - Bollywood Blockbuster Movie - Chiranjeevi , Bhanu Priya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Yeh-hai-Muqaddar-ka-Sikandar---Bollywood-Blockbuster-Movie---Chiranjeevi-%2C-Bhanu-Priya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Yeh-hai-Muqaddar-ka-Sikandar&#8212;Bollywood-Blockbuster-Movie&#8212;Chiranjeevi-,-Bhanu-Priya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XnHG6KBuTcg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh hai Muqaddar ka Sikandar -  Bollywood Blockbuster Movie - Chiranjeevi , Bhanu Priya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Story of two twin brothers named Yuvraj &amp; Raju. Raju wants to take revenge of his parents murder and therefore he starts killing his parents murderers one by one. Yuvraj being a cop tries to arrest Raju but fails at it. Watch the movie to see whether Raju is succesful in taking the revenge and whether yuvraj is able to arrest his own brother.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XnHG6KBuTcg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Item Koun Hai - Shaadi Se Pehle - Akshaye Khanna & Mallika Sherawat - Bollywood Funny Scene]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/YouTube-Comedy-Week-Special/2014/03/22/Yeh-Item-Koun-Hai---Shaadi-Se-Pehle---Akshaye-Khanna-Mallika-Sherawat---Bollywood-Funny-Scene.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/YouTube-Comedy-Week-Special/2014/03/22/Yeh-Item-Koun-Hai&#8212;Shaadi-Se-Pehle&#8212;Akshaye-Khanna-Mallika-Sherawat&#8212;Bollywood-Funny-Scene</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ioJQag0cr_0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh Item Koun Hai - Shaadi Se Pehle - Akshaye Khanna &amp; Mallika Sherawat - Bollywood Funny Scene" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Funny Scene &ldquo;Yeh Item Koun Hain&rdquo; &ndash; Akshaye Khanna, Sunil Shetty &amp; Mallika Sherawat from Shaadi Se Pehle &ndash; 2006 &ndash; Bollywood Movie With English Subtitles Produced by &ndash; Subhash Ghai,  Directed by &ndash; Satish Kaushik, Starring &ndash; Akshaye Khanna, Ayesha Takia, Mallika Sherawat, Sunil Shetty, Aftab Shivdasani, Anupam Kher, Gulshan Grover, Vijayendra Ghatge, Dinesh Hingoo, Boman Irani, Hemang Tanna, Mita Vasisht, Rajpal Yadav; Music by &ndash; Himesh Reshammiya. The movie is a slapstick romantic comedy that tells the story of a man caught between two girls &ndash; his gorgeous girlfriend and a sexy model.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ioJQag0cr_0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Gulistan Hamara]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Dev-Anand-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Yeh-Gulistan-Hamara.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Dev-Anand-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Yeh-Gulistan-Hamara</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XlG0-_gIn5E/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh Gulistan Hamara" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Vijay (Dev Anand), a young and dynamic civil engineer, is assigned with the tasks of bridging the gap between Indian and Chinese villages by constructing a bridge between the two villages. This bridge was going to help them socially as well as economically, but the villagers on both sides of the border didn&rsquo;t want the bridge to be constructed. Vijay managed to convince the villagers on the Indian side to help in constructing the bridge. But the Chinese villager&rsquo;s objected to the bridge under the command of their crooked ruler, Deng Do Rani (Pran), who didn&rsquo;t want to have good relations with India. The construction of the bridge started with the help of villagers on the Indian side but to destroy progress, Deng Do Rani sends his goons to disrupt their work and threaten Vijay. But on the contrary Vijay falls in love with one of his goons, Soo Reni (Sharmila Tagore). Soo Reni also falls in love with Vijay and is moved by the benefits of the bridge after Vijay explains it to her. Deng Do Rani grows furious after he learns about Soo Reni&rsquo;s betrayal and issues orders to kill her. Will Soo Reni survive the odds stacked against her? Can Vijay triumph in his mission to build a bridge and unite the two borders?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XlG0-_gIn5E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Diljale - Full Bollywood Movie - Sai Kumar, Thriller Manju]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Yeh-Diljale---Full-Bollywood-Movie---Sai-Kumar%2C-Thriller-Manju.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Yeh-Diljale&#8212;Full-Bollywood-Movie&#8212;Sai-Kumar,-Thriller-Manju</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ZtA-D_m4-ZM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh Diljale - Full Bollywood Movie - Sai Kumar, Thriller Manju" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Yeh Diljale &ndash; Bollywood Movie. Producer : Imran Qureshi, Director :Thriller Manju, Cast :Sai Kumar, Manju.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ZtA-D_m4-ZM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yaar Gaddar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaar-Gaddar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaar-Gaddar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mGUsVvgLPsI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yaar Gaddar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Inspector Shanker Verma is an honest and dedicated Police Inspector, who has been serving on the police force for many years. He lives with his mom, and a brother, Jai. Shankar was in love with Shashi, but the affair did not last, leaving him with a broken heart. Jai, on the other hand, is precocious, and always in trouble. This precociousness lands him in a soup when he is unable to explain as to why he robbed a bank and a killed a person. Watch the full movie to know more:</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mGUsVvgLPsI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winner - the Real Hero]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Winner---The-Real-Hero.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/Winner&#8212;The-Real-Hero</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/K_pqc_PgfRo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Winner - The Real Hero" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Sakthi (Prashanth), who often gets into fights, is packed off to his grandparents home in the village. There he meets Neelima (Kiran) in a marriage ceremony and falls in love with her. But Neelima&rsquo;s marriage is already fixed with the village brute, Karan. Meanwhile, a dangerous goon named Virender is in pursuit of Neelima to exact revenge against her father. Sakthi sets out to fight Karan, Virender and Neelima&rsquo;s powerful father to triumph in his love. Will Sakthi decimate his enemies and rise to supremacy as the true winner?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/K_pqc_PgfRo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivah]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Vivah.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Vivah</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/R9upjxi7_lk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vivah" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic superhit family drama movie, Rajshri Productions&#8217; Vivah &ndash; A journey from engagement to marriage with English subtitles, starring Shahid Kapur &amp; Amrita Rao, directed by Sooraj R. Barjatya, music composed by Ravindra Jain.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/R9upjxi7_lk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vishwanath]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Vishwanath.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Vishwanath</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vishwanath" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>An honest lawyer, Vishwanath is implicated and imprisoned at the behest of powerful underworld don, GNK and his associates. After his release from prison, Vishwanath decides to seek vengeance, but finds out that it is virtually impossible to do this through due process of law. So he decides to change his identity, hire a gang of crooks and assassins, to carry out his vendetta. Not realizing that in doing this he is alienating himself from the love of his life, Soni; and making himself a wanted man by the police, leaving his crippled sister, Munni and mom, Shanti to fend for themselves, and at the mercy of GNK and his associates.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pvMrnzfvRZ4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vinod Mehra Saves Moushmi Chatterjee From Well - Comedy - Raftaar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Vinod-Mehra-Saves-Moushmi-Chatterjee-From-Well---Comedy---Raftaar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Vinod-Mehra-Saves-Moushmi-Chatterjee-From-Well&#8212;Comedy&#8212;Raftaar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TGe3DWXajPM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vinod Mehra Saves Moushmi Chatterjee From Well - Comedy - Raftaar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the hindi comedy scene from the bollywood classic hindi movie Raftaar (1975) starring Moushmi Chatterjee, Vinod Mehra,Danny Denzongpa, Ranjeet, Madan Puri &amp; Sunder. Directed by Dinesh &mdash; Ramanesh. Produced by S.I Shivadasani. Music by Sonik Omi.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TGe3DWXajPM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veerana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Veerana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Veerana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/UwwnVF_PnU0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Veerana" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>A village is terrorized by an evil witch, Nikita, who seduces men and brutally murder&rsquo;s them. Thakur Sameer apprehends Nikita and hangs her in front of the village. However Nikita&rsquo;s disciple&rsquo;s drag her corpse and prepare to resurrect her. Her evil priest decides to use the body of Sameer&rsquo;s niece, Jasmin to house the spirit of Nikita. Successful in his evil act, he brings Jasmin to his father Thakur Mahendra and claims to have rescued her in the jungle and also announces the death of Sameer. Soon Jasmin controlled by the spirit of Nikita behaves strangely and kills her aunt, which is covered up as a suicide. After the trauma, Thakur Mahendra sends Sameer&rsquo;s daughter Preeti to grow up in Mumbai, while Jasmin remains with him. After many years Preeti comes back to meet her uncle and cousin Jasmin. Meanwhile, in the area, brutal murders are occurring, and everyone is baffled.     Soon Preeti finds out the truth about Jasmin who goes on a killing spree and is unstoppable. How  much blood will be shed till Nikita has her revenge? Can Jasmin be freed of the evil spirit before its too late?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/UwwnVF_PnU0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyaagi - Rajnikanth, Mithun Chakraborty]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Tyaagi---Rajnikanth%2C-Mithun-Chakraborty.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Mithun-Chakraborty-Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/22/Tyaagi&#8212;Rajnikanth,-Mithun-Chakraborty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YSTmOIwJrQo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tyaagi - Rajnikanth, Mithun Chakraborty" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Jagdish (Mithun Chakraborty) lives a simple and honest life with his wife Savitri. Jagdish&rsquo;s co-workers and cruel parents prey on his innocence and take advantage of him. Jagdish is tormented by corruption and atrocities around him and he transforms himself into a man of absolute power. He starts moonlighting as a vigilante named Alfred to fight crime and serve justice. A man named Ranjit sets his eyes on Savitri and schemes devious plans to break her marriage. What price will Jagdish pay to vanquish evil as Alfred? Can he save his wife before it&rsquo;s too late?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YSTmOIwJrQo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tunnel Anewala Hai - 36 China Town - Johnny Lever, Tanaaz Currim, Shahid Kapoor & Kareena Kapoor]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/YouTube-Comedy-Week-Special/2014/03/22/Tunnel-Anewala-Hai---36-China-Town---Johnny-Lever%2C-Tanaaz-Currim%2C-Shahid-Kapoor-Kareena-Kapoor.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/YouTube-Comedy-Week-Special/2014/03/22/Tunnel-Anewala-Hai&#8212;36-China-Town&#8212;Johnny-Lever,-Tanaaz-Currim,-Shahid-Kapoor-Kareena-Kapoor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/P6CT06P08HY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tunnel Anewala Hai - 36 China Town - Johnny Lever, Tanaaz Currim, Shahid Kapoor &amp; Kareena Kapoor" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the hit comedy scene &ldquo;Tunnel Anewala Hai&rdquo; &ndash; 36 China Town &ndash; Shahid Kapoor &amp; Kareena Kapoor from  Subhash Ghai&rsquo;s suspense comedy film 36 China Town Directed by &ndash; Abbas-Mustan, Starring Akshaye Khanna, Kareena Kapoor, Shahid Kapoor, Isha Koppikar, Tanushree Dutta, Upen Patel, Priyanka Chopra, Paresh Rawal, Johnny Lever, Tanaaz Currim ,Payal Rohatgi, Music by &ndash; Himesh Reshammiya.The film is a murder mystery that follows the investigation of a police officer trying to find the killer of a wealthy casino owner, Sonia Chang lives in her huge mansion 36 China Town.Click on <a href="http://www.rajshri.com/Listing/Movies/Free-Hindi-Movies-New-Classic-Bollywood-Blockbuster-Films">http://www.rajshri.com/Listing/Movies/Free-Hindi-Movies-New-Classic-Bollywood-Blockbuster-Films</a> to watch full length Bollywood films absolutely Free!!</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/P6CT06P08HY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trimurti]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Trimurti.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Trimurti</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ERRHdXaNbt8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Trimurti" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Infamous Khoka Singh (Mohan Agashe) conspires against honest inspector Satyadevi Singh (Priya Tendulkar) and gets her locked up in jail by slapping a false case on her. She gives birth to her third child Romi in the prison while her other two sons Shakti and Anand are out on their own. Satyadevi accepts her jail sentence with a strong resolve that when she is out, her trimurti will help her seek revenge from Khoka Singh. However, when she is released she is shattered to know that her sons didn&rsquo;t turn out to be the ones she thought they would. Grown up Anand (Anil Kapoor) and Shakti (Jackie Shroff) got into a fight which led Anand to leave the house. He is believed to be dead. Shakti stays with Romi (Shahrukh Khan), who is very naive. All her kids are oblivious of their mother&rsquo;s existence. Romi, infact is employed by Khoka Singh who asks him to kill Satyadevi. With everything against her, will Satyadevi be able to extract her revenge from Khoka Singh? Will her trimurti ever find out about their mother and her motives?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ERRHdXaNbt8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toofan Mail - Best Comedy Scene - Madhuri Dixit, Ashok Saraf - Abodh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Toofan-Mail---Best-Comedy-Scene---Madhuri-Dixit%2C-Ashok-Saraf---Abodh.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Toofan-Mail&#8212;Best-Comedy-Scene&#8212;Madhuri-Dixit,-Ashok-Saraf&#8212;Abodh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xu5fpMuqrRs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Toofan Mail - Best Comedy Scene - Madhuri Dixit, Ashok Saraf - Abodh" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Check out the best comedy scene from the bollywood classic romantic hindi family drama movie Abodh (1984) starring Madhuri Dixit, Tapas Pal, Vinod Sharma, Ashok Saraf, Mohan Choti &amp; Dinesh Hingoo. Directed by Hiren Nag &amp; Produced by Tarachand Barjatya. Music by Ravindra Jain.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xu5fpMuqrRs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiku Talsania Superhit Comedy Scene - Bahu Beta Aur Maa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Tiku-Talsania-Superhit-Comedy-Scene---Bahu-Beta-Aur-Maa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Tiku-Talsania-Superhit-Comedy-Scene&#8212;Bahu-Beta-Aur-Maa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/U-eZxNn0JTU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tiku Talsania Superhit Comedy Scene - Bahu Beta Aur Maa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Check out the hindi comedy scene from the superhit bollywood family drama movie Bahu Beta Aur Maa (1992) starring Satish Kaul, Rama Viz, Yogesh Chabra, Pravin Sood, Asha Chandra &amp; Tiku Talsania. Directed by Pawan Dev &amp; Produced by K.L Batra. Music by Surendra Kohli.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/U-eZxNn0JTU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiku Talsania Hit Comedy Scene - Bahu Beta Aur Maa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Tiku-Talsania-Hit-Comedy-Scene---Bahu-Beta-Aur-Maa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Superhit-Funny-Scenes/2014/03/22/Tiku-Talsania-Hit-Comedy-Scene&#8212;Bahu-Beta-Aur-Maa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xEgxeKPdFoM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tiku Talsania Hit Comedy Scene - Bahu Beta Aur Maa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Check out the hindi comedy scene from the superhit bollywood family drama movie Bahu Beta Aur Maa (1992) starring Satish Kaul, Rama Viz, Yogesh Chabra, Pravin Sood, Asha Chandra &amp; Tiku Talsania. Directed by Pawan Dev &amp; Produced by K.L Batra. Music by Surendra Kohli.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xEgxeKPdFoM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Man Dharam Veer - Bollywood Action Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/The-Power-Man-Dharam-Veer---Bollywood-Action-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/The-Power-Man-Dharam-Veer&#8212;Bollywood-Action-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GpD19Tjtrgc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="The Power Man Dharam Veer - Bollywood Action Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Dharmveer The Power Man Dharam Veer &ndash; Bollywood Action Movie.  Star Cast : Shivraj Kumar, Charmi, Upendra, Sayaji Shinde.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GpD19Tjtrgc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gunda - Bollywood Movie - Atul Kulkarni, Charmi Singh, Sumant]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/The-Gunda---Bollywood-Movie---Atul-Kulkarni%2C-Charmi-Singh%2C-Sumant.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/22/The-Gunda&#8212;Bollywood-Movie&#8212;Atul-Kulkarni,-Charmi-Singh,-Sumant</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/GFlu5T5IdwE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="The Gunda - Bollywood Movie - Atul Kulkarni, Charmi Singh, Sumant" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Movie The Gunda. Director : Ramana B. V., Producer : Imran Qureshi, Cast : Atul Kulkarni, Charmi Singh, Sumant.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GFlu5T5IdwE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
