<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/blockbuster-bollywood-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:14-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yaadein]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaadein.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:03-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaadein</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yDWIk2DpjAs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yaadein" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Romantic movie Yaadein (2001) directed by Subhash Ghai &amp; produced under Subhash Ghai&rsquo;s banner Mukta Arts. The movie stars Hrithik Roshan, Kareena Kapoor, Jackie Shroff, Amrish Puri, Himani Rawat, Kiran Rathod, Anang Desai, Supriya Karnik, Avni Vasha, Madan Joshi, Suman Dutta, Suhaas Khandke, Ranjan Kapoor, Jennifer Kotwal, Rahul Singh, Dolly Bindra, Kamal Adib, Gargi Patel, Rati Agnihotri, Subhash Ghai, Akhil Ghai.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yDWIk2DpjAs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kisna: The Warrior Poet]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Kisna%3A-The-Warrior-Poet.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:03-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Kisna:-The-Warrior-Poet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xmFwiKmYLZY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Kisna: The Warrior Poet" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Kisna: The Warrior Poet is a triangular love tale of Kisna (Vivek Oberoi), a revolutionary poet, Katherine (Antonia Bernath) and Lakshmi (Isha Sharvani), set in pre-independent India. Kisna befriends Katherine and saves her from a mob of nationalists which include his own uncle and brother. Katherine&rsquo;s father is a ruthless British collector who is the root cause of this movement. Kisna is engaged to Lakshmi who is deeply and possessively in love with him. To ensure Katherine&rsquo;s safety, Kisna decides to hand her over to the British High Commission in New Delhi. Both take this perilous journey and come closer. Will Kisna be able to take her to the destination? Will their love become an hindrance in their path? What will be of Lakshmi?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xmFwiKmYLZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imtihan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Imtihan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:03-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Imtihan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VtjjAtq9lmk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Imtihan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the superhit Bollywood hit Hindi romantic movie Imtihaan (1995) directed by Harry Baweja. The movie stars Saif Ali Khan, Sunny Deol, Raveena Tandon, Gulshan Grover, Shakti Kapoor, Mohan Joshi. Music composed by Anu Malik.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VtjjAtq9lmk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Armaan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Armaan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:03-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Armaan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yB-8AoAYhgs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Armaan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Dr. Siddharth Sinha (Amitabh Bachchan) is a dedicated selfless doctor who dreams of building a state-of-the-art hospital with all the modern instruments and amenities for patient care. He has a adopted son, Akash (Anil Kapoor) who also is a doctor, working to fulfill his father&rsquo;s dream. Akash falls in love with Neha Mathur (Gracy Singh), an anesthetist in the hospital he works. Akash meets Sonia (Preity Zinta), who is the arrogant daughter of millionaire, Gulshan Kapoor (Randhir Kapoor). Soon Sonia falls for Akash and wants to marry him at any cost. Gulshan Kapoor proposes to Dr. Siddharth Sinha that he will donate a huge sum of money for his hospital project, on the condition that Akash marries Sonia . Dr. Siddharth Sinha declines the offer but passes away of a heart attack a few days later. Burdened with fulfilling his father&rsquo;s dream , Akash decides to sacrifice his love for Neha and marry Sonia. But after marriage Sonia becomes increasingly jealous of Neha and constantly accuses Akash of infidelity. Sonia&rsquo;s nature threatens the life of Neha, leaving Akash torn between two women. How will Akash deal with Sonia&rsquo;s menace? Will Neha and Akash unite?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yB-8AoAYhgs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ziddi]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Ziddi.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T09:21:02-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Ziddi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ef72Qqfwias/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ziddi" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Romantic Action Drama Movie &lsquo;Ziddi&rsquo; (1997) directed by Guddu Dhanoa &amp; produced by N.R. Pachisia. The movie stars Sunny Deol, Raveena Tandon, Anupam Kher, Farida Jalal, Raj Babbar, Ashish Vidyarthi. Music composed by Sameer Sen-Dilip Sen.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ef72Qqfwias" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
