<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/blockbuster-bollywood-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:49:12-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yaadein]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaadein.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Yaadein</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yDWIk2DpjAs/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Yaadein" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Romantic movie Yaadein (2001) directed by Subhash Ghai &amp; produced under Subhash Ghai&rsquo;s banner Mukta Arts. The movie stars Hrithik Roshan, Kareena Kapoor, Jackie Shroff, Amrish Puri, Himani Rawat, Kiran Rathod, Anang Desai, Supriya Karnik, Avni Vasha, Madan Joshi, Suman Dutta, Suhaas Khandke, Ranjan Kapoor, Jennifer Kotwal, Rahul Singh, Dolly Bindra, Kamal Adib, Gargi Patel, Rati Agnihotri, Subhash Ghai, Akhil Ghai.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yDWIk2DpjAs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivah]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Vivah.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Vivah</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/R9upjxi7_lk/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Vivah" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic superhit family drama movie, Rajshri Productions' Vivah &ndash; A journey from engagement to marriage with English subtitles, starring Shahid Kapur &amp; Amrita Rao, directed by Sooraj R. Barjatya, music composed by Ravindra Jain.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/R9upjxi7_lk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refugee - Bollywood Romantic Action Movie - Abhishek Bachchan, Kareena Kapoor]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Refugee---Bollywood-Romantic-Action-Movie---Abhishek-Bachchan%2C-Kareena-Kapoor.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Refugee---Bollywood-Romantic-Action-Movie---Abhishek-Bachchan,-Kareena-Kapoor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/S7SQVVjgG_8/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Refugee - Bollywood Romantic Action Movie - Abhishek Bachchan, Kareena Kapoor" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>A Bangladeshi Muslim family must relocate to Pakistan, for which they must cross two borders, one with India and Bangladesh and the second with India and Pakistan. The family head Manzur Ahmed (Kulbhushan Kharbanda) hires a nameless Refugee (Abhishek Bachchan) to guide the family over the immense desert to reach Pakistan. Refugee is a man of self-discipline and refuses to be emotionally involved with the people he helps to cross borders. Then he meets Manzur&rsquo;s daughter, Naaz (Kareena Kapoor) and soon they both fall in love with each other. Officials on both sides of the border are aware of the human trafficking and Refugee comes under their scanner. Indian officer of the border security forces, Raghuvir Singh (Jackie Shroff) and the Pakistani Ranger, Mohammad Ashraf (Sunil Shetty), up the ante to stop all the illegal activities on the border. Mohammad Ashraf also falls in loves with Naaz and his conflict with Refugee heightens. To complicate matters, Raghuvir Singh apprehends Refugee with a load of RDX explosives and Naaz&rsquo;s parents arrange her marriage with Mohammad Ashraf. How will Refugee break free from the Border Security Force? Will Naaz and Refugee be united in love against all odds?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/S7SQVVjgG_8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kisna: The Warrior Poet]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Kisna%3A-The-Warrior-Poet.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Kisna:-The-Warrior-Poet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xmFwiKmYLZY/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Kisna: The Warrior Poet" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Kisna: The Warrior Poet is a triangular love tale of Kisna (Vivek Oberoi), a revolutionary poet, Katherine (Antonia Bernath) and Lakshmi (Isha Sharvani), set in pre-independent India. Kisna befriends Katherine and saves her from a mob of nationalists which include his own uncle and brother. Katherine&rsquo;s father is a ruthless British collector who is the root cause of this movement. Kisna is engaged to Lakshmi who is deeply and possessively in love with him. To ensure Katherine&rsquo;s safety, Kisna decides to hand her over to the British High Commission in New Delhi. Both take this perilous journey and come closer. Will Kisna be able to take her to the destination? Will their love become an hindrance in their path? What will be of Lakshmi?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xmFwiKmYLZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imtihan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Imtihan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Bollywood-Movies/2014/03/22/Imtihan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VtjjAtq9lmk/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Imtihan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the superhit Bollywood hit Hindi romantic movie Imtihaan (1995) directed by Harry Baweja. The movie stars Saif Ali Khan, Sunny Deol, Raveena Tandon, Gulshan Grover, Shakti Kapoor, Mohan Joshi. Music composed by Anu Malik.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VtjjAtq9lmk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
