<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: South-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/south-superhit-action-dhamaka-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-07T23:01:34-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Qayamat]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/2013/05/29/Ek-Qayamat.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-29T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/2013/05/29/Ek-Qayamat</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/iIo3YTSCSUM/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Ek Qayamat"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/iIo3YTSCSUM/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Qayamat"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/iIo3YTSCSUM/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Qayamat"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/iIo3YTSCSUM/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Qayamat"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Kali who lives along with his mother on the business of hiring mike set and lighting equipment for wedding and other ceremonies. Jyothi is a singer who sings chorus in films. A lady police inspector keeps on following Kali and tries to seduce him to make him fall in her love. Kali is also a threat for many in his area as he answers only with muscle power if things work against him. Knowing this, once Jyothi claims that she is Kali&rsquo;s person to save herself from a group of eve teasers. Eve teasers leave her for the fear of Kali. In a dramatic sequence, like in any other film Kali happens to encounter Jyothi. Gopichand inclines for Jyothi and proposes her. But she negates and tells her flash back. Jyothi&rsquo;s aim is to become an IAS officer. She happens to meet Surya, who is another IAS aspirant, in a train. They make friendship and eventually love sprouts between them. For a few reasons, Surya shuns his idea of becoming IAS officer but encourages Jyothi in her attempts. He also says that he would marry her. He accentuates that he wants to see her as Jyothi Surya IAS. He also makes a nameplate in advance that reads &lsquo;Jyothi Surya IAS&rsquo;. But accidentally he gets killed in a road accident. Jyothy wishes to remain unmarried throughout her life assuming deceased Surya as her soul mate and husband.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iIo3YTSCSUM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bunny the Hero]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/2013/04/15/Bunny-The-Hero.html"/>
    <updated>2013-04-15T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/Movies/Hindi/SouthIndian/2013/04/15/Bunny-The-Hero</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/aDWsE8Hlwz4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Bunny The Hero"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/aDWsE8Hlwz4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Bunny The Hero"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/aDWsE8Hlwz4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Bunny The Hero"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/aDWsE8Hlwz4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Bunny The Hero"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Somaraju who is a leading business man in Vizag. Mysamma is a close member of Somaraju, who handles the deals of Somaraju in Hyderabad. Mahalaxmi is the daughter of Somaraju. Somaraju dearly loves his daughter. Bunny joins the same college as Mahalaxmi. He impresses Mahalaxmi on the first day itself. Slowly, she falls in love with him. Somaraju, though reluctant initially, agrees to the marriage. Now Bunny has a condition that Somaraju should give his entire property to Bunny as dowry. Bunny&rsquo;s real father is Mahalaxmi&rsquo;s mom&rsquo;s brother. He was a great man with lots of land and property, as well as lots of regard from the government and other people. When Mahalaxmi is born, Mahalxmi&rsquo;s mom asks him to perform the baby naming ceremony and such. On his way there, Somaraju attacks him with the help of a bunch of rowdies. They pretty much kill him and leave him to die in the forest. However, he manages to live and perform Mahalaxmi&rsquo;s ceremony, but he dies minutes after, without telling anyone what happened. Bunny comes to know of this when his so-called father explains to him that he is really a godfather and not a father. In trying to save him, his godfather and godmother give up their own son to keep him alive. To regain his rightful property, Bunny fights Somaraju and his rowdies.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/aDWsE8Hlwz4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
