<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Blockbuster-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/blockbuster-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-23T00:29:47-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Action Man Adhinayakudu]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/The-Action-Man-Adhinayakudu.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/The-Action-Man-Adhinayakudu</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RRW7gxg7ARc/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="The Action Man Adhinayakudu"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RRW7gxg7ARc/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="The Action Man Adhinayakudu"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RRW7gxg7ARc/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="The Action Man Adhinayakudu"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/RRW7gxg7ARc/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="The Action Man Adhinayakudu"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Harischandra Prasad who is an influential leader in Rayalaseema and he treats all his people as his children. To provide jobs to them, he decides to build a huge steel plant with the assistance of foreign collaborators. But Ramappa and his assistant oppose this. They hatch a plan to eliminate him. His son Ramakrishna thwart the villain&rsquo;s plans. But the story takes a cruel twist as the villains strike at the heart of the family by using Bobby. When Bobby was a small Kid the villains kidnap him and threaten Ramakrishna to leave his father and save Bobby. Although Harischandra Prasad has no love on Ramakrishna, he loved his father and for fulfilling his father&rsquo;s wishes he stands protecting and Bobby is said to be escaped from the house. But Ramappa and his followers make Bobby a professional killer at the age of 12 by another killer and use him to kill Harischandra Prasad. The whole family except Ramakrishna and his step-brother is unaware that Bobby killed Harischandra Prasad. Now Bobby is an adult and is a high profile professional killer and returns to his land with the help of his newly found friend Deepu who share mutual love interest. His mission in short is to protect his father from Ramappa. In this process it is revealed to the family members of Harischandra Prasad and the people that Bobby killed Harischandra Prasad and Moreover the antagonists frame Ramakrishna as the man behind the Death of Harischandra. Frustrated and deeply hurt by this, Ramakrishna&rsquo;s Step Mother and wife and the people expel the both and police arrest them and take them away for a secret encounter by Ramappa. Seeing this all, Ramakrishna&rsquo;s step brother, who was paralysed earlier in attempt to catch Bobby during the murder of Harischandra, springs back to life and reveals the whole truth to his family and the people. Meanwhile Ramkrishna and Bobby team up and kill all the frods and enemies together. Later Ramakrishna&rsquo;s step mother apologises for the ill treatment by her and orders him to fulfill his dead father&rsquo;s wishes.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/RRW7gxg7ARc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rowdy Baadshah]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Rowdy-Baadshah.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Rowdy-Baadshah</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wjBKH-SwvsM/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Rowdy Baadshah"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wjBKH-SwvsM/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Rowdy Baadshah"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wjBKH-SwvsM/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Rowdy Baadshah"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wjBKH-SwvsM/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Rowdy Baadshah"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Rama Rao who is the son of Ranjan who works as an assistant to Mafia Don Saadu Bhai is an IPS Aspirant. However, he is rejected from police work due to his fathers connections to the criminal underworld. Meanwhile his brother Siddu gets killed in a bomb blast planned by Saadu Bhai. Rama Rao seeking revenge, reunites with his father and becomes Baadshah on the advice of a police officer. He soon takes Macau from Saadu Bhai. Saadu Bhai, peeved by Rama Rao&rsquo;s aggression and guts, joins forces with his rivals and IPS officers, such as Aadi and falsely accuses Baadshah of murdering a police officer. Baadshah discovers that Saadu Bhai is planning a series of bombings in India and that Aadi is a culprit. and going to marry Janaki. So he decides to save India and also completes Operation Baadshah. So he approaches Janaki and falls in love with her. He enters as Ramji a Wedding planner in Janaki&rsquo;s house. He cleverly fools Padmanabha Simha with &ldquo;Dream Machine&rdquo; concept and uses him to collect information about Saadu Bhai. Meanwhile Saadu kidnaps police officer and threatens to kill him, Baadshah comes to the location Kills Aadi, Saadu Bhai and Crazy Robert and marries Janaki.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wjBKH-SwvsM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[No 1 Judwa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/No-1-Judwa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/No-1-Judwa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jN14KdQSUzY/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="No 1 Judwa"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jN14KdQSUzY/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="No 1 Judwa"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jN14KdQSUzY/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="No 1 Judwa"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jN14KdQSUzY/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="No 1 Judwa"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Ramachandran a genetic scientist who doesn&rsquo;t get due credit and funds for his research. He tries creating a human with several talents through baby designing, which thus leads to the birth of his sons, who are conjoined together above the waist. Since they share a common heart, doctors suggest a sacrificial surgery, to which their mother Sudha objects. They begin raising their children, Vimalan and Akhilan. In the following years, Ramachandran makes it big with the help of Sudha. His company, Locus Lacto Products, makes huge profit through their product &ldquo;Energion&rdquo;, the top-selling children&rsquo;s powdered milk energy drink in the market. Vimalan and Akhilan are poles apart in character, the former being decent and good at studies while the latter is care-free and poor at studies. Anjali joins their company as a translator. Both Vimalan and Akhilan fall for her. She, along with her Russian friend Volga, a journalist, spend their time with the brothers. Meanwhile, Anjali falls for Vimalan and Akhilan is happy for them. Volga is then revealed to be a spy who tries to steal the trade secrets of Energion. She is exposed and sent out by Ramachandran. She then takes the brothers to their cattle farm under the pretext of an interview where she takes pictures and even collects a milk sample from their farm. When Vimalan questions her, he is warned by her that Energion was an adulterated product and could lead to the death of thousands of children. She also exposes their father of killing the head of their R &amp; D department and setting the lab on fire, thereby destroying evidence. Consequently, she is murdered, but, she swallows a pen-drive containing evidences of the foul-play before dying. Anjali acquires it from the person who performs Volga&rsquo;s autopsy. She hands the pen-drive over to Vimalan. Following this, Vimalan and Akhilan are confronted by goons who try to get the pen-drive from him. Akhilan is convinced that the attack was only meant for robbing them. During this fight, Vimalan suffers a huge blow on the head. Vimalan is declared brain-dead and his heart is transplanted into Akhilan. After the twins are separated through a surgery, Anjali grows closer to Akhilan. Sudha is warned that Energion is adulterated and she confronts her husband who asks the food safety department to raid their company. But to her surprise, Energion is declared safe and hygienic. Meanwhile, Akhilan discovers that his father is behind Vimalan&rsquo;s death by tracking his assistant, Dinesh. He gets hold of the pen-drive that contains several photos, where ingredients used as cattle feed at their farm are declared as no feed. The beginning of the scheme is traced back to the fictional republic of Ukvania. Accompanied by Anjali, Akhilan sets out to solve the mystery. They get her friend Ashok&rsquo;s help, but he is subsequently killed. The photos are revealed to be athletes who were competing as Unified team under the olympic flag in the 1992 Barcelona Olympics. The athletes were declared dead in a plane crash. The investigation leads them to the army medical research centre. The truth is then revealed that Energion was originally an undetectable steroid invented by Ramachandran to improve the performance of the athletes at the world games. Though the country performed well, some of the athletes began suffering from similar health problems leading to their deaths and that their death from a plane crash was faked to avoid national shame. They also learn that the adulterant in Energion could be detected only with the addition of ionization enhancer. After being assaulted by a local mafia led by Dinesh, Akhilan manages to kill him and takes the remedial ingredients back to India. Once they are in India, Ramachandran is exposed and is about to be arrested. Akhilan requests his father to surrender but however, he discovers his father&rsquo;s ugly side and finds out that he and his brother are just a result of their father&rsquo;s failed experiment. Ramachandran also states that he used the whole society as his research lab, through Energion. His leg is then crushed by a rock after being unsuccessful in killing his son. Akhilan then leaves his father to die at the hands of rats which chew on his flesh. Akhilan gets National recognition for bravery. He later gets married to Anjali, and the couple subsequently become parents to conjoined twins.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/jN14KdQSUzY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. Mobile]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Mr.-Mobile.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Mr.-Mobile</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Ss1of1xOMRI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Mr. Mobile"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Ss1of1xOMRI/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mr. Mobile"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Ss1of1xOMRI/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mr. Mobile"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Ss1of1xOMRI/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mr. Mobile"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The story about Nookayya, who calls himself Nokia, is an expert cell phone thief. He has a good heart though and together with his friends Nampally and Charger, he takes care of orphans and abandoned kids. He is deeply in love with Shilpa, who is a waitress in a pub. Shilpa wants Nokia to settle down in life with a nice car, lots of cash and a house in order to marry. A desperate Nokia starts hunting for ways to achieve these things in life.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Ss1of1xOMRI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dangerous Khiladi 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Dangerous-Khiladi-2.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Blockbuster-Movies/2014/03/23/Dangerous-Khiladi-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QlB-BG706-o/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Dangerous Khiladi 2"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QlB-BG706-o/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Dangerous Khiladi 2"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QlB-BG706-o/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Dangerous Khiladi 2"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QlB-BG706-o/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Dangerous Khiladi 2"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Corrupt Central minister, is facing accusations over possessing black money of one lakh crore, and laundering it into Europe, through his un-suspecting daughter, Akanksha, a psychology student who goes to Barcelona to pursue higher education. Akanksha finds a diary in her flat in Barcelona, and out of curiosity she starts reading the book which unfolds the romantic drama between Sanju Reddy and Komal Shankarabharanam. Akanksha gets engaged in Paris with her father&rsquo;s hench man. Incidentally, she runs into Sanju Reddy, and gets to know him. Sanju is an engineer turned lead guitarist of a music band, and makes his living through street and stage performances. As narrated in the diary, Komal comes from an orthodox Telugu Brahmin family, into classical music, and ends up learning violin, at a musical school in Barcelona under Fiddle-professor Brahma. In a twist of fate, she falls in love with Sanju and gets approval for their inter caste marriage, from their parents in India. Komal unknowingly gets caught after a video footage that she accidentally shot while a henchman kills a Spanish Ambassador, in the process of money laundering. Sanju saves Komal from the henchman, on a couple of occasions; this is where the story in the diary ends abruptly. Out of curiosity Akanksha starts questioning Sanju about their love story and in the process ends up with disturbing facts. On continuous asking by Akanksha, Sanju tells her that Komal is dead. It is then shown in flashback that for fixing the marriage of Sanju &amp; Komal, their parents had come to Spain. It was at that time that Komal is kidnapped by the brother of Shawar Ali &amp; when Sanju comes to save her, Komal is murdered by the brother of Shawar Ali. In a fit of rage, Sanju bashes up the whole gang &amp; the brother of Shawar Ali goes into coma. On hearing this, Akanksha feels pity for Sanju &amp; falls in love with him. She also tries to bring Sanju out of the memory of Komal but in vain. Akanksha runs to Sanju to tell him about Komal and at that time, Sanju gets surrounded by the men of Shawar Ali. Sanju while bashing up his men, tells Akanksha that it was his plan to trap Akanksha in his love to avenge the death of his &amp; Komal&rsquo;s parents at the hands of Shawar Ali. It is then shown in flashback that after beating up the brother of Shawar Ali, Sanju had taken the body of Komal to the Hospital, from where Sanju&rsquo;s Dad calls up the Central Minister to arrest Shawar Ali in Spain, after watching the video footage. The Minister then calls up Shawar Ali to finish off this trouble in order to save himself. Shawar Ali, then goes to the hospital &amp; kills Sanju, his parents as well as Komal&rsquo;s parents. However, Sanju &amp; Komal do not die. It is then revealed that Sanju has been all this time waiting to get his revenge &amp; has made Akanksha his pawn in this game &amp; it was him only who faxed their photo in order to make Shawar Ali jealous, so that Shawar Ali will come himself to kill Sanju.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QlB-BG706-o" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
