<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/shahrukh-khan-superhit-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T09:13:31-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trimurti]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Trimurti.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Trimurti</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ERRHdXaNbt8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Trimurti" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Infamous Khoka Singh (Mohan Agashe) conspires against honest inspector Satyadevi Singh (Priya Tendulkar) and gets her locked up in jail by slapping a false case on her. She gives birth to her third child Romi in the prison while her other two sons Shakti and Anand are out on their own. Satyadevi accepts her jail sentence with a strong resolve that when she is out, her trimurti will help her seek revenge from Khoka Singh. However, when she is released she is shattered to know that her sons didn&rsquo;t turn out to be the ones she thought they would. Grown up Anand (Anil Kapoor) and Shakti (Jackie Shroff) got into a fight which led Anand to leave the house. He is believed to be dead. Shakti stays with Romi (Shahrukh Khan), who is very naive. All her kids are oblivious of their mother&rsquo;s existence. Romi, infact is employed by Khoka Singh who asks him to kill Satyadevi. With everything against her, will Satyadevi be able to extract her revenge from Khoka Singh? Will her trimurti ever find out about their mother and her motives?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ERRHdXaNbt8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ram Jaane]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Jaane.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Jaane</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/k6OFS0olUGs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ram Jaane" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Romance Action Drama movie Ram Jaane (1995) directed by: Rajiv Mehra. The movie stars Juhi Chawla, Shahrukh Khan, Mithun Chakraborty &amp; Mandakini.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/k6OFS0olUGs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pardes]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Pardes.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Pardes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/T-LY4gH55ck/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Pardes" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Pardes, meaning foreign land, is a story that revolves around Ganga &ndash; Mahima Chaudhary. She is a young Indian girl living in a rural village, and is brought up by her conservative Indian family. Kishorilal &ndash; Amrish Puri is a wealthy and successful businessman who lives in Los Angeles, America but is still deeply attached to his motherland India and adores the values and culture of India. On a visit to India, he meets his old friend Suraj Dev &ndash; Alok Nath and stays at their house.He hopes to find an Indian girl for his westernized, American son, Rajiv  &ndash; Apurva Agnihotri and feels that Ganga is just right.He offers a marriage proposal between Ganga and Rajiv.He sends his foster son, Arjun  &ndash; Shahrukh Khan &ndash; Little Master to to make the place suitable for Rajiv.Arjun spends many days trying to get Ganga and Rajiv to like each other and in the process becomes a close friend of Ganga. Eventually Rajiv and Ganga both agree to the wedding.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/T-LY4gH55ck" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maya Memsaab]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Maya-Memsaab.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Maya-Memsaab</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MgQDHSMboXs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Maya Memsaab" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Drama film Maya Memsaab (1993) starring Shahrukh Khan, Deepa Sahi &amp; Farooque Sheikh. Directed &amp; Produced by Ketan Mehta. Music by Hridaynath Mangeshkar.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MgQDHSMboXs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chamatkar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Chamatkar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:43:25-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Shahrukh-Khan-Superhit-Movies/2014/03/22/Chamatkar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/zF1FBG4a7XE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Chamatkar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Sunder Srivastava is a young graduate whose main ambition in life is to fulfill his father&rsquo;s dream of starting a school. He has no funds to execute his plans. Sunder&rsquo;s friend, Prem promises him a decent well paying job in Dubai. Hence, Sunder reaches Mumbai nin search of Prem. However, Prem ditches Sunder and uses his money for self benefit. Moreover, Sunder gets cheated by few thugs. Ultimately, Sunder arrives near an old Christian cemetery. Sitting on an old grave, Sunder expresses his frustration and strikes the tombstone in helplessness, but immediately apologizes to the deceased. This amuses the ghost of Amar Kumar alias Marco. Marco was the biggest hooligan around 20 years back. His own men kill him. Marco understands that only he can help Sunder to settle the scores with his enemies because Sunder is a very kind &mdash; hearted man. Will Sunder support Marco to take the revenge or will the fear of ghosts force Sunder to step back?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/zF1FBG4a7XE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
