<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29 | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/nagarjuna-birthday-superhit-movies-special-august-29/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T23:20:09-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mere Hindustan Ki Kasam]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/08/10/Mere-Hindustan-Ki-Kasam.html"/>
    <updated>2013-08-10T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/08/10/Mere-Hindustan-Ki-Kasam</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MQzS4lrUboE/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mere Hindustan Ki Kasam"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MQzS4lrUboE/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Hindustan Ki Kasam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MQzS4lrUboE/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Hindustan Ki Kasam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MQzS4lrUboE/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Hindustan Ki Kasam"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Movies Starts on a flight from Chennai to Delhi five passengers retrieve weapons hidden in the toilet and use them to hijack the plane. An engine is damaged during the struggle with the pilots so they make an emergency landing at Tirupati Airport. Government authorities arrive. The hijackers demand INR100 Crore, release of their imprisoned leader Yusuf Khan, and a fresh aircraft for their escape. National Security Guard Major Raveendra recalls the loss of a valued comrade at the shootout when he captured Yusuf Khan, and regrets not killing the terrorist at the time. He urges the government to allow a commando operation, but officials fear risking passengers' life, not trusting Raveendra&rsquo;s team. The major is frustrated when the government vacillates and it seems that Yusuf Khan might be released. Inside the flight the passengers fall into groups discussing their past lives and religion. One of the terrorists becomes sentimentally attached to Afshana, a little girl returning to Karachi after her heart operation. Another passenger frequently irritates the terrorists with bitter questions about their motives, in which he is supported by Jagdeesh, a retired army colonel. Time passes and tensions rise, until one of the passengers (a drug addict) attempts an escape but is shot down by a terrorist who warns the authorities to act soon. Raveendra&rsquo;s colleague Nawaz Khan discovers that the missing cleaner who prepared the toilet of the flight before its departure has been identified by Tamil Nadu Police. Ravi and Nawaz go to find the cleaner in the hope of getting information about the nature of weapons that were left for the hijackers. After a chase in Red Hills they capture the man, who confesses his involvement in the plot and also gives vague information about the size of the weapon that he placed in the toilet. Ravi and Nawaz deduce that it must be a plastic explosive. On his return Ravi is told the government has decided to release Yusuf Khan. But Yusuf dies in an accident while being transported to the airport. Ravi asks the officials to be very confidential about this information so that they can plan an assault without the terrorists' knowledge. However, a reporter disguises himself as an assistant to a senior police official, and so gets close to the aircraft. He records footage of the flight through his pen camera and overhears two officials talking about the accident of Yusuf Khan in the restroom. The terrorists get alarmed. Despite attempts to contain the news, the media leak it and one of the terrorists kills a passenger, seeking proof that Yusuf is alive, failing which one passenger will be killed every half-an-hour. Ravi later arranges for a scared civilian to pose as Yusuf to make the terrorists believe that Yusuf is alive and getting treated at the hospital. Meanwhile Ravi plans an operation to rescue the victims and christens it as Operation Garuda. Through a cleaning lady he secretly sends a mobile phone onto the plane in a food packet, so he can exchange information with Colonel Jagadeesh. Ravi plans to shoot the terrorists during their transit to a new flight by asking the passengers to bend down when they get a signal. The firing succeeds and four of the five terrorists are killed. The last terrorist who was affectionate to the little girl is killed with help of two passengers. The plastic explosive is found in the girl&rsquo;s bag. Ravi throws it away which explodes. The operation ends with the Prime Minister appreciating Ravi and the passengers heading to their destination.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MQzS4lrUboE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vikram]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/07/01/Vikram.html"/>
    <updated>2013-07-01T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/07/01/Vikram</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kILE-Hq8WOs/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Vikram"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kILE-Hq8WOs/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vikram"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kILE-Hq8WOs/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vikram"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kILE-Hq8WOs/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Vikram"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about a garage mechanic, Vikram, is the Chief mechanic for the upcoming Roots Company Challenge 1991 Automotive rally race. which starts via the route from Chennai coast to Goa coast, a route which is noted. Retired Major Harischandra prasad is the Chief guest for the Rally, his daughter Padmini also competes for the Roots Challenge Trophy. Further, Vikram&rsquo;s journalist friend Sudhakar (Chinna) after witnessing the murder of city D.I.G., gets murdered by the group of goons near his garrage, The D.I.G.&rsquo;S murder happens to be planned by a high profile unknown criminal. Police commissioner who is a close associate to Harischandra prasad is up to unweaving the mysterious murder of D.I.G and the journalist. On the other hand, Vikram finds himself beaten by the goons after he comes to the assistance of his journalist friend. When he regains his senses he finds himself with a revolver in his hand and in Police custody, arrested and charged with the homicide of the very friend he tried to assist. With evidence pointing toward his guilt, he has virtually no defense and may well spend the rest of his life in prison or be hanged. He manages to escape from the prison with the help of Vikram&rsquo;s garage assistant, Golconda through the journalist&rsquo;s friend in a water tanker. Interestingly, in guise of the journalist&rsquo;s friend (joseph),the high profile criminal&rsquo;s henchmen is hidden in the tanker. The criminal&rsquo;s henchmen plans to blast the water tanker and kill Vikram who flees from prison in the same water tanker. But, after a battle with the henchmen,inside the water tanker, Vikram escapes and jumps from the water tanker into a lake and the henchmen dies in the water tanker explosion. Police send Vikram&rsquo;s case to CBI as they come to a conclusion that it was Vikram who was killed in the water tanker explosion. Now, Vikram gets to participate in the &lsquo;one halt race&rsquo; by joining at a mile stone of the route, being in guise of the garage assistant&rsquo;s race car . Vikram also finds out that among 3 cars of the rally, the photogarphs of D.I.G&rsquo;s murder caught by his journalist friend are hidden. In another twist, Padmini happens to drive one of the 3 cars where in the photographs were hidden.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kILE-Hq8WOs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naya Jigar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/24/Naya-Jigar.html"/>
    <updated>2013-04-24T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/24/Naya-Jigar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/KNFXTMDz2bo/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Naya Jigar"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/KNFXTMDz2bo/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Naya Jigar"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/KNFXTMDz2bo/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Naya Jigar"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/KNFXTMDz2bo/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Naya Jigar"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Aravind, Chandru and Krishna Murthy who are childhood friends. Chandru and Krishna Murthy are orphans, who are generously brought up by the parents of Aravind. By the time they reach their 20&rsquo;s, Aravind&rsquo;s sister Amrita falls in love with Chandru. Chandru hesitates to love her, as she is the sister of his close friend. Chandru seeks the help of Krishna Murthy to avoid Amrita. After the entire episode, Aravind and Chandru go to Hyderabad to work with Krishna Murthy. When this trio is assigned to renovate an old palatial house, Aravind encounters Padmini. A mischief by the jealous cousin of Padmini results Aravind falling for Padmini. When Padmini is about to get engaged to another guy, Chandru announces that Padmini cheated Aravind after loving him.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KNFXTMDz2bo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meri Jung]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/24/Meri-Jung.html"/>
    <updated>2013-04-24T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/24/Meri-Jung</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/j_jK-r7fG0U/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Meri Jung"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/j_jK-r7fG0U/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Meri Jung"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/j_jK-r7fG0U/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Meri Jung"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/j_jK-r7fG0U/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Meri Jung"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Mass who 1is an orphan, who bonds well with his landlord&rsquo;s son Adi. He is behind a collegian Anjali who happens to be the daughter of Vizag city&rsquo;s mafia don Satya. This restricts her from falling for him, as it would land him in danger but she finally gives in after some time. She suggests that he ties the knot immediately before her brother and father try separating them. The gangsters in the process kill Mass&rsquo;s best friend Adi, when he tries to stop them when they try separating the lead pair, before their marriage. The hero moves into Vizag and stays in an apartment hiding his identity to take revenge on the mafia dons. Finally his quest for revenge is complete, and also he eliminates the anti-social elements in the society by killing them.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/j_jK-r7fG0U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gambler No : 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/15/Gambler-No-%3A-1.html"/>
    <updated>2013-04-15T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Nagarjuna-Birthday-Superhit-Movies-Special-August-29/2013/04/15/Gambler-No-:-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/88AE9SchRHs/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Gambler No : 1"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/88AE9SchRHs/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gambler No : 1"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/88AE9SchRHs/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gambler No : 1"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/88AE9SchRHs/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gambler No : 1"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Ramesh, nicknamed Rummy who loves his childhood friend Janaki, who asks him to become rich and powerful before marrying her. With this motive, Rummy starts gambling and becomes rich in no time. ACP Sekhar takes notice of his activities and attempts to catch him. Rummy then moves to Goa where he meets Chandra, a pub owner who also runs gambling in it. Both of them enter into a deal. While on the task, Rummy rescues Sara from Victor. Sara&rsquo;s sister Nadia falls in love with him. Another woman, Sandhya, enters his life. She helps him in his task. Meanwhile, differences arise between Rummy and Chandra, and they become rivals.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/88AE9SchRHs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
