<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Horror-Films | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/horror-films/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:42:28-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mahakaal]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Mahakaal.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Mahakaal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/zC0Ey6p2_Rw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mahakaal" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Teenager Anita (Archana Puran Singh) is the daughter of the police chief, whose life becomes terrorized by nightmares of a sinister figure stalking her and trying to kill her. The monster in her dream has a mutilated face and knives attached to his fingers and on waking up, she finds cuts on her arms. Soon Anita&rsquo;s friends start to die in mysterious and bloody circumstances. Soon Anita discovers that not only does the monster in her nightmares link to a tragic incident in her family&rsquo;s past, but every nightmare brings him one step closer to permanently re-entering the real world.  Aided by her boyfriend, Prakash, and a bizarre Michael Jackson wannabe named Canteen, Anita fights to survive the horror.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/zC0Ey6p2_Rw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veerana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Veerana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Veerana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/UwwnVF_PnU0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Veerana" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>A village is terrorized by an evil witch, Nikita, who seduces men and brutally murder&rsquo;s them. Thakur Sameer apprehends Nikita and hangs her in front of the village. However Nikita&rsquo;s disciple&rsquo;s drag her corpse and prepare to resurrect her. Her evil priest decides to use the body of Sameer&rsquo;s niece, Jasmin to house the spirit of Nikita. Successful in his evil act, he brings Jasmin to his father Thakur Mahendra and claims to have rescued her in the jungle and also announces the death of Sameer. Soon Jasmin controlled by the spirit of Nikita behaves strangely and kills her aunt, which is covered up as a suicide. After the trauma, Thakur Mahendra sends Sameer&rsquo;s daughter Preeti to grow up in Mumbai, while Jasmin remains with him. After many years Preeti comes back to meet her uncle and cousin Jasmin. Meanwhile, in the area, brutal murders are occurring, and everyone is baffled.     Soon Preeti finds out the truth about Jasmin who goes on a killing spree and is unstoppable. How  much blood will be shed till Nikita has her revenge? Can Jasmin be freed of the evil spirit before its too late?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/UwwnVF_PnU0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teri Talash Mein]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Teri-Talash-Mein.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Teri-Talash-Mein</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NC5jpFSuDgY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Teri Talash Mein" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the Bollywood Full Length Classic Drama Romantic Thriller Horror Movie &lsquo;Teri Talash Mein&rsquo; (1990) directed by Vinod Talwar &amp; produced by Pawan Kumar. The movie stars Amala Akkineni, Leena Nair, Krishna. Music composed by Naresh Sharma.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/NC5jpFSuDgY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tahkhana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Tahkhana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Tahkhana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/lITb92BEDa8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tahkhana" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Thakur Surjeet Singh hands over his entire estate to his son, Raghuvir, disowning the other, Dhurjan, the family&rsquo;s black sheep. Dhurjan swears to use his black magic to usurp the estate, and abducts Raghuvir&rsquo;s daughters, Sapna and Aarti. Raghuvir is killed while trying to save his daughters and asks his friend Mangal to rescue his daughters. Soon Dhurjan is apprehended and is imprisoned in a dungeon. While Arti is rescued, the fate of Sapna remains unknown. Before dying, Raghuvir informs Mangal that Sapna has one of two pieces of a locket around her neck, while the other is on Aarti&rsquo;s, and when joined together will reveal the location of a treasure buried in a dungeon. Twenty years later, Aarti and her boyfriend, Vijay, along with several others,  attempt to unearth this treasure. But soon they get entangled in a bloody massacre when they face betrayal from one of their own and  release a vicious monster that will hunt and kill them one by one. Can the treasure seekers survive the horror they have unleashed? Can the resurrected monster be stopped before its too late?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/lITb92BEDa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saamri]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Saamri.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Horror-Films/2014/03/22/Saamri</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SRv7o-BQFY0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Saamri" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Feared by many, a wealthy old man named Saamri, lives alone in his huge mansion and is known for his magic and exorcism. Saamri realizes that his end is near and summons his lawyer and wills his entire estate to his niece, Anju. But when Taklifchand, Saamri&rsquo;s step-brother, finds this out he plans to murder Saamri and take control over the estate. Taklifchand together with a  young woman, Maria, a hotel owner, Khanna, professor Chatterjee, and others, kill Saamri. They throw his body in the river, and cover up the murder. With the case closed, Taklifchand and the others must eliminate Anju and keep the wealth and estate for themselves. Before they could carry out their sinister plans, one by one they start dying horrible deaths. Saamri has arisen from the grave to hunt down his murderers, and wont stop until he drains the blood of everyone responsible.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/SRv7o-BQFY0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
