<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: 2013-Top-25-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/2013-top-25-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-07T23:01:34-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fighterman Singam]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/09/20/The-Fighterman-Singam.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-20T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/09/20/The-Fighterman-Singam</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Singam a honest police sub inspector of Nallur. He belongs to Nallur with his father having a respectable status in the village. His family business is provision stores and singam wants to join it, but he joined police due to his father&rsquo;s wishes. He resolves most of the problems in his village with non-violence and mutual counselling. He uses force only when the situation demands it, thereby gaining much reputation and love from the villagers. Mahalingam is an industrialist in Chennai and a friend of Singam&rsquo;s father . He comes to the village with his beautiful daughter Kavya. Eventually Singam and Kavya fall in love with each other. Everything seems to be smooth until Chennai based Shankar, a big-time extortionist with shady mafia dealings who blackmails people by complaining to the Income Tax Department, is required to travel to Nallur to sign a conditional bail. He instead, sends one of his allies to do the formalities, much to the anger and rage of Singam who demands Shankar sign the bail in person. Humiliated, Shankar reaches Nallur but is unable to take any revenge on Singam fearing the immense love and devotion of the entire village towards Singam. Using his political contacts, he gets Singam transferred to Chennai to teach him a lesson. The gangster then swears to seek revenge and humiliate him.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/2-FkBmbCTf4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mard Ki Zaban]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/09/13/Mard-Ki-Zaban.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-13T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/09/13/Mard-Ki-Zaban</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Ram the only son of a wealthy and influential farmer Anjaneya Prasad. Anjaneya Prasad is a happy and contented man. He lives happily with his son Ram, three daughters, sons-in-law, and grandchildren in the same house. However, he has one wish unfulfilled that is to see his son marry and settle down in life. But Ram keeps delaying marriage, as he is apprehensive whether his wife will agree to live in a joint family. However, Ram finally relents after he comes across Raja Rajeswari in unexpected circumstances and falls in love with her. Raja Rajeshwari is the daughter of politician Chamundeshwari and Shankar Rao. The families agree to the marriage but even before the newly weds can go home a small issue between the two families get blown out of proportion. As a result, the two families break up the marriage and part ways. Later, Ram and Rajeswari plans to go abroad for some time to overcome their grief. In a coincidence, the two of them head to the same place Mauritius. Into this Ram meets an old friend Shraddha Das who is madly in love with Ram. However, the married couple reconciles their differences and marries in Mauritius. They come back to India only to face the wrath of their respective families. How they come out of the situation is the remaining part of the story.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/SIsNMl-LlPw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeene Nahi Doonga]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/08/16/Jeene-Nahi-Doonga.html"/>
    <updated>2013-08-16T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/08/16/Jeene-Nahi-Doonga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QxLzn_RhhC8/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Jeene Nahi Doonga"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QxLzn_RhhC8/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jeene Nahi Doonga"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QxLzn_RhhC8/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jeene Nahi Doonga"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QxLzn_RhhC8/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jeene Nahi Doonga"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Bullet Raja who is a small time crook with a good heart. He bumps into Swetha at a function and falls in love with her. But Swetha is already engaged to Harbour Babu, a powerful local goon. Harbour Babu hatches a plan to finish off Bullet Raja and he succeeds in his efforts. Bullet Raja heads to Yamalokam where he realises that his life has unjustly been terminated by Chitragupta and so he picks up a fight with Yamadharma Raja. A helpless Yamadharma Raja decides to send him back to earth into the body of Home Minister Ravindra, who is killed by his associates Balram, Shantaram and Pavitrananda. After Bullet Raja enters into Ravinder&rsquo;s body, he confronts his enemies and fulfills the wishes of his mother Parvathamma and his followers.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QxLzn_RhhC8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[No.1 Mr. Perfect]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/08/02/No.1-Mr.-Perfect.html"/>
    <updated>2013-08-02T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/08/02/No.1-Mr.-Perfect</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/7tKgWCjIq7A/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="No.1 Mr. Perfect"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/7tKgWCjIq7A/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="No.1 Mr. Perfect"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/7tKgWCjIq7A/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="No.1 Mr. Perfect"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/7tKgWCjIq7A/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="No.1 Mr. Perfect"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Vicky, an expert in gaming software, lives in Australia and never compromises in his life, a principle he adheres to since his childhood. He believes that one should be oneself in a relationship and one shouldn&rsquo;t change one&rsquo;s orientation for the sake of the partner. He also encourages his friends to follow his principle of life. But Vicky&rsquo;s principles and attitude leads to a clash of interests with his father, who constantly advises him to adjust his character for his and other&rsquo;s happiness but to no avail. Meanwhile in India, Vicky&rsquo;s parents arrange a wedding alliance between him and Priya, Vicky&rsquo;s childhood friend who is a doctor by profession. She and Vicky are poles apart; while Vicky is modern in his thinking and is not ready to compromise with his life, Priya is traditional and conservative and is ready to compromise for the happiness of others. Initially, Vicky and Priya do not get along well, and both play practical jokes on one another. But later, on her father&rsquo;s advice, Priya attempts to change her attitude towards Vicky. Soon Priya falls in love with Vicky and changes in many ways for him, such as giving up her love of classical dance as Vicky does not like it, eating non-vegetarian food and wearing modern dresses. Vicky too begins to fall in love with her and is ready to accept the wedding proposal until he finds out that Priya has compromised on her interests for his sake. He rejects the wedding proposal and returns to Australia. Back in Australia, Vicky is matched up through a Cadbury survey with Maggie, a free-spirited modern girl who shares his no-compromise attitude. Both of them meet at a mall and interested in each other, begin to date and soon decide to get married. However, Maggie&rsquo;s father is none other than the MindGames head&rsquo;s brother, who is unwilling to let Vicky marry Maggie. After much persuasion from Vicky, Maggie&rsquo;s father agrees to let Vicky marry Maggie on the condition that he should stay in his house for 4 days for Maggie&rsquo;s sister&rsquo;s wedding and if Vicky manages to win over at least 2 relatives of Maggie, he can marry her and he would get a business in India else he should forget Maggie and leave the contract. But Vicky changes the condition that if at least 1 relative of Maggie does not get convinced that Vicky is the correct match for Maggie then he would forget Maggie and leave the contract, else he would marry Maggie and does not leave the contract. Soon, the relatives begin pouring in from India and among them, to Vicky&rsquo;s shock, is Priya, who happens to be the groom&rsquo;s cousin. During the 4 days, with the help of Priya, he manages to win over the entire family. It is clear that Vicky is going to win Maggie&rsquo;s father&rsquo;s challenge. Priya leaves for India on the night before Vicky wins the challenge, heartbroken at the thought that Vicky is marrying someone else. Vicky receives a message Priya had recorded prior to him rejecting her on his mobile phone where she had declared her love for him. He gains a change of heart on seeing this message and realises how much Priya had loved him and was willing to change for him, in spite of his faults. He also realises the need for compromises in life. Vicky conveys his feelings to all the wedding guests present and decides not to marry Maggie. Maggie understands his feelings and accepts his decision. Vicky returns to India to win back Priya. After initially playing hard-to-get, Priya accepts Vicky&rsquo;s love and they live happily ever after.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/7tKgWCjIq7A" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Tha Soldier]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/07/15/Ek-Tha-Soldier.html"/>
    <updated>2013-07-15T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/07/15/Ek-Tha-Soldier</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mE_rbRKOeTI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Ek Tha Soldier"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mE_rbRKOeTI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Tha Soldier"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mE_rbRKOeTI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Tha Soldier"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mE_rbRKOeTI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Tha Soldier"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Aishwarya who is the daughter of central union home minister Raya. Due to some reason, he doesn&rsquo;t allow his daughter to go on a trip with friends. She nonetheless goes to the trip. She then meets a guide, Shakti, who takes the group on a trip to several places. At first, she hates him because he uses every chance to get money from her. But when he saves her, she starts liking him. Afterwards, a few people who are chasing her finally find her in Kashmir and try to kill Shakti as he hurt&rsquo;d them earlier. Their plan fails as Shakti turns out to be a Secret Agent and defends himself and catches the main person in this plan. When Aishwarya goes back to her father, he forgives her and asks whether she had taken a box in which there is a diamond. When she replies in the negative, he says that it is more important than his own daughter. Later, when Shakti goes to a temple, the diamond box falls off a basket his mother brought with flowers on top of it. They inform Mahadevaya who asks them to immediately come to Humpy with the box and Aishwarya. Their travel is blocked by a strong man who is then defeated by Shakti. He then kills one more person who tries to grab the box. Then Mahadeva Raya and a Swami come to him and then the flashback is revealed. It is said that Mahadeva Raya'a father was a royal king who was extremely generous and had the blessings of god which gave him the power that whenever he touched the diamond, it used to shine brightly emitting light. He reveals that apart from the 18 Shakti petas, there is a secret one which protects India and only their family knows of it. There is also a protector who guards it at all times. His name is Rudra. After every 27 years, they must go to the shakti peta where the protector will perform several spiritual rites which must be compulsorily performed. When he starts performing them, an Egyptian king who knows of this comes to destroy the shakti peta. The protector kills the king but a person who works under the Mahadeva Raya&rsquo;s father, Janaki Varma cheats him and kills both the protector and Mahadeva Raya as he sought money from the king. He also steals a sword which is necessary for the rites to be performed. When the protector is killed, his wife, at the same time, delivers a baby boy whom Rudra gives to his loyal servant. The servant tries his best to save the boy but circumstances force him to throw the boy into the river. The boy is then found by a childless couple who adopt him. After finding out his past, he sets out for revenge. Shakti then goes to Janaki&rsquo;s country where he is presently the underworld don and a multimillionaire. He kills Janaki and gets the sword. Finally he goes to perform the rites but is stopped by the Egyptian queen and her powerful son who comes back and cannot be defeated. The swami then tells him that the strong man can only be defeated by damaging his eyes. He then kills him and performs the rites.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mE_rbRKOeTI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
