<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: 2013-Top-25-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/2013-top-25-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:34-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Kaisa Karz]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about SRK who is a real estate contractor. He uses muscle power to encroach land and make money. His business rival Gopala Krishna GK is the &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; of GK Constructions. GK has the power to handle goons as well as the real estate business. He calls for applications from MBA graduates as his personal secretary. None of the applicants reach his expectations. He accidentally meets Anuradha Anu and thinks that she is fit for the job. As a &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; he is tough with his staff but has lots of concern over them. During a trip to Malaysia, Anu and GK get closer and Anu loses her heart to GK. When she is about to confess her love, Anu gets involved in a petty issue and faces the wrath of GK. Consequently, she resigns from her job. GK calls for interviews for his personal secretary again and zeroes in on Sruthi. It is revealed that she was planted in GK&rsquo;s office by SRK. In order to get her father Rammurthy released from a false case, Sruthi steals a tender file. However, she does not hand it over to SRK and demands her father&rsquo;s release. The crooked SRK does not listen to her. At this juncture, she tries to escape from the scene and is saved by GK at the insistence of Anu. However, Anu is injured in the attack by goons in the process, but goes straight to the Tenders office and files the tender to save GK from a huge loss and to fulfill his ambition of securing his dream project. When GK is about to thank her, she admits her love for him, only to learn of his past. In the flashback, GK reveals that he loved Sanjana and married her. She died in a tsunami shortly after. He says he can&rsquo;t replace Sanjana. GK refuses Anu&rsquo;s love politely. As time goes by, Sanjana&rsquo;s mother Sumitra dies of illness in Malaysia and her husband Viswanath tells GK that her last wish is the marriage of GK with Anu. GK also gets a feeling that Sanjana also wants the same. He returns to India and unites with Anu and the film ends on a happy note.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ueSTOqmJSJA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fighter Man: Ghayal]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/The-Fighter-Man%3A-Ghayal.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/The-Fighter-Man:-Ghayal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vk0uat6WBL0/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="The Fighter Man: Ghayal"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vk0uat6WBL0/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighter Man: Ghayal"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vk0uat6WBL0/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighter Man: Ghayal"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vk0uat6WBL0/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighter Man: Ghayal"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about an Auto mobile mechanic Ashok is thrown out of the house by his rough acts which kills his grand mother .His father is compelled to throughout hero. The heroine is a neighbour and Ashok falls in love with her, the Villain in an accident sees the heroine and he also falls in love with her. While saving the heroine from the clutches of villain, the Ashok&rsquo;s friend is killed by the villain gang. This angers the hero who is sent off to Delhi according to a plan laid by villain, villain&rsquo;s mother and hero&rsquo;s father and he rushes back to Hyderabad to save his family and the heroine. The climax fight shot in side the house is breathtaking. Finally as usual the hero is fighting with the villain the villain is about to loose the battle to safe guard the villain, villain&rsquo;s mother enters the scene to shoot the hero. At last, the bullet hits the villain, The villain&rsquo;s mother falls down and the hero takes away the heroine.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vk0uat6WBL0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don No: 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Don-No%3A-1.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Don-No:-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ugbVqFWWkkQ/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Don No: 1"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ugbVqFWWkkQ/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Don No: 1"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ugbVqFWWkkQ/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Don No: 1"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ugbVqFWWkkQ/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Don No: 1"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The story begins when a teen named Suri escapes and finds a drug dealer tormenting some little boys. Suri guns down the drug dealer. One of the boys, Raghava expresses his wish to join him. The rest of the boys too become Suri&rsquo;s helpers and eventually his henchman. The film continues 20 years later with Suri and Raghava and with the establishment of the fact that Suri is the Don with a golden heart. Then of course, he has Raghava as his sidekick, who adores him to death. Together, they rule the underworld of Andhra Pradesh. Since he is the unopposed kingpin, our don even has time for a song and dance on his birthday with his basti people. Everything is peaceful and hunky dory. But only till Feroz enters the scene. Feroz is a feared don throughout India and he wants to add Andhra Pradesh to his underworld fiefdom. That&rsquo;s what sets off the battle of the dons. Suri begins to upset Feroz, because Suri refuses to work with Feroz. In many attempts to kill Suri, Feroz&rsquo;s men get killed. One man wants to kill Raghava. Eventually, Don lets Raghava kill the man because the man also hosted a hideout for Feroz&rsquo;s men in Hyderabad. Meanwhile, Don falls in love with Priya, at first she doesn&rsquo;t like him but later she also begins to like him. Raghava also finds a girl he likes. In that process, Raghava is cornered, where his fiance Nandhini, ends up being on the villains side. Raghava is killed. In a final meet between Suri &amp; Feroz, Feroz returns Raghava&rsquo;s bullet ridden body and challenges Suri for a fight on a condition that &lsquo;A person will lose 2 of his men for each fall he takes&rsquo;. Angered &amp; heartbroken on Raghava&rsquo;s death, Suri accepts his challenge. As the fight progresses, Suri loses 2 of his men. Determined to win, Suri continues the fight and thrashes up Feroz &amp; his two well trained women bodyguards. The fight ends with Feroz getting killed by Suri &amp; he warns Feroz&rsquo;s remaining men not to be like their boss or else they&rsquo;ll end up like him.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ugbVqFWWkkQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheetah the Power of One]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Cheetah-The-Power-Of-One.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Cheetah-The-Power-Of-One</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yJwaNkAChsI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Cheetah The Power Of One"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yJwaNkAChsI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Cheetah The Power Of One"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yJwaNkAChsI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Cheetah The Power Of One"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yJwaNkAChsI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Cheetah The Power Of One"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Movie is about Babloo who likes to have fun and is always getting in trouble. So his father Narayana gets him a job with Shanker Goud. Shanker Goud and Bhallu are rivals and Bhallu is determined to kill Shanker Goud&rsquo;s sister Pooja. Babloo falls in love with Pooja but Shanker is planning an arranged marriage for her with Ajay. Babloo and Pooja elope to get married. Babloo saves Pooja from Bhallu. The Movie is about Nanda Gopal /Nandu who is a professional assassin, and Malli is his partner. They charge Rs. 1.5 crore per assassination. A party leader, Shiva Reddy, wants someone to attempt an assassination on him so that he can get more Sympathy votes in the upcoming election. Shiva Reddy&rsquo;s colleague Baji Reddy hooks him up with Nandu for a deal. However, before Nandu can shoot Shiva Reddy, someone else fatally shoots him. Within minutes, police surround the building. Just before the exit of the building, a big car accident occurs on the street with Nandu&rsquo;s car. Nandu assumes that Malli got trapped and died in the accident. So Nandu goes to the top of the skyscraper. With the police behind him and in front of him, he is helpless. Suddenly a train comes and Nandu uses a rope to jump from the skyscraper to the train.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yJwaNkAChsI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sabse Badhkar Hum]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Sabse-Badhkar-Hum.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T01:05:27-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/23/Sabse-Badhkar-Hum</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The movie starts in the late 1980s when a group of friends celebrate their farewell party. They promise each other to keep in touch. Among them are Hanumantha Rao, who has a son named Prabha, and Vishwanath who has daughter Nandini. To reach their professional goals, Vishwanath and his daughter travel to Switzerland, while Hanumantha Rao becomes a criminal lawyer and settles in India. Thus, Prabha and Nandini get separated in their childhood. Years later, these old friends call for a reunion where a grown-up Prabha is eager to see his love Nandini. But, another girl Nisha, daughter of local don, attempts suicide when Prabha doesn&rsquo;t accept her love. Her father tries to kill Prabha and his friends but Prabha gets out of trouble by faking a story about his childhood love Nandini. During the reunion at the farm house of Buchchaiah, Prabha happens to see Nandini. He tries various tantrums to impress her, but in vain. His attempts are always thwarted by her brother. One day, he knowingly gives a lead about his sister&rsquo;s favorite game of Basketball, forcing Prabha and his team to create a Basketball court. As they play basketball, in comes Rishi, as Appala Raju&rsquo;s son, who gatecrashes into the game as he is cheered by Nandini. Both Rishi and Prabha both vie with each other to impress Nandini, leading to a cold war between them. Meanwhile, Prasanna, daughter of Buchchaiah, confesses to Prabha that she was in love with a man and she would marry him if she could pay a dowry of 50 lakhs, and she forces Prabha to talk to her father into marrying off her to her boyfriend. Prabha is able to convince Buchchaiah about his daughter&rsquo;s marriage with the help of his father and his friends. Impressed by his managing skills, Nandini too begins to like Prabha. Jealous of Nandini&rsquo;s liking for Prabha, Rishi&rsquo;s friends try to paralyse Prabha by misconnecting the power cable of an iron box. Hanumantha Rao, unaware of their conspiracy, accidentally touches the iron box and gets an, leading to a scuffle between Prabha and Rishi. The fight results in Hanumantha Rao ejecting Prabha out of the house. Later, Prabha finds out that Rishi is not Appala Raju&rsquo;s son, but the nephew of Vishwanath. Vishwanath betrayed his father by marrying his girlfriend rather than the girl chosen by his father. As a result, he is ousted by his father. Hanumantha Rao, on behalf of Viswanath negotiates with his father for a reconciliation. After many attempts, he agrees to forgive Viswanath but on the condition that his daughter&rsquo;s son should marry Nandini. Prabha decides not to reveal his love for Nandini and makes up his mind to leave. As Prabha tries to leave, Nandini reveals that she too loves him. But to save his father&rsquo;s reputation, he doesn&rsquo;t reveal his love to her and leaves the place leaving Nandini heartbroken. Nisha&rsquo;s father too realizes the truth that the story that Prabha had said was a lie, and tries to kill Prabha. Meanwhile, Nandini gets to know the truth behind Prabha&rsquo;s silence and convinces her father that she loves Prabha and he should get her married to Prabha. Prabha is rescued from Nisha&rsquo;s father in time by Nandini, who urges Nisha&rsquo;s father to spare Prabha as both of them love each other. The film ends with Prabha and Nandini getting married.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MzSq1oPhJgI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
