<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: 2013-Top-25-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/2013-top-25-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T22:30:42-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fighterman Singam]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/09/20/The-Fighterman-Singam.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-20T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/09/20/The-Fighterman-Singam</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2-FkBmbCTf4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="The Fighterman Singam"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Singam a honest police sub inspector of Nallur. He belongs to Nallur with his father having a respectable status in the village. His family business is provision stores and singam wants to join it, but he joined police due to his father&rsquo;s wishes. He resolves most of the problems in his village with non-violence and mutual counselling. He uses force only when the situation demands it, thereby gaining much reputation and love from the villagers. Mahalingam is an industrialist in Chennai and a friend of Singam&rsquo;s father . He comes to the village with his beautiful daughter Kavya. Eventually Singam and Kavya fall in love with each other. Everything seems to be smooth until Chennai based Shankar, a big-time extortionist with shady mafia dealings who blackmails people by complaining to the Income Tax Department, is required to travel to Nallur to sign a conditional bail. He instead, sends one of his allies to do the formalities, much to the anger and rage of Singam who demands Shankar sign the bail in person. Humiliated, Shankar reaches Nallur but is unable to take any revenge on Singam fearing the immense love and devotion of the entire village towards Singam. Using his political contacts, he gets Singam transferred to Chennai to teach him a lesson. The gangster then swears to seek revenge and humiliate him.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/2-FkBmbCTf4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Kaisa Karz]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/07/10/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz.html"/>
    <updated>2013-07-10T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/07/10/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about SRK who is a real estate contractor. He uses muscle power to encroach land and make money. His business rival Gopala Krishna GK is the &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; of GK Constructions. GK has the power to handle goons as well as the real estate business. He calls for applications from MBA graduates as his personal secretary. None of the applicants reach his expectations. He accidentally meets Anuradha Anu and thinks that she is fit for the job. As a &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; he is tough with his staff but has lots of concern over them. During a trip to Malaysia, Anu and GK get closer and Anu loses her heart to GK. When she is about to confess her love, Anu gets involved in a petty issue and faces the wrath of GK. Consequently, she resigns from her job. GK calls for interviews for his personal secretary again and zeroes in on Sruthi. It is revealed that she was planted in GK&rsquo;s office by SRK. In order to get her father Rammurthy released from a false case, Sruthi steals a tender file. However, she does not hand it over to SRK and demands her father&rsquo;s release. The crooked SRK does not listen to her. At this juncture, she tries to escape from the scene and is saved by GK at the insistence of Anu. However, Anu is injured in the attack by goons in the process, but goes straight to the Tenders office and files the tender to save GK from a huge loss and to fulfill his ambition of securing his dream project. When GK is about to thank her, she admits her love for him, only to learn of his past. In the flashback, GK reveals that he loved Sanjana and married her. She died in a tsunami shortly after. He says he can&rsquo;t replace Sanjana. GK refuses Anu&rsquo;s love politely. As time goes by, Sanjana&rsquo;s mother Sumitra dies of illness in Malaysia and her husband Viswanath tells GK that her last wish is the marriage of GK with Anu. GK also gets a feeling that Sanjana also wants the same. He returns to India and unites with Anu and the film ends on a happy note.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ueSTOqmJSJA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sabse Badhkar Hum]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/07/04/Sabse-Badhkar-Hum.html"/>
    <updated>2013-07-04T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/07/04/Sabse-Badhkar-Hum</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/MzSq1oPhJgI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Sabse Badhkar Hum"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The movie starts in the late 1980s when a group of friends celebrate their farewell party. They promise each other to keep in touch. Among them are Hanumantha Rao, who has a son named Prabha, and Vishwanath who has daughter Nandini. To reach their professional goals, Vishwanath and his daughter travel to Switzerland, while Hanumantha Rao becomes a criminal lawyer and settles in India. Thus, Prabha and Nandini get separated in their childhood. Years later, these old friends call for a reunion where a grown-up Prabha is eager to see his love Nandini. But, another girl Nisha, daughter of local don, attempts suicide when Prabha doesn&rsquo;t accept her love. Her father tries to kill Prabha and his friends but Prabha gets out of trouble by faking a story about his childhood love Nandini. During the reunion at the farm house of Buchchaiah, Prabha happens to see Nandini. He tries various tantrums to impress her, but in vain. His attempts are always thwarted by her brother. One day, he knowingly gives a lead about his sister&rsquo;s favorite game of Basketball, forcing Prabha and his team to create a Basketball court. As they play basketball, in comes Rishi, as Appala Raju&rsquo;s son, who gatecrashes into the game as he is cheered by Nandini. Both Rishi and Prabha both vie with each other to impress Nandini, leading to a cold war between them. Meanwhile, Prasanna, daughter of Buchchaiah, confesses to Prabha that she was in love with a man and she would marry him if she could pay a dowry of 50 lakhs, and she forces Prabha to talk to her father into marrying off her to her boyfriend. Prabha is able to convince Buchchaiah about his daughter&rsquo;s marriage with the help of his father and his friends. Impressed by his managing skills, Nandini too begins to like Prabha. Jealous of Nandini&rsquo;s liking for Prabha, Rishi&rsquo;s friends try to paralyse Prabha by misconnecting the power cable of an iron box. Hanumantha Rao, unaware of their conspiracy, accidentally touches the iron box and gets an, leading to a scuffle between Prabha and Rishi. The fight results in Hanumantha Rao ejecting Prabha out of the house. Later, Prabha finds out that Rishi is not Appala Raju&rsquo;s son, but the nephew of Vishwanath. Vishwanath betrayed his father by marrying his girlfriend rather than the girl chosen by his father. As a result, he is ousted by his father. Hanumantha Rao, on behalf of Viswanath negotiates with his father for a reconciliation. After many attempts, he agrees to forgive Viswanath but on the condition that his daughter&rsquo;s son should marry Nandini. Prabha decides not to reveal his love for Nandini and makes up his mind to leave. As Prabha tries to leave, Nandini reveals that she too loves him. But to save his father&rsquo;s reputation, he doesn&rsquo;t reveal his love to her and leaves the place leaving Nandini heartbroken. Nisha&rsquo;s father too realizes the truth that the story that Prabha had said was a lie, and tries to kill Prabha. Meanwhile, Nandini gets to know the truth behind Prabha&rsquo;s silence and convinces her father that she loves Prabha and he should get her married to Prabha. Prabha is rescued from Nisha&rsquo;s father in time by Nandini, who urges Nisha&rsquo;s father to spare Prabha as both of them love each other. The film ends with Prabha and Nandini getting married.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MzSq1oPhJgI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Policewala Gunda]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/06/20/Policewala-Gunda.html"/>
    <updated>2013-06-20T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/06/20/Policewala-Gunda</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Yamraj Singh who runs away from home at an early age and become a police officer. He likes his mother and dislikes his foster father. On being posted to his hometown, Yamraj Singh comes to a decision, to rid the people of law and order problems.He comes across Siddhappa Naidu, a political aspirant who is involved in all sorts of illegal activities. Yamraj Singh cuts Siddhappa to his size and Siddhappa wants to take revenge. Meanwhile, he meets Bhagyalakshmi and falls in love with her.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kMGwixzZ7BI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mera Insaaf]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Insaaf.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-29T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Insaaf</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NR0X7KGVyQM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mera Insaaf"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NR0X7KGVyQM/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Insaaf"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NR0X7KGVyQM/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Insaaf"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NR0X7KGVyQM/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Insaaf"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Vinay who studies in college where Priya enters as a new student. Srikanth is also a student in the same college. His character has negative shades. The first half of the movie revolves mostly around the love story of the hero and heroine. Dharma Teja happens to rescue the hero from the villans, but hero hates Dharma Teja. Interval arrives disclosing the fact that Dharma Teja is the father of Vinay. Second half of the movie becomes serious with Vinay&rsquo;s allegation on his father stating that he is a smuggler and has killed his wife. Vinay and Priya get married. Dharma Teja shoots Srikanth, as he tries to murder Vinay. However, the villains continue to show their grudge on hero. Meanwhile hero&rsquo;s child is kidnapped. Priya goes to Dharma Teja for help. Vinay finds that Dharma Teja has kidnapped the child. When asked for explanation, Dharma Teja narrates the flashback, where he had to leave his wife to rescue the life of his son. Vinay and Dharma Teja are now united, much to the envy of the villains. The villains now kidnap hero&rsquo;s son leading to the climax.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/NR0X7KGVyQM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
