<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: 2013-Top-25-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/2013-top-25-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:47:37-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Kaisa Karz]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Yeh-Kaisa-Karz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ueSTOqmJSJA/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Yeh Kaisa Karz" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about SRK who is a real estate contractor. He uses muscle power to encroach land and make money. His business rival Gopala Krishna GK is the &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; of GK Constructions. GK has the power to handle goons as well as the real estate business. He calls for applications from MBA graduates as his personal secretary. None of the applicants reach his expectations. He accidentally meets Anuradha Anu and thinks that she is fit for the job. As a &lsquo;Boss&rsquo; he is tough with his staff but has lots of concern over them. During a trip to Malaysia, Anu and GK get closer and Anu loses her heart to GK. When she is about to confess her love, Anu gets involved in a petty issue and faces the wrath of GK. Consequently, she resigns from her job. GK calls for interviews for his personal secretary again and zeroes in on Sruthi. It is revealed that she was planted in GK&rsquo;s office by SRK. In order to get her father Rammurthy released from a false case, Sruthi steals a tender file. However, she does not hand it over to SRK and demands her father&rsquo;s release. The crooked SRK does not listen to her. At this juncture, she tries to escape from the scene and is saved by GK at the insistence of Anu. However, Anu is injured in the attack by goons in the process, but goes straight to the Tenders office and files the tender to save GK from a huge loss and to fulfill his ambition of securing his dream project. When GK is about to thank her, she admits her love for him, only to learn of his past. In the flashback, GK reveals that he loved Sanjana and married her. She died in a tsunami shortly after. He says he can&rsquo;t replace Sanjana. GK refuses Anu&rsquo;s love politely. As time goes by, Sanjana&rsquo;s mother Sumitra dies of illness in Malaysia and her husband Viswanath tells GK that her last wish is the marriage of GK with Anu. GK also gets a feeling that Sanjana also wants the same. He returns to India and unites with Anu and the film ends on a happy note.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ueSTOqmJSJA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fighter Man: Ghayal]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/The-Fighter-Man%3A-Ghayal.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/The-Fighter-Man:-Ghayal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vk0uat6WBL0/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="The Fighter Man: Ghayal" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about an Auto mobile mechanic Ashok is thrown out of the house by his rough acts which kills his grand mother .His father is compelled to throughout hero. The heroine is a neighbour and Ashok falls in love with her, the Villain in an accident sees the heroine and he also falls in love with her. While saving the heroine from the clutches of villain, the Ashok&rsquo;s friend is killed by the villain gang. This angers the hero who is sent off to Delhi according to a plan laid by villain, villain&rsquo;s mother and hero&rsquo;s father and he rushes back to Hyderabad to save his family and the heroine. The climax fight shot in side the house is breathtaking. Finally as usual the hero is fighting with the villain the villain is about to loose the battle to safe guard the villain, villain&rsquo;s mother enters the scene to shoot the hero. At last, the bullet hits the villain, The villain&rsquo;s mother falls down and the hero takes away the heroine.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vk0uat6WBL0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mera Insaaf]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Mera-Insaaf.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Mera-Insaaf</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NR0X7KGVyQM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Mera Insaaf" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Vinay who studies in college where Priya enters as a new student. Srikanth is also a student in the same college. His character has negative shades. The first half of the movie revolves mostly around the love story of the hero and heroine. Dharma Teja happens to rescue the hero from the villans, but hero hates Dharma Teja. Interval arrives disclosing the fact that Dharma Teja is the father of Vinay. Second half of the movie becomes serious with Vinay&rsquo;s allegation on his father stating that he is a smuggler and has killed his wife. Vinay and Priya get married. Dharma Teja shoots Srikanth, as he tries to murder Vinay. However, the villains continue to show their grudge on hero. Meanwhile hero&rsquo;s child is kidnapped. Priya goes to Dharma Teja for help. Vinay finds that Dharma Teja has kidnapped the child. When asked for explanation, Dharma Teja narrates the flashback, where he had to leave his wife to rescue the life of his son. Vinay and Dharma Teja are now united, much to the envy of the villains. The villains now kidnap hero&rsquo;s son leading to the climax.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/NR0X7KGVyQM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mard Ki Zaban]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Mard-Ki-Zaban.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/Mard-Ki-Zaban</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Mard Ki Zaban" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Ram the only son of a wealthy and influential farmer Anjaneya Prasad. Anjaneya Prasad is a happy and contented man. He lives happily with his son Ram, three daughters, sons-in-law, and grandchildren in the same house. However, he has one wish unfulfilled that is to see his son marry and settle down in life. But Ram keeps delaying marriage, as he is apprehensive whether his wife will agree to live in a joint family. However, Ram finally relents after he comes across Raja Rajeswari in unexpected circumstances and falls in love with her. Raja Rajeshwari is the daughter of politician Chamundeshwari and Shankar Rao. The families agree to the marriage but even before the newly weds can go home a small issue between the two families get blown out of proportion. As a result, the two families break up the marriage and part ways. Later, Ram and Rajeswari plans to go abroad for some time to overcome their grief. In a coincidence, the two of them head to the same place Mauritius. Into this Ram meets an old friend Shraddha Das who is madly in love with Ram. However, the married couple reconciles their differences and marries in Mauritius. They come back to India only to face the wrath of their respective families. How they come out of the situation is the remaining part of the story.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/SIsNMl-LlPw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Khiladi]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/International-Khiladi.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/2013-Top-25-Movies/2014/03/22/International-Khiladi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/R5C4gte-9VM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="International Khiladi" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>An orphan boy, named Sunil, wanders through all of Delhi looking for a job. When selling balloons, he sees a girl and gives her a free balloon. A few days later, during a storm, the girl finds the boy getting soaked and gives him an umbrella. The umbrella blows into a place nearby, where the girls parents are headed. The boy stops their car and indicates them about the dangerous path ahead destroyed by the storm. As the boy rescues the girl&rsquo;s parents, the boy gets adopted by the parents. They name the boy &ldquo;Atithi&rdquo; which means &ldquo;guest&rdquo;. One day, while driving Atithi to a hostel, they are stopped by a teenager, a Psychopath, who mugs them, and shoots the parents. In his rage, Athithi lunges after the teen managing to take the teen&rsquo;s gun. Nearby witnesses see Athithi with a gun and the girl&rsquo;s parents and think that Atithi killed them. The police come and arrest Atithi. The girl also thinks that it was Atithi who killed her parents and starts to hate him and thinks that she will never see him again. Fourteen years later, Atithi gets out of jail, and is now in search of the Psychopath {teen who has killed the girl&rsquo;s parents} and the girl who is alive. In Delhi, local goons are feared by Atithi, as he becomes a hurdle for their illegal operation. At one instance, he runs across a girl named Amrita chased by stalkers from her college. Amrita and Atithi meet many times. Amrita starts to like Atithi, but has to go back to Hyderabad before she can confess her love. When she goes to try tell him that she is leaving Atithi gets annoyed. He continuously tells her to leave him alone, when she keeps asking to get some coffee and slaps her. She runs away crying. Later Atithi goes to Amrita to say sorry but only finds her friend. She tells him that Amrita just wanted to tell him that she&rsquo;s leaving. They then go to the cemetery seeing if she is there. Amrita&rsquo;s friend then explains that a boy adopted by Amrita&rsquo;s parents killed them when she was young and Amrita goes to the cemetery to see their graves all the time. Atithi realizes that she was the same girl that he met in his childhood and leaves for Hyderabad to find her. When Atithi also arrives to Hyderabad, and decides to stay with Amrita&rsquo;s family, he learns that a Mafia leader and kidnapper named Kaiser is feared there. Later, after few events, Atithi realizes that Kaiser was the psychopath teen who killed the girl&rsquo;s parents. Now Kaiser is trying to kill Amrita. Atithi stops two attempts by Kaiser to murder Amrita. Meanwhile, Officer Ajay is trying to track down Kaiser. Ajay dies in an explosion in his house, which was planned by Kaiser. Atithi figures out later on that Ajay is none other than Kaiser. Ajay&rsquo;s real name is Kaiser. Before Kaiser&rsquo;s house blew up, Kaiser managed to escape. When the MLA realizes that Ajay&rsquo;s real name is Kaiser, the MLA, after succumbing to shock, dies with a heart attack. Athithi manages to kill one of Kaiser&rsquo;s men. Kaiser then kidnaps Amrita and her cousin. Kaiser kills Amrita&rsquo;s cousin. Then Kaiser leads Amrita to a dungeon and calls Atithi and tells him that he will kill Amrita if Atithi doesn&rsquo;t rescue her in 12 hours. Then Atithi kidnaps Kaiser&rsquo;s brother, and trades for Amrita. Amrita is severely cut and stuck in a certain air tank (Kaiser planned), but is rescued. Kaiser is killed. Atithi and Amrita unite, realising he wasn&rsquo;t the one who killed her parents.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/R5C4gte-9VM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
