<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Classic-Comedy-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/classic-comedy-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:20:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bombay to Goa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Bombay-To-Goa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Bombay-To-Goa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/U6dWCw8zLfU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Bombay To Goa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Just when the tourist bus to Goa is leaving Bombay Central, Mala - Aroona Irani comes running and boards it. Her entry is greeted with many admiring glances, as it was not often that such a beautiful girl took this bus and that too, alone. Aruna may have been alone on the bus, but those who are vitally interested in her movements have momentarily been left behind. The evil Shatrughan - Shatrughan Sinha and his cronies follow in their car. They are after Mala because she has witnessed them committing a murder. Meanwhile, young Ravi - Amitabh Bachchan has already sensed the danger that is lurking on the road from Bombay to Goa and catches the bus midway.


<p>From hereon, begins the laughride. Goa is 616 kms. from Bombay and when you travel in a bus with Mahmood as the conductor, the journey can only be filled with thrills, chills, belly-laughs, and, for good measure, a delightful romance between Mala and Ravi. So, don&rsquo;t miss this bus. It is ready to take you on the most enjoyable journey of your life.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patanga]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Patanga.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Patanga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Rorj5pn7lmo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Patanga" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch the superhit black & white Bollywood blockbuster classic Hindi romantic comedy full length movie Patanga (1949), starring Nigar Sultana, Yakub, Gope, Cuckoo, Ajit, Shyama, Rajendra Nath, Raj Mehra, Poornima, Ramesh Sinha, Mohana, Shashi Kapoor, Vimi, Raj Kishore, Shyam. Directed by H S Rawail. Music composed by C Ramchandra.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Padosan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Padosan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Padosan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/NQ6yBdXmU_4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Padosan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Bollywood classic - Padosan 1968, is the hilarious story of how destiny brings two opposites together.  Bhola - Sunil Dutt is a straightforward and unlettered village bumpkin while Bindu - Saira Bano is a modern and educated rich girl who is independent of spirit and highly accomplished in the arts. While Bhola falls in love with Bindu, she ridicules him and only feels contempt for him. Her music teacher - Mehmood encourages her to heap more insults at Bhola.


<p>A heartbroken Bhola turns to Guru &ndash; Kishore Kumar who runs an amateur theatre company with his motley bunch of artistes and singers. Guru devises ingenious tricks whereby Bhola is able to impress Bindu. A laugh-riot that will have you roll of your sets with mirth, &lsquo;Padosan&rsquo; also boasts of super-hit songs, including the unforgettable &lsquo;Mere Samne Wali Khidki Mein&rsquo;, &lsquo;Ek Chatur Naar&rsquo; and &lsquo;Meri Pyari Bindu&rsquo;.
Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned- <a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts">https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Do-Phool---Superhit-Hindi-Comedy-Film---Ashhok-Kumar-%2C-Vinod-Mehra%2C-Mehmood.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Do-Phool---Superhit-Hindi-Comedy-Film---Ashhok-Kumar-,-Vinod-Mehra,-Mehmood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/N4wv_GrlCGY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Do Phool - Superhit Hindi Comedy Film - Ashhok Kumar , Vinod Mehra, Mehmood" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Mummy called them two `phool', whilst Daddy said they were two fools! Dewan Bahadu Atal Rai believed that both his sons, Pavitra Kumar (alias Puttan) and Charitra Kumar (also known as Chuttan) were nothing better than loafers and ne'er-do-wells. Their mother Malati stubbornly pinned her faith in Chuttan and Puttan and asserted that they were still mere children. Let us find brides for them, and then watch the results! Chuttan was the younger brother. There was a proposal of marriage for him with Shaila, daughter of the lawyer Vardhraj, who was also a practicing Vaid. Puttan accompanied his younger brother, when the latter visited the house of his proposed bride. Both brothers approved of the match. Puttan had already his own plans, and his heart's desire was Poonam' daughter of Inspector Madhusudhan. Unfortunately, the path of love is never smooth, and in desperation both brothers decided to bury themselves alive in a `Prem Samadhi' unless Shaila and Poonam accepted their hands. This public exhibition of their love enraged their father, who took the extreme step and turned them out of his house. Still hoping to win the hearts of their beloved, Chuttan and Puttan hatch a plot. Saying that he had murdered his brother Puttan, Chuttan rushed to Shaila to seek refuge. The poor girl believed his story, and tried to shield him from prying eyes. Meanwhile, Puttan took to a disguise, which led him to a smuggler's den. The criminals discovered him in their midst, and after knocking him unconscious, he was thrown into a convenient lake. Now Puttan really disappeared, and to his brother Chuttan's ill luck a body floated in the lake on which was found Puttan's identification in the shape of his jacket and watch. Chuttan was wanted for murder! The joke had boomeranged. Puttan's father believed that his son was still alive, a faith shared by Shaila. Puttan's photograph was advertised widely, with a reward offered to anyone reporting his whereabouts. Now enter into the drama Mani, who bore a striking resemblance to Puttan, his mother, and his bethrothed Rukmini. Two desperados notice the resemblance, and kidnapping the protesting Mani, carry him off to Bombay to claim the rich reward from Diwan Bahadur Atal Rai. Incidents follow, fast and furious, and the story of "Do Phool" races towards an unexpected climax, providing exhilarating entertainment as laughs and thrills loom as large as life. Such incidents are better enjoyed upon the screen, and it is left to the viewer to decide whether Chuttan and Puttan are `Do Phool' or really `Two Fools'.

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angoor]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Angoor.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Comedy-Movies/2014/03/21/Angoor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/L2dI4IVhfuc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Angoor" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Angoor is based on Shakespeare's 'A comedy of errors', a story of identical twins (2 pairs) and mistaken identities. Ashok R Tilak (Sanjeev Kumar) lives in Dinkapur with his widowed mother and a servant named Bahadur (Deven Verma). He travels to another town on a business trip to buy several acres of land of grape business. He takes one lakh Rupees with him. He is keen of reading suspense & thrilling


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Regular Facebook Updates <a href="http://www.facebook.com/RajshriDotCom.">http://www.facebook.com/RajshriDotCom.</a></p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts">https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
