<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/all-time-hit-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:12:28-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tezaab]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Tezaab.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Tezaab</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YrltCqkWkLo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tezaab" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Mahesh Deshmukh (Anil Kapoor) has joined the nation's armed forces as that he can honestly and patriotically serve the country. During his college days he has a run-in with fellow-collegian Mohini (Madhuri Dixit). A bet between his friends and himself ends up with him falling in love with Mohini, who subsequently realizes that he indeed has fallen in love with her, and she too reciprocates. Mohini's dad (Anupam Kher) is an alcoholic and wishes that Mohini takes up dancing and prostitution so that he can get his daily dose of alchol. Mohini attempts to take refuge with Mahesh, however, cirumstances tangle Mahesh to such an extent that he is arrested, charged, and sentenced to stay away from Bombay city limits. When Mahesh returns, it is no longer the honest, and patriotic Mahesh, but a gangster named Munna, who has many old scores to settle.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daag: The Fire]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Daag%3A-The-Fire.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Daag:-The-Fire</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XtUZROpRoVU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Daag: The Fire" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Ravi Verma is an unprincipled lawyer, who will bend the law to seek an acquittal for his clients. Ravi helps his father-in-law, Tejeshwar and his friends to imprison Satyaprakash, the local Municipal Commissioner on false grounds. Tejeshwar's friends arrange for Satyaprakash's death in prison, and label it as suicide. Satyaprakash's son Karan finds out about his dad's predicament and swears to avenge his humiliation and death. Karan goes on a rampage grievously injuring Ravi and killing his wife Kajal. After the attack, Ravi is left in a comatose condition and has no recollection of his past life while Tejeshwar and his friends plot to bring back Ravi's memories by hiring a look-alike of Kajal. Will this succeed in helping Ravi regain his memory? How far will Karan go to seek his revenge?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty%2C-Sanjay-Dutt%2C-Preeti-Jhangiani.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty,-Sanjay-Dutt,-Preeti-Jhangiani</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Jimmy (Sunil Shetty) is an underworld don, working with his brother, the more influential and powerful, Raghav (Ashutosh Rana). Jimmy hangs around with his childhood friend, Sameer (Gautam Rode) who also joins Jimmy's gang. Jimmy's sister, Preeti (Preeti Jhangiani) and Sameer fall in love and Jimmy gets into the bad books of Don Dayal (Tinnu Anand) who wants him dead. Dayal tells Raghav to finish off Jimmy. Things take a twist when Preeti comes to know that Sameer is an undercover cop working with Don Iqbal (Sanjay Dutt) to destroy the crime empire of Raghav and Dayal. Can Jimmy escape the erupting gang war with his own brother wanting to kill him? Can Sameer vanquish the underworld and unite with Preeti?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ram Lakhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Ram-Lakhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Ram-Lakhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dcoHobLosts/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ram Lakhan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Ram Lakhan - Full Length Classic Bollywood Movie - With English Subtitles - 1989. Subhash Ghai's Bollywood revenge drama anchored by a powerful, award-winning performance by Rakhee Gulzar with multi-star cast, including Anil Kapoor, Jackie Shroff, Madhuri Dixit, Dimple Kapadia ,Gulshan Grover, Amrish Puri, Paresh Rawal, Anupam Kher, Annu Kapoor,Raza Murad, Music?Director - Laxmikant Pyarelal, Singers - Lata Mangeshkar,Nitin Mukesh,Kavita Krishnamurthy,Amit Kumar,Anuradha Paudwal.


<p>Synopsis: Sharda &ndash; Rakhee vows vengeance when her husband is murdered by his two evil cousins, Bhishamber &ndash; Amrish Puri and Bhanu &ndash; Paresh Rawal, and she and her two young sons are thrown out on the street. Those sons grow into the upstanding police officer Ram &ndash; Jackie Shroff and the easily tempted dreamer Lakhan &ndash; Anil Kapoor. If the family is to be avenged, Ram will have to lead his brother away from the path of corruption he&rsquo;s strayed onto, and protect him from the influence of Bhanu and Bhishamber.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts">https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prem Deewane]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Prem-Deewane.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:40-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Prem-Deewane</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Prem Deewane" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Radha (Pooja Bhatt) and Manohar (Vivek Mushran) are in love and want to marry each other. But Radha's father is staunchly against this union as Manohar belongs to a poor family. He even instructs Radha not to meet him and confines her in the house. But Radha manages to escape and lands in Manohar's house. Radha's uncle Natarwalal (Prem Chopra) is the biggest support of these lovebirds who help them to elope. He even advises them to kidnap a wealthy man and demand ransom in exchange for his release. And then take the money to Radha's father. While doing so, Radha and Manohar discover Natwarlal's cruel intentions. Will Radha and Manohar do as suggested by Natwarlal? Who will they kidnap if they do?

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
