<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/all-time-hit-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T00:22:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tezaab]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Tezaab.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Tezaab</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YrltCqkWkLo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tezaab" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Mahesh Deshmukh (Anil Kapoor) has joined the nation&rsquo;s armed forces as that he can honestly and patriotically serve the country. During his college days he has a run-in with fellow-collegian Mohini (Madhuri Dixit). A bet between his friends and himself ends up with him falling in love with Mohini, who subsequently realizes that he indeed has fallen in love with her, and she too reciprocates. Mohini&rsquo;s dad (Anupam Kher) is an alcoholic and wishes that Mohini takes up dancing and prostitution so that he can get his daily dose of alchol. Mohini attempts to take refuge with Mahesh, however, cirumstances tangle Mahesh to such an extent that he is arrested, charged, and sentenced to stay away from Bombay city limits. When Mahesh returns, it is no longer the honest, and patriotic Mahesh, but a gangster named Munna, who has many old scores to settle.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daag: The Fire]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Daag%3A-The-Fire.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Daag:-The-Fire</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XtUZROpRoVU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Daag: The Fire" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Ravi Verma is an unprincipled lawyer, who will bend the law to seek an acquittal for his clients. Ravi helps his father-in-law, Tejeshwar and his friends to imprison Satyaprakash, the local Municipal Commissioner on false grounds. Tejeshwar&rsquo;s friends arrange for Satyaprakash&rsquo;s death in prison, and label it as suicide. Satyaprakash&rsquo;s son Karan finds out about his dad&rsquo;s predicament and swears to avenge his humiliation and death. Karan goes on a rampage grievously injuring Ravi and killing his wife Kajal. After the attack, Ravi is left in a comatose condition and has no recollection of his past life while Tejeshwar and his friends plot to bring back Ravi&rsquo;s memories by hiring a look-alike of Kajal. Will this succeed in helping Ravi regain his memory? How far will Karan go to seek his revenge?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty%2C-Sanjay-Dutt%2C-Preeti-Jhangiani.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty,-Sanjay-Dutt,-Preeti-Jhangiani</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Jimmy (Sunil Shetty) is an underworld don, working with his brother, the more influential and powerful, Raghav (Ashutosh Rana). Jimmy hangs around with his childhood friend, Sameer (Gautam Rode) who also joins Jimmy&rsquo;s gang. Jimmy&rsquo;s sister, Preeti (Preeti Jhangiani) and Sameer fall in love and Jimmy gets into the bad books of Don Dayal (Tinnu Anand) who wants him dead. Dayal tells Raghav to finish off Jimmy. Things take a twist when Preeti comes to know that Sameer is an undercover cop working with Don Iqbal (Sanjay Dutt) to destroy the crime empire of Raghav and Dayal. Can Jimmy escape the erupting gang war with his own brother wanting to kill him? Can Sameer vanquish the underworld and unite with Preeti?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aamne Saamne]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Aamne-Saamne.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:56-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Aamne-Saamne</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QK2A0gX4ZoQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Aamne Saamne" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Deepak (Shashi Kapoor) is on trial for the murder of his wealthy wife Vimla, but is acquitted and set free. Deepak gets possession of all his wife&rsquo;s wealth and sets out to Bombay and starts a new life under the alias Gopal. Sapna (Sharmila Tagore) is his wealthy neighbor who finds Gopal annoying and  believes that Gopal is stalking her. Soon, Sapna falls for Gopal&rsquo;s charms, though her brother Pran wants Sapna to marry Prem (Prem Chopra). Sapna tells Prem and Pran that she is choosing Gopal, which enrages them and they both threaten to kill her. Sapna and Gopal get married and while honeymooning, an attempt is made on Sapna&rsquo;s life. Soon, Sapna learns that Gopal&rsquo;s real name is Deepak, who was previously accused of murdering his first wife. Gopal&rsquo;s ever changing behavior throws everyone into suspicion and Sapna fears she will be his next victim. Is Gopal innocent or Guilty? Who is spinning the web of lie and deceit and who will survive the murderer&rsquo;s cruel intentions?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ram Lakhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Lakhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:21:55-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Lakhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dcoHobLosts/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ram Lakhan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Ram Lakhan &ndash; Full Length Classic Bollywood Movie &ndash; With English Subtitles &ndash; 1989. Subhash Ghai&rsquo;s Bollywood revenge drama anchored by a powerful, award-winning performance by Rakhee Gulzar with multi-star cast, including Anil Kapoor, Jackie Shroff, Madhuri Dixit, Dimple Kapadia ,Gulshan Grover, Amrish Puri, Paresh Rawal, Anupam Kher, Annu Kapoor,Raza Murad, Music?Director &ndash; Laxmikant Pyarelal, Singers &ndash; Lata Mangeshkar,Nitin Mukesh,Kavita Krishnamurthy,Amit Kumar,Anuradha Paudwal.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
