<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/all-time-hit-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T22:53:40-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Khalnayak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/19/Khalnayak.html"/>
    <updated>2011-11-19T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/19/Khalnayak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/3vMMxqX84K4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Khalnayak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/3vMMxqX84K4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Khalnayak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/3vMMxqX84K4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Khalnayak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/3vMMxqX84K4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Khalnayak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Ballu (Sanjay Dutt) is a notorious criminal and Ram (Jackie Shroff) is a diligent police officer. The latter captures Ballu and tries to lure him to spill the beans on his mentor Roshida. But Ballu escapes from jail while Ram was visiting his girlfriend Ganga (Madhuri Dixit) who too is a police officer. Ballu&rsquo;s jail break puts a dent in Ram&rsquo;s reputation as he is accused of neglecting his duty. Ganga decides to salvage the situation for Ram and goes undercover as a village belle. She befriends Ballu and gradually realises that Ballu has a benign side in spite of being notoriously bad. She tries to hone the good side of Ballu. This makes Ballu fall for Ganga only to realise that she is in love with someone else and is also a police officer. Ganga however continues to care for Ballu. Ram meets Ballu&rsquo;s mother for help but finds out instead that Ballu is his childhood friend. Ballu and his mother narrate their plight and Ram and Ganga decide to get Ballu back on track. Will Ram and Ganga succeed? Or will Ballu&rsquo;s fate get sealed with a policeman&rsquo;s bullet?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/3vMMxqX84K4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/14/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty%2C-Sanjay-Dutt%2C-Preeti-Jhangiani.html"/>
    <updated>2011-11-14T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/14/Annarth---Bollywood-Action-Movie---Suniel-Shetty,-Sanjay-Dutt,-Preeti-Jhangiani</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/utfTvFXXRwc/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Annarth - Bollywood Action Movie - Suniel Shetty, Sanjay Dutt, Preeti Jhangiani"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Jimmy (Sunil Shetty) is an underworld don, working with his brother, the more influential and powerful, Raghav (Ashutosh Rana). Jimmy hangs around with his childhood friend, Sameer (Gautam Rode) who also joins Jimmy&rsquo;s gang. Jimmy&rsquo;s sister, Preeti (Preeti Jhangiani) and Sameer fall in love and Jimmy gets into the bad books of Don Dayal (Tinnu Anand) who wants him dead. Dayal tells Raghav to finish off Jimmy. Things take a twist when Preeti comes to know that Sameer is an undercover cop working with Don Iqbal (Sanjay Dutt) to destroy the crime empire of Raghav and Dayal. Can Jimmy escape the erupting gang war with his own brother wanting to kill him? Can Sameer vanquish the underworld and unite with Preeti?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/utfTvFXXRwc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awaargi]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/13/Awaargi.html"/>
    <updated>2011-11-13T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/13/Awaargi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mnTXZb0-GXQ/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Awaargi"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mnTXZb0-GXQ/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Awaargi"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mnTXZb0-GXQ/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Awaargi"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/mnTXZb0-GXQ/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Awaargi"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Azad (Anil Kapoor), is a mob enforcer working for Don Lalla Jamal Khan (Anupam Kher). He rescues Meena (Meenakshi Sheshadri) from a brothel, thereby inviting the wrath of Bhau (Paresh Rawal),  a rival Don. He vows to help Meena achieve her dream of becoming a singer and enlists music Director, Dhiren (Govinda) to help her. Things become complicated when both men fall for Meena. Meena falls in love with Dhiren and this causes Azad to loose his mind in jealousy. Meanwhile, Bhau&rsquo;s men violently pursue Meena and Azad and want them dead at any cost. Will Azad be able to free Meena from the danger? Can Dhiren and Meena be united?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mnTXZb0-GXQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aamne Saamne]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/13/Aamne-Saamne.html"/>
    <updated>2011-11-13T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/11/13/Aamne-Saamne</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QK2A0gX4ZoQ/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Aamne Saamne"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QK2A0gX4ZoQ/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Aamne Saamne"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QK2A0gX4ZoQ/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Aamne Saamne"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/QK2A0gX4ZoQ/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Aamne Saamne"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Deepak (Shashi Kapoor) is on trial for the murder of his wealthy wife Vimla, but is acquitted and set free. Deepak gets possession of all his wife&rsquo;s wealth and sets out to Bombay and starts a new life under the alias Gopal. Sapna (Sharmila Tagore) is his wealthy neighbor who finds Gopal annoying and  believes that Gopal is stalking her. Soon, Sapna falls for Gopal&rsquo;s charms, though her brother Pran wants Sapna to marry Prem (Prem Chopra). Sapna tells Prem and Pran that she is choosing Gopal, which enrages them and they both threaten to kill her. Sapna and Gopal get married and while honeymooning, an attempt is made on Sapna&rsquo;s life. Soon, Sapna learns that Gopal&rsquo;s real name is Deepak, who was previously accused of murdering his first wife. Gopal&rsquo;s ever changing behavior throws everyone into suspicion and Sapna fears she will be his next victim. Is Gopal innocent or Guilty? Who is spinning the web of lie and deceit and who will survive the murderer&rsquo;s cruel intentions?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QK2A0gX4ZoQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prem Deewane]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/10/01/Prem-Deewane.html"/>
    <updated>2011-10-01T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2011/10/01/Prem-Deewane</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Prem Deewane"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prem Deewane"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prem Deewane"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Prem Deewane"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Radha (Pooja Bhatt) and Manohar (Vivek Mushran) are in love and want to marry each other. But Radha&rsquo;s father is staunchly against this union as Manohar belongs to a poor family. He even instructs Radha not to meet him and confines her in the house. But Radha manages to escape and lands in Manohar&rsquo;s house. Radha&rsquo;s uncle Natarwalal (Prem Chopra) is the biggest support of these lovebirds who help them to elope. He even advises them to kidnap a wealthy man and demand ransom in exchange for his release. And then take the money to Radha&rsquo;s father. While doing so, Radha and Manohar discover Natwarlal&rsquo;s cruel intentions. Will Radha and Manohar do as suggested by Natwarlal? Who will they kidnap if they do?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/9LwrGBlTlsU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
