<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/all-time-hit-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T01:22:57-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tezaab]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Tezaab.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Tezaab</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YrltCqkWkLo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tezaab" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Mahesh Deshmukh (Anil Kapoor) has joined the nation&rsquo;s armed forces as that he can honestly and patriotically serve the country. During his college days he has a run-in with fellow-collegian Mohini (Madhuri Dixit). A bet between his friends and himself ends up with him falling in love with Mohini, who subsequently realizes that he indeed has fallen in love with her, and she too reciprocates. Mohini&rsquo;s dad (Anupam Kher) is an alcoholic and wishes that Mohini takes up dancing and prostitution so that he can get his daily dose of alchol. Mohini attempts to take refuge with Mahesh, however, cirumstances tangle Mahesh to such an extent that he is arrested, charged, and sentenced to stay away from Bombay city limits. When Mahesh returns, it is no longer the honest, and patriotic Mahesh, but a gangster named Munna, who has many old scores to settle.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YrltCqkWkLo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ram Lakhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Lakhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Ram-Lakhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dcoHobLosts/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ram Lakhan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Ram Lakhan &ndash; Full Length Classic Bollywood Movie &ndash; With English Subtitles &ndash; 1989. Subhash Ghai&rsquo;s Bollywood revenge drama anchored by a powerful, award-winning performance by Rakhee Gulzar with multi-star cast, including Anil Kapoor, Jackie Shroff, Madhuri Dixit, Dimple Kapadia ,Gulshan Grover, Amrish Puri, Paresh Rawal, Anupam Kher, Annu Kapoor,Raza Murad, Music?Director &ndash; Laxmikant Pyarelal, Singers &ndash; Lata Mangeshkar,Nitin Mukesh,Kavita Krishnamurthy,Amit Kumar,Anuradha Paudwal.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dcoHobLosts" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prem Deewane]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Prem-Deewane.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Prem-Deewane</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/9LwrGBlTlsU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Prem Deewane" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Radha (Pooja Bhatt) and Manohar (Vivek Mushran) are in love and want to marry each other. But Radha&rsquo;s father is staunchly against this union as Manohar belongs to a poor family. He even instructs Radha not to meet him and confines her in the house. But Radha manages to escape and lands in Manohar&rsquo;s house. Radha&rsquo;s uncle Natarwalal (Prem Chopra) is the biggest support of these lovebirds who help them to elope. He even advises them to kidnap a wealthy man and demand ransom in exchange for his release. And then take the money to Radha&rsquo;s father. While doing so, Radha and Manohar discover Natwarlal&rsquo;s cruel intentions. Will Radha and Manohar do as suggested by Natwarlal? Who will they kidnap if they do?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/9LwrGBlTlsU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karz]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Karz.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Karz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/AEGGnOhRZOQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Karz" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Ravi Verma (Raj Kiran) and Kamini (Simi Garewal) are in love with each other and plan to get married. Sir Juda (Prem Nath), wants to take over the vast estate of Ranimaa, and finds out that he can only do so with the help of Ravi&rsquo;s girlfriend Kamini. Sir Juda tells Kamini about the plan, wherein she will marry Ravi and thereafter kill him accidentally, and Kamini agrees to do so. After Ravi&rsquo;s death Ranimaa is devastated, and Sir Juda takes over the vast estate. Ravi is reborn as Monty (Rishi Kapoor) &ndash; a popular singer now. He plans to go for a holiday to Ooty, where he recollects about his previous life&rsquo;s memories which disturb him. Now he enquires about these memories and reaches Ranimaa&rsquo;s estate. It is then that he realizes the reason and motive of his re-birth. Upon realisation, he decides to avenge his death and bring back his family&rsquo;s lost glory by putting Kamini and others behind bars. Will Monty suceed in his endeavor or will Kamini and Sir Juda crush him to death once again?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/AEGGnOhRZOQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karma]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Karma.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/All-Time-Hit-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Karma</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/c9Sb1t_jWec/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Karma" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Jailer Vishwa Pratap Singh (Dilip Kumar) changed his fate forever when he slapped captured terrorist Dr. Michael Deng (Anupam Kher) as, soon after his sons and daughter in law are murdered by Deng&rsquo;s men. He is left with his wife Rukmani (Nutan) who loses her speech after the mishap and a crippled son. Singh now called Dada Thakur resolves to bring Deng to book and therefore, recruits three defaulters of law sentenced to death Baiju Thakur (Jackie Shroff), Jonny/Gyaneshwar (Anil Kapoor) and a former terrorist Khairudding Khisti (Naseeruddin Shah). While Dad Thakur is doing everything to teach them combat tricks, the three accomplices are busy enjoying their freedom and a life away from confirmed deaths. Will Dada Thakur be successful in getting even with Deng?  Will his three recruits rise up to the occasion?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/c9Sb1t_jWec" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
