<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/republic-day-special-south-superhit-hindi-dubbed-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T23:20:09-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Policewala Gunda]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/06/20/Policewala-Gunda.html"/>
    <updated>2013-06-20T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/06/20/Policewala-Gunda</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/kMGwixzZ7BI/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Policewala Gunda"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Yamraj Singh who runs away from home at an early age and become a police officer. He likes his mother and dislikes his foster father. On being posted to his hometown, Yamraj Singh comes to a decision, to rid the people of law and order problems.He comes across Siddhappa Naidu, a political aspirant who is involved in all sorts of illegal activities. Yamraj Singh cuts Siddhappa to his size and Siddhappa wants to take revenge. Meanwhile, he meets Bhagyalakshmi and falls in love with her.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kMGwixzZ7BI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Angrakshak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/06/07/Main-Hoon-Angrakshak.html"/>
    <updated>2013-06-07T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/06/07/Main-Hoon-Angrakshak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/JJREGJzTBoM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Angrakshak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/JJREGJzTBoM/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Angrakshak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/JJREGJzTBoM/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Angrakshak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/JJREGJzTBoM/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Angrakshak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Indira who works as a security chief to Ananda Naidu, a politician. After a death, Indira brings up his children but they show no gratitude towards her when they grow up. They even join her rivals and turn against her. The Story revolves round family-based feuds and Vijayashanti as a duty-bound policewoman, Indira, gets involved. She has to deal with Ananda Naidu&rsquo;s step-brother Kesava Naidu, who holds a grudge and eventually kills his brother. Their children carry it forward.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/JJREGJzTBoM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mera Kanoon]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Kanoon.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-29T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Kanoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jtHWFWgKCBM/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mera Kanoon"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jtHWFWgKCBM/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Kanoon"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jtHWFWgKCBM/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Kanoon"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jtHWFWgKCBM/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Kanoon"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Nagaraju who is a law student and the son of a bantroth the white dressed man who stands besides judge. Bantroth&rsquo;s ambition in life is to see his son Naaga as a truthful and noble lawyer serving the society. In that process, he spends lot of money on Naaga though he could not financially afford such a costly education. Chandra Sekhara Naidu is the CM of the state. The Home Minister is looking for an opportunity to destabilize CM. The HM has an illegitimate affair with a wonton woman under the guise of social worker called Mandaram. Mandaram has insatiable thirst for the power. She pressurizes HM to make her an MLA when an assembly position falls vacant. When CM refuses to give ticket to Mandaram, the HM join hands with an opposition leader Potti Kasaiah and launches Mandaram as an independent candidate. In one of such political rally campaigns, the goons happen to enter the house of Naaga due to some petty quarrel. In the process, they bruise Naaga&rsquo;s father and sister. In a fist of anger, Naaga beats those guys black and blue. Those guys file a case on Naaga for injuring them.Naaga impresses one and all in the court by saying how the political campaigns and street rallies are affecting the privacy and comfort of common citizens. He also suggests that the politicians should use electronic media for campaign instead of wasting money by trying to influence voters with unfair means. His argument becomes the talk of the town and the headlines in various newspapers. The CM also gets impressed with Naaga. All the students unions in AP join hands with Naaga to establish youth student organizations under one roof in the leadership of Naaga. Naaga campaigns for the ruling party candidate and contributes his part in the victory. An impressed CM appoints Naaga as the youth leader for his ruling party. The opposition party uses the current draught situation in the state as the weapon to destabilize government. As a reply to this, CM starts fast-unto-death for Central Government&rsquo;s intervention in this water issue. Due to some miscommunication, Naaga starts creating law and order problem to make sure that CM stops his fast-unto-death and rule the state again. Father of Naaga dies in the process. The rest of the story is all about how Naaga overcame all the hurdles and emerge unscathed as a winner.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/jtHWFWgKCBM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dangerous Khiladi]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/03/08/Dangerous-Khiladi.html"/>
    <updated>2013-03-08T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Republic-Day-Special-South-Superhit-Hindi-Dubbed-Movies/2013/03/08/Dangerous-Khiladi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/n0kZBeYDHDM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Dangerous Khiladi"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/n0kZBeYDHDM/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dangerous Khiladi"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/n0kZBeYDHDM/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dangerous Khiladi"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/n0kZBeYDHDM/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dangerous Khiladi"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The movie begins with Bittu planning with the local MLA Varadarajulu to rob 1500 crores from the Vizag Co-operative Bank. Ravindra Narayan is a brainy individual who believes in earning quick money rather than toiling like his father Narayana for every month&rsquo;s salary. He gets into a dispute with his father about his attitude and challenges him that he would convert 10,000 into 1 lakh in quick time. He happens to meet Bittu on his way, who drops him at his destination. Ravi inadvertently reveals his plan of making quick money by betting on an IPL match and also the location of betting to Bittu and his companions on the way. However his plans turn upside down when police raid the location and is caught red-handed. During interrogation, Ravi guesstimates that Bittu could have diverted the Police, and that he is about to commit a robbery at the Vizag Cooperative Bank. He convinces Raja Manikyam that Bittu is planning to rob the bank and both go to catch him. Bittu successfully robs the bank and his brother Laala takes the money to the city&rsquo;s dumping yard, as per Bittu&rsquo;s instructions, as the Police follow them. However Police catch Lala, who resists them only to be killed by Ravi. Police try to trace the money but in vain. Meanwhile Bittu gets arrested, but is rescued in transit by his sidekick Devayani. They go to the dumping yard to collect the money but Bittu is shocked as the dumping yard is burnt to ashes. Having his brother dead and the money burnt, Bittu decides to kill Ravi. Raja Manikyam sends Ravi to Hyderabad from Vizag under Witness Protection Program and makes him to stay at his friend ACP Sitaram&rsquo;s house. ACP Sitaram is a cowardly cop who is afraid of using his gun. One day, Ravi happens to see Madhu, a middle class girl who works with travel agent &lsquo;Travel&rsquo; Murthy, an associate of Bittu. He prepares fake passports for Bittu&rsquo;s gang to help them escape from India. Ravi befriends Madhu and both fall in love with each other. Ravi steals Madhu&rsquo;s identity card which leads Sitaram and him to know all the details regarding the escape plan of Bittu, in which Madhu would be tricked to pose as Bittu&rsquo;s wife, suffering from Vertigo to help him escape easily. Ravi &amp; Sitaram go after Bittu, with Sitaram of the impression that Bittu would go to airport. However, Bittu plays a trick on them and escapes through other route. Ravi, however, outwits Bittu and forces Sitaram to go in the route taken by Bittu. Ravi &amp; Bittu confront each other and Bittu threatens to kill Madhu. However, Devayani forces Bittu to abandon Madhu as Bittu is surrounded and they escape. Bittu vows to exact revenge on Ravi by targeting his family. He decides to kidnap Ravi&rsquo;s family, but before he could, Ravi shifts his family to Hyderabad. Frustrated, Bittu seeks the help of Varadarajulu to help him escape to abroad. But Varadarajulu tells him that he is helpless in this matter. Enraged, Bittu kills him. But before dying Varadarajulu tells the truth that he and Raja Manikyam had the custody of the loot. Bittu makes a deal with Raja Manikyam and traps Ravi in a car blast with Manikyam faking his death. Ravi gets arrested but is released on bail by Sitaram. Ravi realizes the foul play and also that Manikyam too is involved in the robbery. Meanwhile, Ravi&rsquo;s family is kidnapped by &lsquo;Travel&rsquo; Murthy. Ravi manages to save his family but not before &lsquo;Travel&rsquo; Murthy shot his father. Narayan Murthy is shifted to ICU where he prods Ravi to restore the 1500 Cr to the Bank. Meanwhile, Ravi&rsquo;s sister is kidnapped by Devayani &amp; Bittu shifts her to Vizag. Ravi gets to know the location of his sister through &lsquo;Travel&rsquo; Murthy and he leaves for Vizag with Sitaram. Ravi finds that the whole money is being transported in 1 of 3 containers by Bittu to the sea port. He finds out the right container and the driver of the container. He uses his sharp wit to divert the container and makes it stop before the very bank from which the money was stolen. Bittu is confronted by Ravi &amp; Sitaram and a fight arises between Ravi and Bittu. Sitaram shoots Bittu while he tries to kill Ravi and by their last conversation, Ravi comes to know the location of his sister and Devayani and saves his Sister while Sitaram apprehends Devayani. The film ends with Sitaram transforming into a tough cop and Ravi having a change of mind and starting to believe in hard work.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/n0kZBeYDHDM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
