<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-07T23:01:34-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love U...Mr. Kalakaar!]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/10/01/Love-U...Mr.-Kalakaar%21.html"/>
    <updated>2013-10-01T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2013/10/01/Love-U...Mr.-Kalakaar!</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0Td2ekmN5fc/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Love U...Mr. Kalakaar!"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0Td2ekmN5fc/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Love U...Mr. Kalakaar!"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0Td2ekmN5fc/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Love U...Mr. Kalakaar!"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0Td2ekmN5fc/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Love U...Mr. Kalakaar!"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Watch this Bollywood Blockbuster Romantic Drama Hindi Movie Love U&hellip;Mr. Kalakaar (2011) produced by Rajshri Productions. The movie is directed by S. Manasvi and stars Tusshar Kapoor &amp; Amrita Rao in the lead roles along with Ram Kapoor, Prem Chopra, Madhoo &amp; Yateen Karyekar. Music composed by Sandesh Shandilya.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/0Td2ekmN5fc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. X in Bombay]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2012/02/07/Mr.-X-In-Bombay.html"/>
    <updated>2012-02-07T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2012/02/07/Mr.-X-In-Bombay</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mr. X In Bombay"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mr. X In Bombay"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mr. X In Bombay"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mr. X In Bombay"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Sudarshan (Kishore Kumar), is a talented poet who crosses paths with a young artist, Shobha (Kum Kum) and instantly falls in love with her. Sudarshan is a simpleton while Shobha is very modern girl. Shobha lives a wealthy lifestyle with her father, Professor Mathur who is now carrying out experiments on various issues. One day, Sudarshan goes to meet Shobha at her house but ends up being the guinea pig for her father&rsquo;s experiment. Soon a series of paranormal events follow that alter the lives of everyone. What effects does the experiment bring upon Sudarshan?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YJTyKUytMpw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honeymoon]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/09/13/Honeymoon.html"/>
    <updated>2011-09-13T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/09/13/Honeymoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IJTA8HK-fP8/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Honeymoon"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IJTA8HK-fP8/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Honeymoon"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IJTA8HK-fP8/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Honeymoon"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IJTA8HK-fP8/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Honeymoon"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Neelu and Madhu are close friends and have boyfriends. After hearing about the divorce case of one of their friends, Neelu and Madhu decide to call it quits with their boyfriends. They agree to marry someone who meets with their parents approval. Later Madhu is introduced to Chandrakant and both get  married. On their honeymoon, she meets with Neelu, who is married to Deepak. Both are delighted to see other, and are eager to meet the others spouse, little realizing the shock awaiting them. What surprise awaits the two friends on their honeymoon trip?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/IJTA8HK-fP8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/08/03/Saanch-Ko-Aanch-Nahin.html"/>
    <updated>2011-08-03T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/08/03/Saanch-Ko-Aanch-Nahin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C44IFchcjlg/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C44IFchcjlg/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C44IFchcjlg/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C44IFchcjlg/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Saanch Ko Aanch Nahin is a  Romantic Bollywood Movie. Manoharlal Agarwal is a wealthy businessman who lives with his family consisting of three sons: Pratap, Dilip &amp; Babu, two daughters Nirmala &amp; Munni; his wife, Sharda; &amp; Pratap&rsquo;s wife; He asks Satyaprakash Agarwal to be the sole arbitrator in a matter concerning himself and Hariram. Before the arbitration, he gets his daughter, Nirmala, who is studying in college, to get engaged to Satyaprakash&rsquo;s son, Ajay, who has recently completed his college. Hoping that this will get the arbitration verdict in his favor, he gets a shock when Satyaprakash gives a decision in Hariram&rsquo;s favor. Angered at this humiliation, Manoharlal breaks off the engagement between Ajay and Nirmala, and gets himself appointed as a sole arbitrator in a matter with Satyaprakash on one side and Manikchand on the other. Manoharlal intends to use this position to financially ruin Satyaprakash, and he also intends to wed Nirmala with a man named Murli shortly. What Manoharlal does not know is that Nirmala and Ajay have fallen in love with each other and have decided to elope and get married. Watch what the powerful and wealthy Manoharlal does to prevent Nirmala from getting married to Ajay.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/C44IFchcjlg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mere Bhaiya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/08/03/Mere-Bhaiya.html"/>
    <updated>2011-08-03T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Movies/Movies/Hindi/2011/08/03/Mere-Bhaiya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2unUf9_FfBo/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mere Bhaiya"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2unUf9_FfBo/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Bhaiya"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2unUf9_FfBo/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Bhaiya"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/2unUf9_FfBo/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mere Bhaiya"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Mere Bhaiya is a Bollywood Movie by Rajshri Productions. It is the story about &ldquo;Companionship&rdquo;. On one hand there is a conflict between the Father and Son while on the other hand an unconditional support from a Sister to her Brother. Father Pandit Devdhar Sharma, a reputed lawyer of the town holds orthodox views about culture and manners. He did not want his son Subhash to be friendly with Ranga who because of his conduct and business had earned lot of notoriety. But Subhash was sentimental. He was a poet and a thinker and he wanted to judge good and bad by his own experience as he refused to be guided by what others said. Suffocated by his father&rsquo;s insistence on strict discipline and family traditions, he found pleasure only in the company of Ranga. Torn between the attentions and regard for brother and father was Lakshmi. After their mother&rsquo;s death it was Lakshmi who had to look after her brother and save him from all hardship. To save her brother sometimes she had to hide the truth from his own father. And one day, just when newly married Lakshmi was leaving for her husband&rsquo;s home, she was forced to give her necklace which was part of her dowry, to a Pathan to pay off Subhash&rsquo;s debts. Whenever her husband referred to the necklace Lakshmi got worried. But how long could the hide the truth. When the truth was known Lakshmi was forced to return to her father&rsquo;s home.What happened then? What did Subhash do to bring back happiness to his beloved sister? See it in this story of a brother and sister&rsquo;s deep love for each other, the story of their hopes and frustrations, their happiness and suffering. Their story is the story of today, the story of today&rsquo;s living characters reflecting today&rsquo;s society.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/2unUf9_FfBo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
