<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/classic-blockbuster-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:49:12-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharmilee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Sharmilee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Sharmilee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vXBs3UhR29I/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Sharmilee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Captain Ajit (Shashi Kapoor) crosses paths with young and energetic Kamini (Rakhee) in Kashmir and instantly falls in love with her. After a brief romance, Kamini disappears leaving Ajit in despair of ever seeing her again. Meanwhile, Ajit&rsquo;s guardian, Father Joseph (Nazir Hussein) seeks to arrange Ajit&rsquo;s marriage to Kamini&rsquo;s twin sister, Kanchan (Rakhee in double role), not knowing Ajit has fallen for Kamini. Ajit agrees to the marriage mistaking Kanchan to be Kamini but when the truth comes out, Ajit insists on marrying Kamini, leaving Kanchan heart-broken. Things take a violent turn when Kundan (Ranjeet) a villain from Kamini&rsquo;s past surfaces and threatens to destroy her. Kundan attacks Kamini but ends up getting murdered. In a race to dispose Kundan&rsquo;s body, Kamini meets with an accident and her car falls off a cliff. Presumed dead, Kamini&rsquo;s parents make Kanchan to pose as Kamini and marry her off to Ajit. Is Kamini dead? What happens when the truth gets exposed?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vXBs3UhR29I" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milan - Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath, Deven Varma - Classic Bollywood Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Milan---Sunil-Dutt%2C-Nutan%2C-Jamuna%2C-Pran%2C-Surendranath%2C-Deven-Varma---Classic-Bollywood-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Milan---Sunil-Dutt,-Nutan,-Jamuna,-Pran,-Surendranath,-Deven-Varma---Classic-Bollywood-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/zYNqF3koI7M/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Milan - Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath, Deven Varma - Classic Bollywood Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Milan &ndash; Classic Bollywood Movie &ndash; 1967 Directed By : A.Subba Rao Starring : Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath , Shyama , Deven Varma , Leela Misra, Mukri, Lata Arora, David Music Director : Laxmikant Pyarelal</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/zYNqF3koI7M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Khilona]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Khilona.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Khilona</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/rJALUv2xXyY/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Khilona" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Thakur Suraj Singh lives a wealthy lifestyle with his wife; three sons &ndash; Kishore, his wife Laxmi &amp; two children Pappu and Laali; Vijaykamal, &amp; Mohan; and an unmarried daughter, Radha. Kishore looks after the family business, while Vijaykamal is a renowned poet, and Mohan is studying law in the city. Vijaykamal is in love with Sapna, but she is forced to marry Bihari, and kills herself on the night of the marriage. Vijaykamal witnesses her death and loses his mind. The family decides to keep him under lock and key on the terrace of their house. Unable to admit Vijaykamal to a mental asylum, Suraj brings home a young courtisan, Chand, who he hopes will cure Vijaykamal, and she does succeed considerably, but is traumatized, sexually assaulted by Vijaykamal, and abused by the rest of the family. Mohan finds her very attractive and wants her for himself, so does Bihari. A pregnant Chand is again traumatized when Vijaykamal recovers, but is unable to recognize her. The rest of the family do not believe that the child she is carrying is Vijaykamal&rsquo;s, and want her to leave. The question remains, what can this woman, who has been used as a toy, do under these circumstances?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/rJALUv2xXyY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Junglee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Junglee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Junglee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/snVIebSQUXw/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Junglee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Junglee. Synopsis : The difference between rich and poor always flanks the real love. This story is of how redundant regulations of royal family brings in risk the love of a youth and his sister who loves a girl and a boy respectively from a lower class family. Shekhar belongs to an noble family, run by his domineering mom who believes laughter is a sign of belonging to the lower class. In this household the only one who dares to laugh and enjoy life is Shekhar&rsquo;s sister Mala, who loves Jeevan. Things change when their mom finds out about Mala&rsquo;s imprudence, and she asks Shekhar to take her away from their home, to Kashmir. There he meets beautiful Rajkumari and becomes a cheerful man in love. To make matters worse, Rajkumari does not belong to a princely family, and Shekhar knows that his mom will never approve of his marriage with Rajkumari. Will they ever get marry?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/snVIebSQUXw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chitchor - Amol Palekar, Zarina Wahab, Vijayendra Ghatge, Master Rajoo - Romantic Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Chitchor---Amol-Palekar%2C-Zarina-Wahab%2C-Vijayendra-Ghatge%2C-Master-Rajoo---Romantic-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:49:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Chitchor---Amol-Palekar,-Zarina-Wahab,-Vijayendra-Ghatge,-Master-Rajoo---Romantic-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wgZ0HOQ18wQ/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Chitchor - Amol Palekar, Zarina Wahab, Vijayendra Ghatge, Master Rajoo - Romantic Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>A simple, yet interesting romantic movie, &lsquo;Chitchor&rsquo; revolves around Vinod  &ndash; Amol Palekar who falls in love with Geeta &ndash; Zarina Wahab after her family mistakes him for someone else. When the misunderstanding about Vinod&rsquo;s identity is cleared, it seems that he may have to lose Geeta for no fault of his. This Basu Chatterji film boasts of a sterling performance by Master Rajoo and an excellent music score by Ravindra Jain, which contains soulful songs like &lsquo;Gori Tera Gaon&rsquo;, &lsquo;Jab Deep Jale Aana&rsquo;, &lsquo;Tu Jo Mere Sur Mein&rsquo; and &lsquo;Aaj Se Pehle&rsquo;.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wgZ0HOQ18wQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
