<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/classic-blockbuster-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:13:03-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharmilee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Sharmilee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Sharmilee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vXBs3UhR29I/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sharmilee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Captain Ajit (Shashi Kapoor) crosses paths with young and energetic Kamini (Rakhee) in Kashmir and instantly falls in love with her. After a brief romance, Kamini disappears leaving Ajit in despair of ever seeing her again. Meanwhile, Ajit's guardian, Father Joseph (Nazir Hussein) seeks to arrange Ajit's marriage to Kamini's twin sister, Kanchan (Rakhee in double role), not knowing Ajit has fallen for Kamini. Ajit agrees to the marriage mistaking Kanchan to be Kamini but when the truth comes out, Ajit insists on marrying Kamini, leaving Kanchan heart-broken. Things take a violent turn when Kundan (Ranjeet) a villain from Kamini's past surfaces and threatens to destroy her. Kundan attacks Kamini but ends up getting murdered. In a race to dispose Kundan's body, Kamini meets with an accident and her car falls off a cliff. Presumed dead, Kamini's parents make Kanchan to pose as Kamini and marry her off to Ajit. Is Kamini dead? What happens when the truth gets exposed?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>

<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milan - Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath, Deven Varma - Classic Bollywood Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Milan---Sunil-Dutt%2C-Nutan%2C-Jamuna%2C-Pran%2C-Surendranath%2C-Deven-Varma---Classic-Bollywood-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Milan---Sunil-Dutt,-Nutan,-Jamuna,-Pran,-Surendranath,-Deven-Varma---Classic-Bollywood-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/zYNqF3koI7M/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Milan - Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath, Deven Varma - Classic Bollywood Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Milan - Classic Bollywood Movie - 1967 Directed By : A.Subba Rao Starring : Sunil Dutt, Nutan, Jamuna, Pran, Surendranath , Shyama , Deven Varma , Leela Misra, Mukri, Lata Arora, David Music Director : Laxmikant Pyarelal


<p>Synopsis : On the banks of the holy River Ganga, Gopi, a ferryman conducts an unconsummated romance with Radha, a girl from the upper classes. At the same time, he rejects the advances of Gauri, a girl from his own village, who is attracting the unwanted attention of Radha&rsquo;s lecherous uncle. Fate is not kind to them. Radha is married off to a man she doesn&rsquo;t care for and Gopi is severely beaten by thugs sent by Radha&rsquo;s uncle after he prevents him from molesting Gauri. Radha&rsquo;s husband dies suddenly and she returns home in disgrace to find her father is dangerously ill. However, the attraction between Radha and Gopi remains as strong as ever and ugly rumours start to circulate about the nature of their relationship &ndash; for which Gopi blames the jealous Gauri. Emotions come to the boil and tragedy results. Fortunately, for all concerned, another birth awaits them.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Junglee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Junglee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Junglee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/snVIebSQUXw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Junglee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Junglee. Synopsis : The difference between rich and poor always flanks the real love. This story is of how redundant regulations of royal family brings in risk the love of a youth and his sister who loves a girl and a boy respectively from a lower class family. Shekhar belongs to an noble family, run by his domineering mom who believes laughter is a sign of belonging to the lower class. In this household the only one who dares to laugh and enjoy life is Shekhar's sister Mala, who loves Jeevan. Things change when their mom finds out about Mala's imprudence, and she asks Shekhar to take her away from their home, to Kashmir. There he meets beautiful Rajkumari and becomes a cheerful man in love. To make matters worse, Rajkumari does not belong to a princely family, and Shekhar knows that his mom will never approve of his marriage with Rajkumari. Will they ever get marry?


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amar Prem]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Amar-Prem.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Amar-Prem</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Sp-9EYdTlfc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Amar Prem" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>AMAR PREM is the story of three innocent souls-who by circumstances come near each other and are bound by the thread of eternal love. Pushpa - Sharmila Tagore a simple housewife from a village is thrown out of her house by her husband because she could not have a child. Dejected she comes to her own village and meets a croom nepal babu - who takes her to calcutta to give her a job. There she is cheated by him and is forced to take shelter in prostitute quarters.  Anand - Rajesh Khanna A rich man of the city is neglected by his ultra modern wife and has no place to go. One day while passing through the same locality he hears a song and is attracted by the beautiful voice. He meets pushpa and both are tied to each other.  Nandoo - a child who stays nearby - is always ill-treated by his step-mother. He comes in pushpa's life and finds a mother in her. But fate had something else to offer. They are all separated and how they are again united after ages - that is what you will see in  Amar Prem.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajnabee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Ajnabee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/21/Ajnabee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wiv0VF1OSe4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Ajnabee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch this Bollywood film Ajnabee (1974)


<p>Synopsis: Middle-classed young and dashing Rohit Kumar Saxena falls in love with wealthy and lovely Reshmi, and both decide to get married. Reshmi&rsquo;s dad, the wealthy Diwan Sardarilal is strongly opposed to this marriage, but relents when Reshmi refuses to marry anyone else. As a result, Rohit and Reshmi get married. Shortly after their marriage, Reshmi gets pregnant, news that is very well received. Then Reshmi enters a beauty pageant, and wins it &ndash; being crowned Miss India, with offers to travel abroad. Reshmi decides that she does not want the child now, but Rohit opposes this decision. Both quarrel, and separate, and Reshmi goes back to live with her dad. Shortly thereafter, Sardarilal sends a legal notice to Rohit asking for a divorce. Devastated, Rohit seeks employment, and finds it as a station master at a remote hill station. He meets with Reshmi and her dad, and is humiliated because he is poor. He decides to accumulate enough money to win back Reshmi&rsquo;s love, and decides to do it quickly. This decision results in his being arrested for stealing a suitcase full of jewelery and valuables, and he is also charged with killing the owner of the suitcase &ndash; a Miss Sonia. Looks like Rohit&rsquo;s dream of getting back together with his wife will remain unfulfilled during this lifetime.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
