<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/classic-blockbuster-hindi-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T01:09:11-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vishwanath]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Vishwanath.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Vishwanath</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pvMrnzfvRZ4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vishwanath" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>An honest lawyer, Vishwanath is implicated and imprisoned at the behest of powerful underworld don, GNK and his associates. After his release from prison, Vishwanath decides to seek vengeance, but finds out that it is virtually impossible to do this through due process of law. So he decides to change his identity, hire a gang of crooks and assassins, to carry out his vendetta. Not realizing that in doing this he is alienating himself from the love of his life, Soni; and making himself a wanted man by the police, leaving his crippled sister, Munni and mom, Shanti to fend for themselves, and at the mercy of GNK and his associates.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pvMrnzfvRZ4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suraj]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Suraj.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Suraj</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DsceB49u6Og/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Suraj" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Suraj &ndash; Classic Bollywood Movie Directed By : T. Prakash Rao Starring : Vyjayanthimala, Rajendra Kumar, Ajit, Mumtaz, Johnny Walker, Lalita Pawar, Jagirdar, Agha, David, Mukri, Keshav. Music Director : Shankar Jaikishan, Lyricist : Hasrat Jaipuri, Shailendra Singers: Mohd.Rafi, Asha Bhosle, Suman Kalyanpur, Sharada.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DsceB49u6Og" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharmilee]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Sharmilee.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Sharmilee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vXBs3UhR29I/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sharmilee" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Captain Ajit (Shashi Kapoor) crosses paths with young and energetic Kamini (Rakhee) in Kashmir and instantly falls in love with her. After a brief romance, Kamini disappears leaving Ajit in despair of ever seeing her again. Meanwhile, Ajit&rsquo;s guardian, Father Joseph (Nazir Hussein) seeks to arrange Ajit&rsquo;s marriage to Kamini&rsquo;s twin sister, Kanchan (Rakhee in double role), not knowing Ajit has fallen for Kamini. Ajit agrees to the marriage mistaking Kanchan to be Kamini but when the truth comes out, Ajit insists on marrying Kamini, leaving Kanchan heart-broken. Things take a violent turn when Kundan (Ranjeet) a villain from Kamini&rsquo;s past surfaces and threatens to destroy her. Kundan attacks Kamini but ends up getting murdered. In a race to dispose Kundan&rsquo;s body, Kamini meets with an accident and her car falls off a cliff. Presumed dead, Kamini&rsquo;s parents make Kanchan to pose as Kamini and marry her off to Ajit. Is Kamini dead? What happens when the truth gets exposed?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vXBs3UhR29I" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Professor]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Professor.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Professor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_zYbGVfwhqI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Professor" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Pritam (Shammi Kapoor), is a young man who in desperate need of a job to pay for his ill mother&rsquo;s treatment. He finds out about a job tutoring two young women and two school going children but the catch is that their guardian, Sita Devi Verma (Lalita Pawar) will only hire an old man for the job. Pritam puts on a disguise as an old man and takes up the  job. Sita Devi Verma is the guardian of the young women whose parents have recently died. She is very strict and her relationship with the young women is very tense.  While Pritam&rsquo;s young avatar is romancing Neena (Kalpana), one of his students, his old avatar is romancing their guardian, Sita Devi. What comic situations will Pritam get into with his disguise?What will happen when Sita Devi finds out about the truth?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/_zYbGVfwhqI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prince]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Prince.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:04:48-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Classic-Blockbuster-Hindi-Movies/2014/03/22/Prince</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/dG3bEy9dn-U/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Prince" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Prince Shamsher Singh (Shammi Kapoor) is the only son of the local King, is an irresponsible, alcoholic, and womanizing adult, who wants everyone to bow down before him and his princely rank. One priest refuses to do so, and Shamsher pummels him mercilessly. Frustrated, he asks the priest what he should with his mundane life, and the priest tells him that he should repent, sacrifice all his palatial pleasures, and live the life of a simple and ordinary man, and hence learn the true meaning of life, for at least six months. Shamsher agrees to do so, and arranges an accident with his car, which crashes down a mountain, explodes and is blown to smithereens. Everyone in the palace believe that Shamsher is dead. He goes to a nearby village, and a blind woman there mistakes him for her long-lost son and starts calling him Sajjan Singh. Shamsher decides to play along as Sajjan. How will life treat the Prince who is set to live as a commoner?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dG3bEy9dn-U" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
