<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: South-Indian-Punch | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/south-indian-punch/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:16:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Hai Muqaddar Ka Sikandar - Bollywood Blockbuster Movie - Chiranjeevi , Bhanu Priya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Yeh-hai-Muqaddar-ka-Sikandar---Bollywood-Blockbuster-Movie---Chiranjeevi-%2C-Bhanu-Priya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Yeh-hai-Muqaddar-ka-Sikandar---Bollywood-Blockbuster-Movie---Chiranjeevi-,-Bhanu-Priya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XnHG6KBuTcg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh hai Muqaddar ka Sikandar -  Bollywood Blockbuster Movie - Chiranjeevi , Bhanu Priya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Story of two twin brothers named Yuvraj & Raju. Raju wants to take revenge of his parents murder and therefore he starts killing his parents murderers one by one. Yuvraj being a cop tries to arrest Raju but fails at it. Watch the movie to see whether Raju is succesful in taking the revenge and whether yuvraj is able to arrest his own brother.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeh Diljale - Full Bollywood Movie - Sai Kumar, Thriller Manju]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Yeh-Diljale---Full-Bollywood-Movie---Sai-Kumar%2C-Thriller-Manju.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Yeh-Diljale---Full-Bollywood-Movie---Sai-Kumar,-Thriller-Manju</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ZtA-D_m4-ZM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Yeh Diljale - Full Bollywood Movie - Sai Kumar, Thriller Manju" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch Yeh Diljale - Bollywood Movie. Producer : Imran Qureshi, Director :Thriller Manju, Cast :Sai Kumar, Manju.


<p>Synopsis: ACP Narhari goes ahead with various missions to reach the secret of every underworld plan and accordingly imprisons the hooligans. Narsimha is also a capable young guy who enters Narhari&rsquo;s house on a secret mission. He is basically on a mission to kill Narhari. Fortunately, Narhari keeps safe and now needs to know the reason behind Narsimha&rsquo;s behavior. His father reveals a secret to Narhari but he could not define the problem clearly. To understand the depth of this difficulty Narhari reaches Hyderabad. Here he meets Lavanya and falls in love with her. Will Narhari get exposed to the problem and will he be able to solve it successfully?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taqatwala - Chiranjeevi - Bollywood Action Full Length Movie]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Taqatwala---Chiranjeevi---Bollywood-Action-Full-Length-Movie.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Taqatwala---Chiranjeevi---Bollywood-Action-Full-Length-Movie</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yI0j6_-2_74/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Taqatwala - Chiranjeevi - Bollywood Action Full Length Movie" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch the classic Bollywood film Taqatwala (1983) Starring: Chiranjeevi, Madhavi, Silk Smita, Prem Kumar, Chitra Sushma. Directed by K S R Doss.


<p>Synopsis: Taqatwala is an action suspense thriller based movie in which, Chiranjeevi played the role of CID informer and Thyagaraju and Prabhakar are two gang leaders and CID officer Neelima (Silk Smitha) is assigned to burst their underworld.</p>

<p>Neelima uses Sikander (Chiranjeevi), who works for them, as her informer, but before sikander manages to gather enough evidences, Prabhakar comes to know about his reality and kills him. Now, Neelima is left without any support in her mission.
Oneday, she spots a Sikander look a like (chiru again) and persuades him to act like sikander, During this process, they fall in love with each other. In the end, sikander manages to liquidate all secret activities of thyagu and bhayankar and helps neelima in completing her mission.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sarfarosh - the Burning Youth - Bollywood Movie - Diya, Kalyan Ram, Ravi Kale, Charan Raj]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Sarfarosh---The-Burning-Youth---Bollywood-Movie---Diya%2C-Kalyan-Ram%2C-Ravi-Kale%2C-Charan-Raj.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Sarfarosh---The-Burning-Youth---Bollywood-Movie---Diya,-Kalyan-Ram,-Ravi-Kale,-Charan-Raj</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TPEKqIR1SgU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sarfarosh - The Burning Youth - Bollywood Movie - Diya, Kalyan Ram, Ravi Kale, Charan Raj" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch Sarfarosh - The Burning Youth - Bollywood Movie. Producer : Anil Arora, Chandra B. Verma, Director :Anil Krishna, Cast : Charan Raj, Ravi Kale, Diya, Kalyan Ram .


<p>Synopsis: The story rotates around Pratap (Kalyan Ram), an angry young student who gets aroused by inequities around him. Prakash (Ravi Kale) and his brother Thambi are hardened criminals. Their violent writ runs all over. Obviously Pratap runs into them. Pratap kills Thambi. So Prakash is thirsting for revenge. Meanwhile, Pratap falls in love with Diya, she is the daughter of Raghunath (Charanraj), a big crook of the society. Raghunath is impressed with the boldness of Pratap and agrees to marry his daughter to him. In the meantime, Pratap comes to know that Raghunath has been trying to eliminate him. Lets us watch the movie to know how Pratap manages to ward off the evil forces. There is a touching sentimental thread woven around the revenge plot.
Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts">https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Return of Tezaab - Bollywood Movie - Sumanth, Sangeeta, Ashish Vidhyarti]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Return-Of-Tezaab---Bollywood-Movie---Sumanth%2C-Sangeeta%2C-Ashish-Vidhyarti.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Indian-Punch/2014/03/21/Return-Of-Tezaab---Bollywood-Movie---Sumanth,-Sangeeta,-Ashish-Vidhyarti</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vQDCGFKg88c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Return Of Tezaab - Bollywood Movie - Sumanth, Sangeeta, Ashish Vidhyarti" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Watch Bollywood Movie Return Of Tezaab. Director : G. Siva, Cast : Sumanth, Sangeeta, Ashish Vidhyarti.


<p>Synopsis: Dhanam (Sangitha) is the youngest member in a family of sex workers. Young, beautiful and vivacious, Dhanam rules a tiny suburb in Hyderabad .She is the dream-girl of men who queue up to be in her company. Though reluctantly involved in the hereditary occupation, Dhanam&rsquo;s thoughts are noble.She helps the poor residents in her colony with a portion of her earnings. Anybody within her close circle knows her true self, one that is beyond the fa?ade of a sex worker and crowd-puller.
Anantharaman (Prem) a Brahmin boy, happens to witness some of Dhanam&rsquo;s charitable work. Moved by her selfless nature, he decides to marry her. Soon, Anantharaman approaches Dhanam and expresses his interest and his decision. Though initially surprised at his suggestion, Dhanam scrutinizes Anantharaman&rsquo;s stability in his decision. After gaining considerable trust in the young gentleman, Dhanam consents for the wedding. However, she puts forth a condition. She asks Anantharaman to convince his parents and only with their approval and blessings would she agree for the arrangement. But Anantharaman&rsquo;s conservative family does not accept their son&rsquo;s weird request. Subsequently, arguments and disagreements arise in the family. At that tumultuous situation, astrologer Vedagiri (Kota Srinivasa Rao) visits Anantharaman&rsquo;s family. Listening to the family&rsquo;s predicament and examining Dhanam and Anantharaman&rsquo;s horoscopes, the astrologer presents a surprising finding. He assures the family that if the couple are married, Dhanam&rsquo;s luck is likely to bring in more wealth into the family and it would certainly raise the family&rsquo;s status. Excited by the prediction and the prospect of wealth, the family finally agrees for the wedding. Dhanam and Anantharaman are happily married in a grand wedding ceremony.
However, Vedagiri tries to use Dhanam&rsquo;s precarious position to his own advantage. He tries to lure her to sleep with him. Not knowing a
safe way out, poor Dhanam continues to avoid him. Eventually, Dhanam becomes pregnant which kindles a lot of doubts amid
Anantharaman&rsquo;s family members. The situation becomes serious and unable to prove her stand, Dhanam walks out of Anantharaman&rsquo;s
life. Does she extract revenge on the family for its messy approach and mean attitude? Does she nurture the same warmth and love on her
husband even after the split? Does she wish to return to him? Does the child prove her innocence? What happens to Vedagiri? Does he
continue to trouble Dhanam? How does Dhanam handle him and how does she teach him a lesson? Dhanam, the tragic tale, has all the answers.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts">https://plus.google.com/100462035193279555026/posts</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/">http://pinterest.com/rajshridotcom/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom">https://www.facebook.com/rajshridotcom</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
