<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Famous-TV-Shows | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/famous-tv-shows/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:47:22-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fauji - Episode 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Fauji---Episode-1.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Fauji---Episode-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xBUryt4BpMY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Fauji - Episode 1" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>About The Show: Fauji was a TV series following the training of an Indian Army commando regiment that aired on India&rsquo;s national channel DD National in 1988. With the extremely popular soap Fauji the Bollywood superstar Shah Rukh Khan made his television debut. The soap is based on the life of an irresponsible lad who finally matures into a responsible army man in the due course of his life. Watch all the episodes of Fauji on Rajshri.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xBUryt4BpMY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chanakya - Episode 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Chanakya---Episode-1.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Chanakya---Episode-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/vmnRN9DGOS4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Chanakya - Episode 1" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>&lsquo;Chanakya&rsquo; was a renowned Indian scholar and teacher to the Maurya Emperor Chandragupta. We bring you Dr. Chandraprakash Dwivedi&rsquo;s popular television series &lsquo;Chanakya&rsquo;, a 47-part Indian television historical drama that won the prestigious Uptron Awards in the year 1992. The series takes us through the life of Chanakya, his works &ndash; Chanakya Neeti and Arthasastra. His teachings on politics, economics and social welfare can be used even today in the modern world. The narration of the story has been kept simple to match up with the finest details that begin from the early life of Vishnugupta (Chanakya) in the kingdom of Magadha to the historic rebellion against Alexander under the leadership of Chandragupta Maurya and ends with the coronation of Chandragupta Maurya as the King of Magadha. The critically acclaimed show is definitely worth watching for its authentic costumes, artistic value and most importantly to strengthen our relationship with the Indian history.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vmnRN9DGOS4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akbar the Great - Episode 01]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Akbar-The-Great---Episode-01.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Akbar-The-Great---Episode-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ZffvRbswyI0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Akbar The Great - Episode 01" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Akbar The Great &ndash; Episode 1- Classic Indian Hindi TV Show directed by Akbar Khan narrates the magnificent and moving story of Jalaluddin Mohammed, known to posterity as Akbar The Great". The show vividly re-captures one of the most dazzling and outstanding accounts of chivalry valour and statesmanship in the history of the world.? The serial has been produced and directed by Akbar Khan, a well established motion picture producer, director and leading film actor. He has also directed -The Sword of Tipu Sultan. The Show stars Akbar Khan, Shikha Rai, Vikrant Chaturvedi, Shahid Khan, Ghazal, Arvind Bahmi,Puja Acharya, Shoeb Khan, Puja Ghai, Ishtiaq Khan, Sharmilee Raj, Sushma Seth, Col. Kapoor, Nawab Shah &amp; Shiv Rohira. Music Composed by Naushad.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ZffvRbswyI0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiger Episode - 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Tiger-Episode---1.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Tiger-Episode---1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/59gv5p8CTDM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tiger Episode - 1" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch the entire series back to back &ndash; <a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLF01DF97CCFC9015A">http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLF01DF97CCFC9015A</a></p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/59gv5p8CTDM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talaash - Episode 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Talaash---Episode-1.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:42:06-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Famous-TV-Shows/2014/03/22/Talaash---Episode-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/f8nDBrAdml0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Talaash - Episode 1" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Talaash is the story of Shankarlal&rsquo;s search for his beloved cousin Sudhir. Disillusioned in life, Sudhir had left home after his mother&rsquo;s death. In his search, Shankarlal learns that Sudhir lived in Sarsavan, a small hilly town. There he fell in love with Rajasaheb&rsquo;s daughter Urmila but ruined his life by having an illicit relationship with Pramila, his sister-in-law. Shankarlal learns of Sudhir&rsquo;s presence in an ashram and goes to meet him there. What he sees there shocks him to the core.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/f8nDBrAdml0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
