<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/hindi-dubbed-superhit-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T21:20:56-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mard Ki Zaban]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Mard-Ki-Zaban.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Mard-Ki-Zaban</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/SIsNMl-LlPw/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mard Ki Zaban"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Ram the only son of a wealthy and influential farmer Anjaneya Prasad. Anjaneya Prasad is a happy and contented man. He lives happily with his son Ram, three daughters, sons-in-law, and grandchildren in the same house. However, he has one wish unfulfilled that is to see his son marry and settle down in life. But Ram keeps delaying marriage, as he is apprehensive whether his wife will agree to live in a joint family. However, Ram finally relents after he comes across Raja Rajeswari in unexpected circumstances and falls in love with her. Raja Rajeshwari is the daughter of politician Chamundeshwari and Shankar Rao. The families agree to the marriage but even before the newly weds can go home a small issue between the two families get blown out of proportion. As a result, the two families break up the marriage and part ways. Later, Ram and Rajeswari plans to go abroad for some time to overcome their grief. In a coincidence, the two of them head to the same place Mauritius. Into this Ram meets an old friend Shraddha Das who is madly in love with Ram. However, the married couple reconciles their differences and marries in Mauritius. They come back to India only to face the wrath of their respective families. How they come out of the situation is the remaining part of the story.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/SIsNMl-LlPw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mar Mitenge]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Mar-Mitenge.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Mar-Mitenge</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jLda6G2Nawg/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mar Mitenge"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jLda6G2Nawg/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mar Mitenge"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jLda6G2Nawg/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mar Mitenge"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/jLda6G2Nawg/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mar Mitenge"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Tony who does anything for money. When tony went to Kashmir he met a young girl named Niharika while being kidnapped by terrorists. He falls in love with her and then rescues her. But tony found out that Niharika was already engaged to Rakesh. Rakesh is a goon but Niharika doesn&rsquo;t know that. When Niharika found out that he was a goon, she dumped him. And she also came to know that she is in love with tony. Later on tony kills Rakesh and captures his son DSP Jr. Later on when Tony, Niharika, and Chitra go to the temple, Chitra sees tony killing someone. And then there is a flashback about how he and niharika met before but she lost her memory. That happened because niharika&rsquo;s brother was an undercover cop and when goons found out they killed the whole family. The only one who survived was niharika but she had a bullet in her head. The doctors said that she would lose her memory soon. So, she tells Tony to kill the people who killed her family because she had seen Tony beating up a bunch of people. In the end tony kills all the goons who killed Niharika&rsquo;s family.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/jLda6G2Nawg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[HoneyMoon Ke Side Effects]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/HoneyMoon-Ke-Side-Effects.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/HoneyMoon-Ke-Side-Effects</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ndAYVkmj1F4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="HoneyMoon Ke Side Effects"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ndAYVkmj1F4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="HoneyMoon Ke Side Effects"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ndAYVkmj1F4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="HoneyMoon Ke Side Effects"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/ndAYVkmj1F4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="HoneyMoon Ke Side Effects"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Sandhana Krishnan, also known as Sakhi works in an automobile company and lives in a joint family. He comes across a model named Priya and the two fall in love with each other. Eventually they get married. Here begins the story. Unlike that of Sakhi&rsquo;s family, Priya&rsquo;s family is &lsquo;cosmopolitan&rsquo; and too outgoing. Her mother, is a party going socialite, while her father restricts himself to his house and doesn&rsquo;t bother to have a social life of his own. Priya always goes out partying and doesn&rsquo;t spend much time with her family. Brought up in such a situation, Priya finds it hard to adjust to the family of Sakhi because his family doesn&rsquo;t like all this going out and partying stuff. They prefer to stay home and mix with family. Sakhi tries to make his wife understand the realities of life and the importance of family but is unsuccessful. After their honeymoon Priya gets pregnant. Sakhi is on top of the world but Priya has doubts as she feels shes too young to be a mother.priya does not want the baby and she tells sakhi but sakhi tells her that the whole family is happy and if now he goes and tell them then they would be upset but priya says she does nt care about them making sakhi angry and sakhi fires her. She tells her mother about it, who insists shes too young and under a guise that one of her relatives is ill, takes Priya to the hospital for an abortion. Sakhi finds out in time and rushes to the hospital where a reluctant Priya is being pulled towards the abortion room by her mother. When he calls to her she turns but is hit by a stretcher in her abdomen. The story moves ahead with Priya finding her diary in Sakhis suitcase accusing him of tricking her she leaves to her parents house. At the same time she wants a divorce but Sakhi wants the child. The judge presiding rules that Priya will have to have the baby. Sakhi moves into Priya&rsquo;s parents house with her in order to take care of his unborn child, claiming he doesn&rsquo;t trust them, they might try to abort his baby. Months pass and Priya has the baby. As it needs to be fed mothers' milk, Priya moves back in with Sakhis family for a period of two months. These two months find Priya getting closer to her baby then the day before the last, regretting her decision of leaving the house but convinced that Sakhi hates her, decides to go through with it. The next day her parents come to get her, her mother has already selected another husband for her.Sakhi acts unbothered and taking the baby tells her to leave. Halfway home Priya gets out of the car; her dad and herself finally stand up to her mother. She stands lost on the island in the middle of the road when Sakhi drives by,and then priya and sakhi ask forgiveness from each other and hugh each other in the middle of the road and they both return home happily.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ndAYVkmj1F4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangotri]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Gangotri.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Gangotri</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Gangotri"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Neelakanta Naidu is a big factionist. He has a loyal confidant called Narasimha, who is willing to give his life for the sake of his master. After many years, Neelakanta&rsquo;s wife gives a birth to a baby daughter. But all the earlier babies born to Neelakanta Naidu died due to some unknown reason. The priests advise Neelakanta to name his daughter as &lsquo;Gangotri&rsquo;. They also warn Neelakanta that the child has &lsquo;jalagandam&rsquo;, hence they ask Neelakanta to take Gangotri to the holy place of Gangotri in Himalayas and perform the &lsquo;abhyangana snanam&rsquo; for the next 15 years. After 15 years, Gangotri would be free of any danger. When nobody could entertain the child Gangotri, Simhadri &ndash; the son of Narasimha &ndash; entertains her with a song. Simhadri becomes a servant and friend to Gangotri. They grow up together. In the mean time mother of Simhadri sacrifices her life to save Neelakantam. When Gangotri attains puberty, Gangotri&rsquo;s aunt restricts Simhadri from meeting Gangotri. Gangotri and Simhadri realize that they are in love. When Simhadri comes to Gangotri&rsquo;s place clandestinely to meet her, they are caught by Neelakantam. Neelakantam beats Simhadri. Meanwhile, Narasimha comes to the spot and interferes. This causes a rift between Neelakantam and Narasimha. Neelakantam is misinformed about Narasimha&rsquo;s intentions; hence he has bombs planted in the house of Narasimha. Simhadri is away at that time. When Simhadri comes to know that Neelakantam is responsible for the bombing, he comes to Neelakantam&rsquo;s house and challenges that he will marry Gangotri in 365 days. Then Simhadri goes to the holy place Gangotri and waits for his ladylove to come there for the final sacred bath. The rest of the film is about how Simhadri and Gangotri unite.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pW89Woe_bzc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veerta the Power]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Veerta-The-Power.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:27-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/2014/03/25/Veerta-The-Power</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Veerta The Power"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/_eYQMFD474k/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Veerta The Power"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Neelakantam is a village elder. He has two daughters Subbalakshmi and Meenakshi. The film begins with the elopement of Subbalakshmi with one Babu of the same village and he is a friend of Krishna. The entire family of Neelakantam holes up the friends of Babu, on the presumption that they helped him. Krishna is also caught by the men of Neelakantam. Krishna makes an attempt to escape from the village but can not do so after having a look at a beautiful girl, who is none other than Meenakshi. However, he does not know that it is Neelakantam&rsquo;s younger child. Though the entire situation is quite charged, Krishna is on the look out of the girl to whom he loses his heart. Before the interval bang, the secret unravels. Neelakantam&rsquo;s brother realises that it was Krishna who helped Babu in taking away Subbalakshmi in vizag. On being questioned, Krishna takes the entire gang to Hyderabad along with Meenakshi. He tries to impress her whenever, he gets an opportunity . During the search for the girl, an incident occurs and Neelakantam comes out in open and explains Krishna how a father of an eloped girl will be broken. This turns an eye-opener for Krishna, who decides to sacrifice his love. Soon, Neelakantam and his group find Subbalakshmi and her boyfriend. But she makes it very clear that she will be happy only with her boyfriend and dares her father not to try to separate them. Then Neelakantam has challenged to do his younger daughter marriege grandly with broken heart through his elder daughter what she did,In the end, Neelakantam comes to know that Meenakshi falls in love with Krishna. However, Krishna tells Neelakantam that he is against to separate him with his daughter. But Neelakantam realizes the value of love and unites the lovers and the film ends on a happy note, in the same place of Krishna was stopped his running for beautiful girl.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/_eYQMFD474k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
