<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/hindi-dubbed-superhit-romantic-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-08T18:26:30-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangotri]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Romantic/Dubbed/2014/01/09/Gangotri.html"/>
    <updated>2014-01-09T12:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Romantic/Dubbed/2014/01/09/Gangotri</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Gangotri"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pW89Woe_bzc/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Gangotri"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Neelakanta Naidu is a big factionist. He has a loyal confidant called Narasimha, who is willing to give his life for the sake of his master. After many years, Neelakanta&rsquo;s wife gives a birth to a baby daughter. But all the earlier babies born to Neelakanta Naidu died due to some unknown reason. The priests advise Neelakanta to name his daughter as &lsquo;Gangotri&rsquo;. They also warn Neelakanta that the child has &lsquo;jalagandam&rsquo;, hence they ask Neelakanta to take Gangotri to the holy place of Gangotri in Himalayas and perform the &lsquo;abhyangana snanam&rsquo; for the next 15 years. After 15 years, Gangotri would be free of any danger. When nobody could entertain the child Gangotri, Simhadri &ndash; the son of Narasimha &ndash; entertains her with a song. Simhadri becomes a servant and friend to Gangotri. They grow up together. In the mean time mother of Simhadri sacrifices her life to save Neelakantam. When Gangotri attains puberty, Gangotri&rsquo;s aunt restricts Simhadri from meeting Gangotri. Gangotri and Simhadri realize that they are in love. When Simhadri comes to Gangotri&rsquo;s place clandestinely to meet her, they are caught by Neelakantam. Neelakantam beats Simhadri. Meanwhile, Narasimha comes to the spot and interferes. This causes a rift between Neelakantam and Narasimha. Neelakantam is misinformed about Narasimha&rsquo;s intentions; hence he has bombs planted in the house of Narasimha. Simhadri is away at that time. When Simhadri comes to know that Neelakantam is responsible for the bombing, he comes to Neelakantam&rsquo;s house and challenges that he will marry Gangotri in 365 days. Then Simhadri goes to the holy place Gangotri and waits for his ladylove to come there for the final sacred bath. The rest of the film is about how Simhadri and Gangotri unite.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pW89Woe_bzc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Bodyguard]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Romantic/Dubbed/2013/09/27/Main-Hoon-Bodyguard.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-27T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Romantic-Movies/Movies/Hindi/Romantic/Dubbed/2013/09/27/Main-Hoon-Bodyguard</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0sZbkzhuox4/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Bodyguard"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0sZbkzhuox4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Bodyguard"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0sZbkzhuox4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Bodyguard"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0sZbkzhuox4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Bodyguard"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about the strange fascination of a guy who worships anyone with a trace of heroism. He one comes across a reformed liquor mogul and now leading businessman and finds him to be his hero. He then joins him as the bodyguard to protect his beautiful daughter.The body guard and the beautiful daughter fall in love without knowing to each other and later separate without wanting to. What happened to their love and after is the story.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/0sZbkzhuox4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
