<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/south-hindi-dubbed-superhit-action-dhamaka-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T22:44:46-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Wanted]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/09/23/Main-Hoon-Wanted.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-23T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/09/23/Main-Hoon-Wanted</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/02m9G0K7UwE/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Wanted"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/02m9G0K7UwE/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Wanted"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/02m9G0K7UwE/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Wanted"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/02m9G0K7UwE/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Wanted"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Alibhai a mafia don and Darshan is a police officer investigating Alibhai and his mafia. Darshan comes to Ali&rsquo;s mafia as a rowdy. He killed many people in the mafia secretly. Anjali loves Darshan who saves her from a policeman who intends to make her his wife. Alibhai comes from Dubai and kills the father and brother of Darshan. Finally, Darshan kills Alibhai and destroys his gang.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02m9G0K7UwE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Vinashak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/06/21/Main-Hoon-Vinashak.html"/>
    <updated>2013-06-21T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/06/21/Main-Hoon-Vinashak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Easwaran who is upright and honest youth, who runs a local cable channel in Kumbakonam. He is known to fight for the cause of the society and the common man. He enters into fisticuffs with local MLA after he exposes his corrupt and greedy ways through his cable TV channel. Fearing trouble, his mom takes him to a saint in Thiruvannamalai. The Swami resembles Easwaran. A sequence of events forces them to swap places. The soft-spoken Swami tries to sort all issues through non-violent means. Half way through Karunas dies in the hand of and the corrupt MLA. In the climax Easwaran kills off the MLA.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wqwYk7uavi4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mera Farz]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Farz.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-29T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/29/Mera-Farz</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C_lI0PT-bLk/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Mera Farz"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C_lI0PT-bLk/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Farz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C_lI0PT-bLk/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Farz"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/C_lI0PT-bLk/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Mera Farz"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Aalwar which is a traditional priest. He is devoted to his mother and sister. But the villainous elements Lal, Vincent Asokan, kill the sister and mother. Aalwar, with revenge ringing in his mind, ends up as Shiva the killer, even while working as a ward boy in a hospital. Shiva is out to make a statement against the venal forces. He sees himself as some kind of avatar in fact, he bumps off the baddies under the get-up&rsquo;s of Lord Rama and Lord Krishna. In climax, Shiva turns up as Lord Narasimha and bumps off the last villain by placing him on his thighs and ripping apart his bowels and chest with his sharp claws.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/C_lI0PT-bLk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marte Dam Tak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/22/Marte-Dam-Tak.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-22T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/22/Marte-Dam-Tak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/g5OsHeJfK6Q/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Marte Dam Tak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/g5OsHeJfK6Q/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Marte Dam Tak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/g5OsHeJfK6Q/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Marte Dam Tak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/g5OsHeJfK6Q/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Marte Dam Tak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Koti He has only one goal in life. That is to become a hero and to be called as &lsquo;Babu&rsquo; by the industry people. Amjad is an auto driver. Though extremely religious Muslim, Amjad is very patriotic about India. His younger brother Azhar is been missing since one year. The cops of Hyderabad arrested a dreadful ISI terrorist Masood. In a bid to get him released, the Pakistan authorities train Azhar and send him across to Hyderabad to create riots and build communal tension. Azhar comes to Hyderabad and stays with his brother Amjad. Azhar&rsquo;s secret activities include devising and executing plans to release Masood. Radha Krishna is a sincere and efficient police officer. But he is very serious in nature and has enormous hatred towards Pakistan for the reasons best known to him. The rest of the story includes how these three protagonists save the terrorist Masood from fleeing to Pakistan. And of course there is a 15 minutes flashback for Radha Krishna that involves his ladylove Swathy getting killed by the ISI guys.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/g5OsHeJfK6Q" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jigarwala]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/22/Jigarwala.html"/>
    <updated>2013-05-22T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2013/05/22/Jigarwala</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Jigarwala"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The film starts with the police arresting Aadhikesavan&rsquo;s men suspecting them for burning an MLA&rsquo;s wine shop.The MLA sends a false evidence to the court against Aadhikesavan.But Aadhi sends Dheena who is actually his adopted brother to attack the false evidence.Later some people complain to Aadhi that the MLA had removed the breakwire from a schoolvan due to rivalry between his school and their school leading to the death of many children.Aadhi asks Dheena and his henchmen to cut the hands of the MLA and his men especially the right hand and Dheena completes his task. Meanwhile Dheena falls in love with a girl named Chitra who initially mistakes him to be a bus conductor and later a vegetable seller.One day one of Dheena&rsquo;s henchmen spots Chitra and her cousin in the plaza and reports to Dheena.Dheena pretends to meet her by chance and pays their bill using the plaza manager&rsquo;s money.One day Chitra calls Dheena&rsquo;s home landline number posing as &lsquo;Pepsi&rsquo; Uma and comes to know about Dheena&rsquo;s tricks. Meanwhile Dheena comes to know that someone has teased his sister Shanthi and thrashes him.One day when Dheena meets Chitra they are ridiculed by a gang of rowdies but Dheena stays calm as he thinks that girls hate people who are violent. The next day he meets Chitra at the plaza and tells him he should have beaten the rowdies as she likes violence.As a coincidence the rowdies come and Dheena thrashes them and informs Chitra that he is a local goon.Later she comes to know that Dheena has love for her as she did. Meanwhile the same person who teased Shanthi gave a love letter to her and Dheena beats him up and comes to know that the persons sister was Chitra.Chitra tells him that they both love each other and Dheena agrees to help them.Shanthi accepts this to Dheena but afraid to tell to Aadhi. Finding the difficulty of the situation,Shanthi elopes with her lover and Aadhi&rsquo;s men chase them in which they get into an accident. In the hospital Shanthi tells Dheena to protect her lover&rsquo;s family from Aadhi. Dheena promises and she dies. Aadhi,enraged by his sister&rsquo;s death asks Dheena to kill the family of the boy responsible for Shanthi&rsquo;s death.But Dheena refuses and tells that Shanthi was in love with that boy.But Aadhi could not believe this and misunderstands Dheena was refusing since he loved the boy&rsquo;s sister Chitra.Aadhi swears that he will kill Dheena also and declares he his not his brother anymore. Dheena moves to Chitra&rsquo;s flat to protect her family but her brother does not believe him. Aadhi kills one of Chitra&rsquo;s brother&rsquo;s friend and lands in jail.Dheena stays in the room of two auto drivers who believe in him. One time Aadhi sends his men to kill Chitra&rsquo;s family but Dheena stops them and in the process he gets badly wounded. Chitra&rsquo;s family starts believing Dheena and their love develops. Later Aadhi gets released and orders his men to kill Dheena and Chitra&rsquo;s family.The MLA who was his enemy wants to kill Dheena but Aadhi asks him to stay away due to ego. The MLA creates confusion by sending half of his men in the outfit of auto drivers and remaining in outfit of Aadhi&rsquo;s men.Dheena finds this and goes to warn Aadhi but is unaware that one of the MLA&rsquo;s men had stabbed Chitra. Meanwhile Aadhi comes to know about Shanthi&rsquo;s love from her college friends. Aadhi and Dheena join forces and stop the confusion. Knowing that the MLA was responsible for this,Aadhi goes to kill him but Dheena stops him that if he kills him another person would avenge and this chain could continue and asks him to leave violence. The End is shown in the hospital where Chitra wakes to see Dheena and Aadhi. Aadhi finally declares Dheena to be his brother hereafter.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/OZ21AJ7W8D4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
