<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/south-hindi-dubbed-superhit-action-dhamaka-movies/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-25T22:14:21-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Vinashak]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Main-Hoon-Vinashak.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:29-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Main-Hoon-Vinashak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/wqwYk7uavi4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Main Hoon Vinashak"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Easwaran who is upright and honest youth, who runs a local cable channel in Kumbakonam. He is known to fight for the cause of the society and the common man. He enters into fisticuffs with local MLA after he exposes his corrupt and greedy ways through his cable TV channel. Fearing trouble, his mom takes him to a saint in Thiruvannamalai. The Swami resembles Easwaran. A sequence of events forces them to swap places. The soft-spoken Swami tries to sort all issues through non-violent means. Half way through Karunas dies in the hand of and the corrupt MLA. In the climax Easwaran kills off the MLA.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wqwYk7uavi4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garjana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Garjana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:29-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Garjana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yvwTr8-Au4s/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Garjana"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yvwTr8-Au4s/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Garjana"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yvwTr8-Au4s/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Garjana"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/yvwTr8-Au4s/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Garjana"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Raja who works with a cook Arusuvai Ambi. Raja comes across Anjali, who catches his interest. She falls for Raja. But Raja cannot remember anything of his past. All he recollects are vague images and memories that disturb him in his sleep. After a sequence of events and chase by rowdies, Raja collects his past. Raja, a year ago was Dorai, who was the close associate of honest politician Deivanayagam. Dorai who leads a happy life with his wife and his son, is hesitant to assume the post. Anjali, a reporter, pursues him for interviews and falls in love. Deivanayagam gets killed and the blame falls on Dorai. His wife and son are murdered. Eventually, Dorai alias Raja takes on his enemies cracks the truth behind Deivanayakam&rsquo;s death.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yvwTr8-Au4s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ek Elaan - E - Jung]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Ek-Elaan---E---Jung.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:29-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Ek-Elaan---E---Jung</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VE-mt-wxzHk/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Ek Elaan - E - Jung"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VE-mt-wxzHk/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Elaan - E - Jung"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VE-mt-wxzHk/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Elaan - E - Jung"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/VE-mt-wxzHk/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Ek Elaan - E - Jung"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Sagar is a fun loving guy, bumping babe Rajya Laxmi bumps into Sagar with a cycle first. The family of Sagar meets the family of Rajya Laxmi to fix up the match to Sagar&rsquo;s sister too gets engaged to a guy. There is a parallel story running along with the Sagar&rsquo;s love story. Chepala Krishna is a noted smuggler in Vizag. Chepala Nani is his younger brother. Both of them rule the rowdy world in the steel city. Chepala Krishna has an ambition of a life time. He wants to become an MLA. Krishnam Raju is the S.I. Of police for that area. Enter the C.I. of police Sri Hari He is the most dreaded and honest Police Officer. With the help of Krishnam Raju he gets to know about all the criminals in that area and Chepala Krishna tops the most wanted criminals list. When Chepala Krishna is about to file his nominations for the post of an MLA, he gets arrested by Sri Hari.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VE-mt-wxzHk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jigarwala]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Jigarwala.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Jigarwala</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Jigarwala"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/OZ21AJ7W8D4/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Jigarwala"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The film starts with the police arresting Aadhikesavan&rsquo;s men suspecting them for burning an MLA&rsquo;s wine shop.The MLA sends a false evidence to the court against Aadhikesavan.But Aadhi sends Dheena who is actually his adopted brother to attack the false evidence.Later some people complain to Aadhi that the MLA had removed the breakwire from a schoolvan due to rivalry between his school and their school leading to the death of many children.Aadhi asks Dheena and his henchmen to cut the hands of the MLA and his men especially the right hand and Dheena completes his task. Meanwhile Dheena falls in love with a girl named Chitra who initially mistakes him to be a bus conductor and later a vegetable seller.One day one of Dheena&rsquo;s henchmen spots Chitra and her cousin in the plaza and reports to Dheena.Dheena pretends to meet her by chance and pays their bill using the plaza manager&rsquo;s money.One day Chitra calls Dheena&rsquo;s home landline number posing as &lsquo;Pepsi&rsquo; Uma and comes to know about Dheena&rsquo;s tricks. Meanwhile Dheena comes to know that someone has teased his sister Shanthi and thrashes him.One day when Dheena meets Chitra they are ridiculed by a gang of rowdies but Dheena stays calm as he thinks that girls hate people who are violent. The next day he meets Chitra at the plaza and tells him he should have beaten the rowdies as she likes violence.As a coincidence the rowdies come and Dheena thrashes them and informs Chitra that he is a local goon.Later she comes to know that Dheena has love for her as she did. Meanwhile the same person who teased Shanthi gave a love letter to her and Dheena beats him up and comes to know that the persons sister was Chitra.Chitra tells him that they both love each other and Dheena agrees to help them.Shanthi accepts this to Dheena but afraid to tell to Aadhi. Finding the difficulty of the situation,Shanthi elopes with her lover and Aadhi&rsquo;s men chase them in which they get into an accident. In the hospital Shanthi tells Dheena to protect her lover&rsquo;s family from Aadhi. Dheena promises and she dies. Aadhi,enraged by his sister&rsquo;s death asks Dheena to kill the family of the boy responsible for Shanthi&rsquo;s death.But Dheena refuses and tells that Shanthi was in love with that boy.But Aadhi could not believe this and misunderstands Dheena was refusing since he loved the boy&rsquo;s sister Chitra.Aadhi swears that he will kill Dheena also and declares he his not his brother anymore. Dheena moves to Chitra&rsquo;s flat to protect her family but her brother does not believe him. Aadhi kills one of Chitra&rsquo;s brother&rsquo;s friend and lands in jail.Dheena stays in the room of two auto drivers who believe in him. One time Aadhi sends his men to kill Chitra&rsquo;s family but Dheena stops them and in the process he gets badly wounded. Chitra&rsquo;s family starts believing Dheena and their love develops. Later Aadhi gets released and orders his men to kill Dheena and Chitra&rsquo;s family.The MLA who was his enemy wants to kill Dheena but Aadhi asks him to stay away due to ego. The MLA creates confusion by sending half of his men in the outfit of auto drivers and remaining in outfit of Aadhi&rsquo;s men.Dheena finds this and goes to warn Aadhi but is unaware that one of the MLA&rsquo;s men had stabbed Chitra. Meanwhile Aadhi comes to know about Shanthi&rsquo;s love from her college friends. Aadhi and Dheena join forces and stop the confusion. Knowing that the MLA was responsible for this,Aadhi goes to kill him but Dheena stops him that if he kills him another person would avenge and this chain could continue and asks him to leave violence. The End is shown in the hospital where Chitra wakes to see Dheena and Aadhi. Aadhi finally declares Dheena to be his brother hereafter.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/OZ21AJ7W8D4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Josh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Dynamic-Josh.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-25T09:20:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/South-Hindi-Dubbed-Superhit-Action-Dhamaka-Movies/2014/03/25/Dynamic-Josh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oqu3zMOmaPw/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Dynamic Josh"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oqu3zMOmaPw/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dynamic Josh"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oqu3zMOmaPw/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dynamic Josh"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oqu3zMOmaPw/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Dynamic Josh"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Satya who is a student. He discontinues his graduation studies in Vizag and comes to Hyderabad in search of a job. He stays with his uncle in Hyderabad. He runs into a fight with MGM college students who are influenced by political mafia leader Durga Rao. Satya tries to change the students but fails. Then Satya joins the college to cleanse the system. On the other hand there is Vidhya  who aspires to go to college but could not as her brother feels that college students are rowdies and she would not be safe in college. So she teaches in an elementary school. She meets Satya and love blossoms between them. Main crux of the movie is how Satya changes the students and brings them out of the bad influence of Durga Rao.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oqu3zMOmaPw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
