<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Originals | AnyNewMovies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-originals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T00:43:25-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sawaan Ko Aane Do]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:39:11-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TAduWgissb8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sawaan Ko Aane Do" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Sawaan Ko Aane Do &ndash; 1979 Directed By : Kanak Mishra Starring : Zarina Wahab, Arun Govil, Reeta Bhaduri, Amrish Puri, Pinchoo Kapoor, Ram Mohan, Jagirdar, Roopesh Kumar, Yunus Parvez, Jagirdar, Jankidas, Surendar Kumar, Leela Mishra. Music Director : Rajkamal.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TAduWgissb8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saaransh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saaransh.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:39:11-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saaransh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/uY71PzZvX4g/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Saaransh" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Devastated to learn that their only son has been killed by muggers in New York City, former Headmaster B.B. Pradhan and his wife, Parvati, grieve. With their son dead, there is no source of income for the couple, so they rent out a room, in their Shivaji Park &ndash; Bombay apartment to a budding Bollywood actress, Sujata Suman, who has been having an illicit affair with the only son &ndash; Vilas of a politician named Gajanan Chitre. Vilas lacks the guts to tell his father that he is in love and would like to marry Sujata, and hence puts off any marriage plans. They do get intimate and as a result Sujata gets pregnant. When Pradhan finds out, he offers to take Sujata to meet Gajanan with the hope that he will permit her to become his daughter-in-law. But Gajanan not only refuses, he also threatens them, he warns them of dire consequences if Sujata does not abort the child, and moves away to another town. Pradhan refuses to let Sujata out of his house, and then begins the stalking and harassment by Gajanan&rsquo;s men. Pradhan goes to file a police complaint, but is told that the police cannot even touch Gajanan&rsquo;s men. Sujata has no choice but to continue to seek shelter with Pradhan and his wife. Sujata does not know that Pradhan and Parvati have a secret agenda of their own in keeping her within their sight.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/uY71PzZvX4g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rakta Bandhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Rakta-Bandhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:39:11-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Rakta-Bandhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/sMbnPWsQ2Ag/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Rakta Bandhan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Rakta Bandhan is a Bollywood Movie, starring Mithun Chakraborty &amp; Rati Agnihotri. Kundan and Chandan are idential twins, Dacoits loot their village and carry away Kundan. Kundan becomes the feared decoit Trishul Singh, Chandan drives a tonga in the village. Kundan has an affair with Kammo Bai, a dancing girl, whilst Chandan secretly loves a village maidan, Rupa. Chowdhry bullies all the tonga drivers. Chandan is also severely beaten up and dumped in jungle to die. Hotly chased by the police Kundan is looking for a hiding place when he comes across Chandan lying unconcious. Noticing the natural resemblance, he quickly changes with Chandan and escapes to the village. When Kundan&rsquo;s followers find Chandan, they mistake him for their Sardar and carry him back to their hide-out. Chowdhry is taken aback when he tries to rape Chandan&rsquo;s sister and is given a merciless beating by Kundan. Chowdhry is intrigued to find a weak and timid Chandan suddenly becoming an aggressive bull. Meanwhile Chandan surrounded by the decoits pleads with them to release him. He is not their Sardar. They think he is suffering from loss of memory. Everyone in the village, including Chandan&rsquo;s sweetheart Rupa accept Kundan as Chandan, but he realises that this deceptive disguise cannot go on for ever. He decides to rescue Chandan and restore him to the village. The Police have already discovered the dacoit&rsquo;s den, and Kundan rushes to save his brother&rsquo;s life. Though he succeeds, he falls victim to the police firing, whilst the dancing girl Kammo is also killed in the cross fire. As Kundan is dying, he urges Chandan to return to the village and to his beloved Rupa.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/sMbnPWsQ2Ag" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Piya Ka Ghar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Piya-Ka-Ghar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:39:11-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Piya-Ka-Ghar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Y-7St_MxMEQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Piya Ka Ghar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Piya Ka Ghar is a Classic Bollywood Movie, directed by Basu Chatterjee,  starring Jaya Bhaduri, Anil Dhawan &amp; Ranjita Thakur.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Y-7St_MxMEQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. X in Bombay]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Mr.-X-In-Bombay.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T12:39:11-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Mr.-X-In-Bombay</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mr. X In Bombay" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Sudarshan (Kishore Kumar), is a talented poet who crosses paths with a young artist, Shobha (Kum Kum) and instantly falls in love with her. Sudarshan is a simpleton while Shobha is very modern girl. Shobha lives a wealthy lifestyle with her father, Professor Mathur who is now carrying out experiments on various issues. One day, Sudarshan goes to meet Shobha at her house but ends up being the guinea pig for her father&rsquo;s experiment. Soon a series of paranormal events follow that alter the lives of everyone. What effects does the experiment bring upon Sudarshan?</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YJTyKUytMpw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
