<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Originals | AnyNewMovies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-originals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:13-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivah]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Vivah.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Vivah</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/R9upjxi7_lk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vivah" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic superhit family drama movie, Rajshri Productions' Vivah &ndash; A journey from engagement to marriage with English subtitles, starring Shahid Kapur &amp; Amrita Rao, directed by Sooraj R. Barjatya, music composed by Ravindra Jain.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/R9upjxi7_lk&vq=hd1080" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taraana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taraana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taraana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/k0f1CeZt5dQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Taraana" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Tarana is the melody of love! Love of Radha and Shyam which blossomed in the beautiful valley of Kashmir. When Radha&rsquo;s father Rana came to know of this love affair, he was shaken to the core. For he knew that rich and poor are like two banks of the same river which never meet.Even then for the sake of his daughter&rsquo;s happiness Rana went to Shyam&rsquo;s rich guardian Thakur who spurned the offer and almost literally kicked him out. Little did Thakur knew that Radha whom he rejected as Shyam prospective wife was none other than his own daughter whom he had betrothed to his friend&rsquo;s son Shyam in childhood. After having lost his daughter Thakur had brought up Shyam as his own son. Strange are the ways of fate. Though Thakur was really Radha&rsquo;s father he was bent upon destroying her love and happiness. And Rana who had brought up Radha as his daughter was willing to sacrifice everything for her happiness, but he proved powerless against Thakur&rsquo;s might. And the time came when Thakur was about to kill his own daughter Radha. At that very moment, the doll which was Radha&rsquo;s childhood companion came to her rescue by revealing the truth and re-uniting the lovers.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/k0f1CeZt5dQ&vq=hd1080" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taqdeer]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taqdeer.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taqdeer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PjLMaNKas5w/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Taqdeer" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Taqdeer  is a Classic Bollywood Movie, directed by A. Salam, starring Bharat Bhooshan, Shalini &amp; Kamal Kapoor.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PjLMaNKas5w&vq=hd1080" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tapasya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Tapasya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Tapasya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IhUvewdcZrY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tapasya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Tapasya &ndash; 1976 Directed By : Anil Ganguly Starring : Rakhee Gulzar, Parikshit Sahni, Asrani, A. K. Hangal, Viju Khote, Lalita Pawar, Abha Dhuliya, Gayatri, V. Gopal, Nazir Hussain, Lalita Kumari, Om Shivpuri, Urmila Bhatt,  Adil. Music Director : Ravindra Jain</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/IhUvewdcZrY&vq=hd1080" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shikshaa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Shikshaa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T01:03:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Shikshaa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pu2wULVZgKM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Shikshaa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Shikshaa is the story of a modern youth&rsquo;s awakening. The youth is Vijay Gupta, the only son of the rich Raj Saheb Dwarkadas Gupta and Laxmi Gupta. He was spoiled by the over-indulgence and affection showered by his mother. Thanks to his own irresponsible behaviour, bad company and reckless driving, his car met with an accident in which one man died and his brother lost his eyes. Unmindful, Vijay drove away. The loyal driver of the family, Kundan took the blame for the accident and went to jail. Vijay&rsquo;s father who was a strict disciplinarian rebuked his son for his carelessness and unforgivable crime. In a huff, Vijay left home pledging that he would live his own life and would not divulge to anyone his identity. And Vijay kept up his pledge. Without any recommendation, he got a job as a driver in Kamal Rai&rsquo;s house. By coincidence, Kamal Rai happened to be a great friend of Vijay&rsquo;s father and he had a daughter whom he wanted to marry his friend&rsquo;s son Vijay. Though the daughter Madhu found out Vijay&rsquo;s true identity, she kept it a secret from everyone. Madhu however fell in love with Vijay. To atone for his misdeeds, Vijay spared nothing to help Kishan who had lost his eyes in the accident and Kishan&rsquo;s widowed sister-in-law. Winning a prize in a car race, he got Kishan&rsquo;s eyes operated though he knew that Kishan would recognise him as the man who caused his brother&rsquo;s death and would take revenge on him.  Vijay confronted Kishan when he got his eye sight back. Enraged Kishan was about to kill him. But when he came to know that it was Vijay who had looked after the bereaved family, Kishan realised his madness and instead of killing, he embraced Vijay forgiving him of his sins. To atone for his crime Vijay started to go to the police station to give his confession. On his way he met his anxious parents, fiancee Madhu and his loyal driver who had gone to jail for him&hellip;.find out what happens next.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pu2wULVZgKM&vq=hd1080" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
