<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Originals | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-originals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-22T23:47:37-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taqdeer]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taqdeer.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Taqdeer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PjLMaNKas5w/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Taqdeer" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Taqdeer  is a Classic Bollywood Movie, directed by A. Salam, starring Bharat Bhooshan, Shalini &amp; Kamal Kapoor.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PjLMaNKas5w" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shikshaa]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Shikshaa.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Shikshaa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pu2wULVZgKM/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Shikshaa" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Shikshaa is the story of a modern youth&rsquo;s awakening. The youth is Vijay Gupta, the only son of the rich Raj Saheb Dwarkadas Gupta and Laxmi Gupta. He was spoiled by the over-indulgence and affection showered by his mother. Thanks to his own irresponsible behaviour, bad company and reckless driving, his car met with an accident in which one man died and his brother lost his eyes. Unmindful, Vijay drove away. The loyal driver of the family, Kundan took the blame for the accident and went to jail. Vijay&rsquo;s father who was a strict disciplinarian rebuked his son for his carelessness and unforgivable crime. In a huff, Vijay left home pledging that he would live his own life and would not divulge to anyone his identity. And Vijay kept up his pledge. Without any recommendation, he got a job as a driver in Kamal Rai&rsquo;s house. By coincidence, Kamal Rai happened to be a great friend of Vijay&rsquo;s father and he had a daughter whom he wanted to marry his friend&rsquo;s son Vijay. Though the daughter Madhu found out Vijay&rsquo;s true identity, she kept it a secret from everyone. Madhu however fell in love with Vijay. To atone for his misdeeds, Vijay spared nothing to help Kishan who had lost his eyes in the accident and Kishan&rsquo;s widowed sister-in-law. Winning a prize in a car race, he got Kishan&rsquo;s eyes operated though he knew that Kishan would recognise him as the man who caused his brother&rsquo;s death and would take revenge on him.  Vijay confronted Kishan when he got his eye sight back. Enraged Kishan was about to kill him. But when he came to know that it was Vijay who had looked after the bereaved family, Kishan realised his madness and instead of killing, he embraced Vijay forgiving him of his sins. To atone for his crime Vijay started to go to the police station to give his confession. On his way he met his anxious parents, fiancee Madhu and his loyal driver who had gone to jail for him&hellip;.find out what happens next.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/pu2wULVZgKM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sawaan Ko Aane Do]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TAduWgissb8/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Sawaan Ko Aane Do" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Sawaan Ko Aane Do &ndash; 1979 Directed By : Kanak Mishra Starring : Zarina Wahab, Arun Govil, Reeta Bhaduri, Amrish Puri, Pinchoo Kapoor, Ram Mohan, Jagirdar, Roopesh Kumar, Yunus Parvez, Jagirdar, Jankidas, Surendar Kumar, Leela Mishra. Music Director : Rajkamal.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TAduWgissb8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudagar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saudagar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saudagar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/qhe0xFmGX2Q/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Saudagar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Saudagar &ndash; 1973 &ndash; Full Length Bollywood Movie &ndash; Directed By : Sudhendu Roy Starring : Nutan, Amitabh Bachchan, Padma Khanna, Trilok Kapoor, Murad, Dev Kishen Music Director : Ravindra Jain</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/qhe0xFmGX2Q" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saaransh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saaransh.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-22T11:47:33-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/22/Saaransh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/uY71PzZvX4g/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Saaransh" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Devastated to learn that their only son has been killed by muggers in New York City, former Headmaster B.B. Pradhan and his wife, Parvati, grieve. With their son dead, there is no source of income for the couple, so they rent out a room, in their Shivaji Park &ndash; Bombay apartment to a budding Bollywood actress, Sujata Suman, who has been having an illicit affair with the only son &ndash; Vilas of a politician named Gajanan Chitre. Vilas lacks the guts to tell his father that he is in love and would like to marry Sujata, and hence puts off any marriage plans. They do get intimate and as a result Sujata gets pregnant. When Pradhan finds out, he offers to take Sujata to meet Gajanan with the hope that he will permit her to become his daughter-in-law. But Gajanan not only refuses, he also threatens them, he warns them of dire consequences if Sujata does not abort the child, and moves away to another town. Pradhan refuses to let Sujata out of his house, and then begins the stalking and harassment by Gajanan&rsquo;s men. Pradhan goes to file a police complaint, but is told that the police cannot even touch Gajanan&rsquo;s men. Sujata has no choice but to continue to seek shelter with Pradhan and his wife. Sujata does not know that Pradhan and Parvati have a secret agenda of their own in keeping her within their sight.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/uY71PzZvX4g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
