<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Originals | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-originals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:20:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sawaan Ko Aane Do]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Sawaan-Ko-Aane-Do</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TAduWgissb8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sawaan Ko Aane Do" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Sawaan Ko Aane Do - 1979 Directed By : Kanak Mishra Starring : Zarina Wahab, Arun Govil, Reeta Bhaduri, Amrish Puri, Pinchoo Kapoor, Ram Mohan, Jagirdar, Roopesh Kumar, Yunus Parvez, Jagirdar, Jankidas, Surendar Kumar, Leela Mishra. Music Director : Rajkamal.


<p>Synopsis : Birju (Arun Govil) lives in a small village and likes to sing. The village zamindar&rsquo;s (Amrish Puri) city-educated daughter, Chandrika (Zarina Wahab) returns to the village and is thrilled by Birju&rsquo;s voice. She encourages him to share his talents with the world and thus earn a living. Eventually both fall in love. Her father is angered when he comes to know of their affair, and he sends her back to the city and warns Birju of attempting to even think about her. Heartbroken Birju decides to go to the city, and there he meets with Gitanjali (Rita Bhaduri), who is also thrilled by his voice. She assists him in getting an audition, and which turns out to be a success. Soon Birju is singing over the radio, and becomes wealthy and popular. In the meantime, Chandrika&rsquo;s pround dad has lost an important court case, and as a result lost all his wealth, but his pride is still intact. When Birju returns to ask for the hand of Chandrika, he is again rebuked. Will Birju and Chandrika ever marry? Or will Birju marry Gitanjali?</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saaransh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Saaransh.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Saaransh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/uY71PzZvX4g/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Saaransh" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Devastated to learn that their only son has been killed by muggers in New York City, former Headmaster B.B. Pradhan and his wife, Parvati, grieve. With their son dead, there is no source of income for the couple, so they rent out a room, in their Shivaji Park - Bombay apartment to a budding Bollywood actress, Sujata Suman, who has been having an illicit affair with the only son - Vilas of a politician named Gajanan Chitre. Vilas lacks the guts to tell his father that he is in love and would like to marry Sujata, and hence puts off any marriage plans. They do get intimate and as a result Sujata gets pregnant. When Pradhan finds out, he offers to take Sujata to meet Gajanan with the hope that he will permit her to become his daughter-in-law. But Gajanan not only refuses, he also threatens them, he warns them of dire consequences if Sujata does not abort the child, and moves away to another town. Pradhan refuses to let Sujata out of his house, and then begins the stalking and harassment by Gajanan's men. Pradhan goes to file a police complaint, but is told that the police cannot even touch Gajanan's men. Sujata has no choice but to continue to seek shelter with Pradhan and his wife. Sujata does not know that Pradhan and Parvati have a secret agenda of their own in keeping her within their sight.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rakta Bandhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Rakta-Bandhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Rakta-Bandhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/sMbnPWsQ2Ag/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Rakta Bandhan" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Rakta Bandhan is a Bollywood Movie, starring Mithun Chakraborty & Rati Agnihotri. Kundan and Chandan are idential twins, Dacoits loot their village and carry away Kundan. Kundan becomes the feared decoit Trishul Singh, Chandan drives a tonga in the village. Kundan has an affair with Kammo Bai, a dancing girl, whilst Chandan secretly loves a village maidan, Rupa. Chowdhry bullies all the tonga drivers. Chandan is also severely beaten up and dumped in jungle to die. Hotly chased by the police Kundan is looking for a hiding place when he comes across Chandan lying unconcious. Noticing the natural resemblance, he quickly changes with Chandan and escapes to the village. When Kundan's followers find Chandan, they mistake him for their Sardar and carry him back to their hide-out. Chowdhry is taken aback when he tries to rape Chandan's sister and is given a merciless beating by Kundan. Chowdhry is intrigued to find a weak and timid Chandan suddenly becoming an aggressive bull. Meanwhile Chandan surrounded by the decoits pleads with them to release him. He is not their Sardar. They think he is suffering from loss of memory. Everyone in the village, including Chandan's sweetheart Rupa accept Kundan as Chandan, but he realises that this deceptive disguise cannot go on for ever. He decides to rescue Chandan and restore him to the village. The Police have already discovered the dacoit's den, and Kundan rushes to save his brother's life. Though he succeeds, he falls victim to the police firing, whilst the dancing girl Kammo is also killed in the cross fire. As Kundan is dying, he urges Chandan to return to the village and to his beloved Rupa.


<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Piya Ka Ghar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Piya-Ka-Ghar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Piya-Ka-Ghar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Y-7St_MxMEQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Piya Ka Ghar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Piya Ka Ghar is a Classic Bollywood Movie, directed by Basu Chatterjee,  starring Jaya Bhaduri, Anil Dhawan & Ranjita Thakur.


<p>Synopsis: Mumbai &ndash; Bombay, the dream city with skyscrapers, has only one-room tenements for most of its citizens.There, they live and adapt themselves; their joys, sorrows, emotions, and even their grievances all are confined to the four walls of the room.Bharat Mahal is one such huge building where Ram &ndash; Anil Dhawan lives with his aged parents, two brothers and his sister-in-law.To this abode comes the seventh member of the family, Malti, the bride of Ram&hellip; Malti &ndash; Jaya Bhaduri comes from a place which still boasts of wide, green, open fields under a canopy of deep blue skies, with trees and flowers, hills and streams.She comes to the dream city with hopes of an exciting, thrilling happy life. She discovers soon that the wide world of her own home-town has to be confined within the four walls of her new one-room home in Mumbai.Happiness eludes Ram and Malti, despite their love and devotion to each other. Malti finds it difficult to live, love or even quarrel in the one room with so many relations breathing down her neck! The problems of the newly-weds who come to the dream city, their trials and tribulations, and their compromises is told in this breezy, marital comedy.</p>

<p>Click on <a href="http://www.rajshri.com/Listing/Movies/Free-Hindi-Movies-New-Classic-Bollywood-Blockbuster-Films">http://www.rajshri.com/Listing/Movies/Free-Hindi-Movies-New-Classic-Bollywood-Blockbuster-Films</a> to watch full length Bollywood films absolutely Free!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. X in Bombay]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Mr.-X-In-Bombay.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:07:41-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Mr.-X-In-Bombay</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YJTyKUytMpw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Mr. X In Bombay" /></p>

<!--more-->


<br/>Sudarshan (Kishore Kumar), is a talented poet who crosses paths with a young artist, Shobha (Kum Kum) and instantly falls in love with her. Sudarshan is a simpleton while Shobha is very modern girl. Shobha lives a wealthy lifestyle with her father, Professor Mathur who is now carrying out experiments on various issues. One day, Sudarshan goes to meet Shobha at her house but ends up being the guinea pig for her father's experiment. Soon a series of paranormal events follow that alter the lives of everyone. What effects does the experiment bring upon Sudarshan?


<p>Subscribe &ndash; <a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
