<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rajshri-Originals | movie blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/rajshri-originals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T16:00:54-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivah]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Vivah.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:36:57-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Vivah</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/R9upjxi7_lk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Vivah" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Watch Bollywood Romantic superhit family drama movie, Rajshri Productions' Vivah &ndash; A journey from engagement to marriage with English subtitles, starring Shahid Kapur &amp; Amrita Rao, directed by Sooraj R. Barjatya, music composed by Ravindra Jain.</p>

<p>Vivah is the story of Poonam &amp; Prem. Poonam (Amrita Rao) an orphaned middle-class girl lives with her uncle (Alok Nath) and aunt (Seema Biswas). Poonam&rsquo;s chachi (aunt) has been unable to accept Poonam as part of their family as she is more beautiful than her own daughter, Rajni (Amrita Prakash). Poonam&rsquo;s simple and affectionate demeanor touches the heart of Bhagatji (Manoj Joshi), who takes her marriage proposal for Prem (Shahid Kapoor), son of renowned businessman Mr. Harishchandra (Anupam Kher). Inspite of being brought up in the fast city life of New Delhi, Prem is rooted to the ground and has retained his family&rsquo;s traditional values and upbringing.</p>

<p>Respecting his fathers wishes, Prem agrees to meet Poonam to get to know her better, which, follows a &lsquo;meeting&rsquo; arranged by the two families. Prem and Poonam suddenly find themselves in midst of a situation they have never been in before. They discover their soul mates in each other and are engaged &ndash; to be married in six months. Prem and Poonam go through the most magical and romantic period of their lives. Six months fly by and just when everything is set for Prem and Poonam&rsquo;s marriage&hellip; a crisis puts the love of Prem and Poonam through a trial by fire. &lsquo;Vivah&rsquo; is a heart-warming tale of their unconditional love&hellip;</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash;
<a href="http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri">http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=rajshri</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus:
<a href="https://plus.google.com/+rajshri">https://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest :
<a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter:
<a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>

<p>Vivah Movie Songs Now available on iTunes: <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/vivah-original-motion-picture/id565958986">https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/vivah-original-motion-picture/id565958986</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uphaar]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Uphaar.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:36:57-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Uphaar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/6NdiCd0fmXI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Uphaar" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Uphaar &ndash; 1971 Directed By : Sudhendu Roy Starring :  Jaya Bhaduri, Swaroop Dutt, Nana Palsikar, Kamini Kaushal. Music Director : Laxmikant Pyarelal
Synopsis : Anoop &ndash; Swaroop Dutt studies law in Calcutta, while his widowed mom lives in a small town in West Bengal. He has a sister, Sudha, who is married to Anil and lives in Calcutta. Since Anoop is of marriageable age, his mom has seen a girl for him, whose name is Vidya, and is the daughter of Shankarlal. When Anoop returns home, she seeks his approval, but he says he wants to see the girl first. He goes to see Vidya but also gets to meet another belle by the name of Minoo &ndash; Jaya Bhaduri. He returns home, tells his mom that he cannot marry Vidya, but will marry only Minoo. His mother reluctantly agrees and the marriage takes place. It is then that they find out that Minoo has no household skills, neither is she educated, nor mature enough to understand her relationship with Anoop. Her only interests appear to be stealing mangoes and other fruits, and playing with children much younger than her. Anoop&rsquo;s mom is quite exasperate with her and is compelled to keep her locked up. When the time comes for Anoop to return to Calcutta, he asks Minoo to come with him, but she refuses. His mother cannot handle her childishness and refuses to let her stay with her. Anoop accordingly leaves her with her mom, Sharda Awasthi. However what will finally happen between Minoo and Anoop is what you can find out&hellip;&hellip;.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taraana]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Taraana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:36:57-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Taraana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/k0f1CeZt5dQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Taraana" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Tarana is the melody of love! Love of Radha and Shyam which blossomed in the beautiful valley of Kashmir. When Radha&rsquo;s father Rana came to know of this love affair, he was shaken to the core. For he knew that rich and poor are like two banks of the same river which never meet.Even then for the sake of his daughter&rsquo;s happiness Rana went to Shyam&rsquo;s rich guardian Thakur who spurned the offer and almost literally kicked him out. Little did Thakur knew that Radha whom he rejected as Shyam prospective wife was none other than his own daughter whom he had betrothed to his friend&rsquo;s son Shyam in childhood. After having lost his daughter Thakur had brought up Shyam as his own son. Strange are the ways of fate. Though Thakur was really Radha&rsquo;s father he was bent upon destroying her love and happiness. And Rana who had brought up Radha as his daughter was willing to sacrifice everything for her happiness, but he proved powerless against Thakur&rsquo;s might. And the time came when Thakur was about to kill his own daughter Radha. At that very moment, the doll which was Radha&rsquo;s childhood companion came to her rescue by revealing the truth and re-uniting the lovers.</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taqdeer]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Taqdeer.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:36:57-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Taqdeer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PjLMaNKas5w/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Taqdeer" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Taqdeer  is a Classic Bollywood Movie, directed by A. Salam, starring Bharat Bhooshan, Shalini &amp; Kamal Kapoor.
Synopsis :  Gopal (Bharat Bhooshan) a poor music-teacher of Goa, earns his livelihood by teaching music to the children in his village.Though Gopal and his wife Sharda (Shalini) and their three children are poor they face life with integrity.One day Gopal leaves home to better his prospects by taking employment on board a ship. But, soon after his departure, news comes that the ship has been wrecked, and he is reported missing. Sharda tries her best to stem the onrushing tide of poverty but cannot, and soon her children are on the verge of starvation. Trapped in the storms of agony and tortures, Sharda finally takes a brave decision &mdash; and accepts Vijay Babu&rsquo;s offer to marry him. Several years pass, and we find on the shores of Africa a bearded Gopal bereft of memory. But one day he hears a familiar melody, a composition of his own, sung by one of his former pupils. Memory flashes back to him, and he returns to his native place in Goa. Here,series of shock await him. He finds his home broken down and deserted. Then he hears of his wife&rsquo;s remarriage to Vijay Babu and finds his children grownup, rich and happy. Gopal decides not to re-enter their lives but to eke out his quite and lonely existence. But the wheel of fate turns once again. One day, the old man saves Geeta(his daughter) from a ruffian. One thing leads to another, and soon, Sharada, comes to know that the strange friend of her youngest daughter is none other than her own husband! Almost simultaneously, Vijay Babu learns the truth too. Instantly he decides to get rid of poor Gopal. Watch the film to know what happens in the end&hellip;&hellip;</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tapasya]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Tapasya.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-21T02:36:57-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Rajshri-Originals/2014/03/21/Tapasya</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/IhUvewdcZrY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Tapasya" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>Tapasya &ndash; 1976 Directed By : Anil Ganguly Starring : Rakhee Gulzar, Parikshit Sahni, Asrani, A. K. Hangal, Viju Khote, Lalita Pawar, Abha Dhuliya, Gayatri, V. Gopal, Nazir Hussain, Lalita Kumari, Om Shivpuri, Urmila Bhatt,  Adil. Music Director : Ravindra Jain
Synopsis : Indrani Sinha (Raakhee) is the eldest child in the Sinha household, consisting of her elderly and ill father, Chandranath (A.K. Hangal); two younger sisters and a younger brother. She loves Dr. Sagar Varma (Parikshat Sahni), who looks after her ailing dad, and hopes to marry him soon. His mother approves of Indu, but would like her to leave everthing behind, and look after her son and the household, which is not acceptable to Indu. Misfortune visits the Sinha household and Chandranath passes away, leaving the entire responsiblity of the household on Indu&rsquo;s shoulders. She decides to open a school for children, and her siblings help her. She refuses Sagar&rsquo;s offer of living at his house. Sagar and Indu decide to marry after the children grow up and are well settled. Years pass by, the children have all grown up, her younger brother, Vinod (Asrani) is a graduate, and finds a job with an organization, the owner (Om Shivpuri) of which wants him to marry his only daughter, Pinky (Manju Bansal), and he must leave his family behind and live at Pinky&rsquo;s house. Vinod&rsquo;s decides to do so, and leaves Indu once again to shoulder the entire responsiblity of getting her two sisters married and looking after the household, he does not even invite them to his marriage. How long will life permit Indu and Sagar to wait? Will the younger sisters assist Indu or will they also turn up like Vinod?</p>

<p>Subscribe and Stay Tuned &ndash; <a href="http://goo.gl/eXlZ3">http://goo.gl/eXlZ3</a></p>

<p>Find us on google plus: <a href="http://plus.google.com/+rajshri">http://plus.google.com/+rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Pinterest: <a href="http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/">http://www.pinterest.com/rajshrivideos/</a></p>

<p>Like and Share your favorite videos on Facebook:
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/rajshri">https://www.facebook.com/rajshri</a></p>

<p>Follow us on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Rajshri">https://twitter.com/Rajshri</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
