<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Special-Uploads | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/special-uploads/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-23T00:29:47-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pavitra Bandhan]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Pavitra-Bandhan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Pavitra-Bandhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oRYh_cQjr-A/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Pavitra Bandhan"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oRYh_cQjr-A/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Pavitra Bandhan"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oRYh_cQjr-A/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Pavitra Bandhan"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/oRYh_cQjr-A/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Pavitra Bandhan"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Balu who is a son of lovable middle-class couple. Swapna is the daughter of a strict and rich father. Both of them study in a residential college located at Visakhapatnam. Balu and Swapna fall in love. Swapna is taken away from the college after a picture of them gets published in the newspaper. Balu is told that in order to write his exam he has to bring his father to the college. He goes home and tells his parents a completely different story. While his parents keep thinking that he is studying for his exam, he is busy daydreaming about Swapna and looking for her. At last he brings his father to the college, not to write the exam but to see Swapna. His father is clueless what is happening and still believes Balu. Balu meets Swapna and her parents. Swapna&rsquo;s parents arrange another marriage for her. When Balu&rsquo;s father comes to know what is actually happening he thinks his child should be dealt with love rather than fear. While leaving in a train, Balu&rsquo;s father dies in an accident. On the same day Swapna runs away from her house to live with Balu, but Balu doesn&rsquo;t show up because of his father&rsquo;s death. Balu thinks that Swapna is with her father and her father thinks that she is with Balu. Four years later, when Balu and her father meet, Balu&rsquo;s mother tells Balu that she hid Swapna with one of his lecturers who helped him realize the meaning of life.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oRYh_cQjr-A" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mission to Finish Corruption]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Mission-To-Finish-Corruption.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Mission-To-Finish-Corruption</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YPZBbXO_rMY/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Mission To Finish Corruption"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YPZBbXO_rMY/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mission To Finish Corruption"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YPZBbXO_rMY/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mission To Finish Corruption"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/YPZBbXO_rMY/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Mission To Finish Corruption"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Chandrasekhar who is the editor of a daily called Addam. As he was ready to expose the misdeeds and corrupt practices of Home Minister Bhagawan Raj the latter hangs him to death with the help of his henchman Lingam Goud. Chandu, Abhi and Aparna were orphans and were brought up by Chandrasekhar. They go to high positions and stay abroad. But they return to India to continue the legacy of Chandrasekhar and run Addam.Chandrasekhar wishes not to cause physical harm to the crooked politicians but they should be made unpopular. So Chandu takes over the editor&rsquo;s job and prepares a plan to catch the political red handed.As a first step they catch Vaishnavi Bank chairman Rajareddy who declares insolvency in order to loot the people and expose him. During the course, the trio comes to know that Bhagawan Raj is part of the scam.Based on a video and audio, Chandu starts blackmailing Bhagawan Raj and makes him to spend the money he earned through scams for the benefit of people, as part of fulfilling his election promises. Meanwhile, Chandu falls in love with Vandana, the sister of Lingam Goud. As the recording had the mention of Lingam Goud&rsquo;s name, he could not do any harm to Chandu. However there was a blacksheep among the trio. It is none other than Aparna, who wants to take revenge against Chandrasekhar as he was responsible for the death of her parents and sister. She joins hands with Bhagawan Raj and helps in the murder of Chandrasekhar. She is out to ensure the closure of Addam newspaper.Finally, Bhagawan Raj realises that the real happiness in life lies in working for the welfare of the people. After the self-introspection, Bhagawan Raj kills Aparna and decides to commit suicide. But Chandu stops him saying that the people need a politician who realized his mistakes.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YPZBbXO_rMY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Hoon Tapori]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Main-Hoon-Tapori.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:31-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Main-Hoon-Tapori</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PnFiCJIQR80/hqdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Main Hoon Tapori"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PnFiCJIQR80/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Main Hoon Tapori"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PnFiCJIQR80/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Main Hoon Tapori"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PnFiCJIQR80/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Main Hoon Tapori"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Movie is about a petty thief whose travails to steal a diamond necklace gets him involved with a naive girl searching for her fiance in the big city. Subbalakshmi is simple girl who grows up in a quaint little village. She goes to the city to find her fiance, Prakash, who comes there to pursue his higher studies. On the train she comes across, Raju, a petty thief who just stole a diamond necklace. To avoid being caught by the police, he places the necklace in Lakshmi&rsquo;s bag without her knowing. Once he&rsquo;s through the police checking, he goes to find Lakshmi. On the pretext of helping her find her fiance, he tries to steal the necklace back. Just when he&rsquo;s about to take the necklace, something funny always happens that prevents him from taking the necklace. Raju starts to develop feelings for Lakshmi but never acts on them. Lakshmi searches the entire city to find her Prakash and Raju tries to help her, and one day she sees Prakash at a five star hotel with another woman. Prakash, falls in love with Lavanya, the owner of the five star hotel and plans to inherit her fortune by marrying her. Heartbroken by what she sees, Lakshmi tries to commit suicide but Raju stops her at the nick of time and reasons with her. They decide to teach Prakash a lesson, so Lakshmi changes her appearance from a simple looking village girl to a flamboyantly beautiful woman. She checks into the hotel under an alias and introduces herself to Prakash and Lavanya. Meanwhile, Raju befriends Lavanya and gets close to her. Prakash gets furious and threatens Lakshmi and Raju not to interfere with his wedding to Lavanya. But Lavanya learns Prakash&rsquo;s true intentions and calls off the wedding. Lakshmi also realizes that Prakash is a selfish man and that she has feelings for someone else, Raju. The movie ends with Raju and Lakshmi ending up together.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PnFiCJIQR80" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meri Taqat Mera Faisla]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Meri-Taqat-Mera-Faisla.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:30-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Meri-Taqat-Mera-Faisla</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/5DK6fYRAxgA/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Meri Taqat Mera Faisla"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/5DK6fYRAxgA/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Meri Taqat Mera Faisla"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/5DK6fYRAxgA/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Meri Taqat Mera Faisla"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/5DK6fYRAxgA/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Meri Taqat Mera Faisla"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The Story is about Veera Pandi a landlord who is also the most respected person in Pandiapuram, a hamlet near Sivaganga. He is a do-gooder who commands respect from all and is feared the most by his enemies. Selvam is his loyal son, who always does the right things at the right time and sees his father as his role model. Rajalingam, the local MLA, who has risen to his position mostly because of the influence enjoyed by Veera Pandi in the region. Rajalingam doesn&rsquo;t share the good motives of Veera Pandi. He has come into politics to enjoy power and earn lot of money. Veera Pandi tries to influence him, but the MLA has no intention to listen to him. At the same time, he cannot afford to ignore Veera Pandi. Meanwhile,Veera Pandi, who has many enemies because of his strictness, wants to protect his son from them. So he sends him to his uncle who lives in Trichy. Selvam meets his childhood friend Radhika in Trichy. Selvam tries to revive the friendship, but the girl avoids him. Selvam pursues her and expresses his love. Radhika responds positively after a lot of hesitation. Rajalingam tries to eliminate Selvam, to tame his father. Though Selvam tries to avoid any confrontation to satisfy his father, he is forced to take the sickle soon. He defeats Rajalingam&rsquo;s plans. This incident makes Rajalingam more furious. He manages to become a minister and uses his power to insult Veera Pandi. Selvam defuses his efforts and Rajalingam is ready for final show down. Selvam is ready to face anything to save his father.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5DK6fYRAxgA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highway]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Highway.html"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T12:29:30-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Special-Uploads/2014/03/23/Highway</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/gGbVUVYJiu0/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="640" alt="Highway"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/gGbVUVYJiu0/1.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Highway"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/gGbVUVYJiu0/2.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Highway"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/gGbVUVYJiu0/3.jpg" height="158" width="100" alt="Highway"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>The story exploits both the darker and brighter sides of the land acquisition scam. The story is set in a remote village where people make their living through farming.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gGbVUVYJiu0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
