<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Naseeruddin-Shahs-Birthday-Special-July-20-2013 | Any.New.Movies]]></title>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/categories/naseeruddin-shahs-birthday-special-july-20-2013/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-08T18:26:30-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://anynewmovies.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[admin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hasti]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Naseeruddin-Shahs-Birthday-Special-July-20-2013/Movies/Hindi/NaseeruddinShah/2012/09/24/Hasti.html"/>
    <updated>2012-09-24T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Naseeruddin-Shahs-Birthday-Special-July-20-2013/Movies/Hindi/NaseeruddinShah/2012/09/24/Hasti</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/BeimyCM36BE/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Hasti"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/BeimyCM36BE/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Hasti"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/BeimyCM36BE/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Hasti"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/BeimyCM36BE/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Hasti"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>Narang is an accomplished and wealthy industrialist who lives with his daughter, Neena, in a palatial home. His daughter is now of marriageable age, and he would like her to marry his associate&rsquo;s, Bhisham, son, Vicky. But Neena is in love with a much poorer man named Jaikishan alias Jaggu. When Neena informs her father that she would like to marry Jaggu, he summons Jaggu&rsquo;s mom, Shanti, and instantly recognizes her from his questionable past. He belittles her, humiliates her and asks her to leave his house. When Jaggu finds out he goes to meet Narang, and asks him to change his decision, but he too gets insulted, and is asked to leave, never to see nor speak to Neena again. Jaggu promises him that he will return within one year and by that time he will be even more wealthy than Narang. Jaggu befriends a homeless man named Vishal and together they set forth to meet Jaggu&rsquo;s deadline&hellip;</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/BeimyCM36BE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giddh]]></title>
    <link href="http://anynewmovies.com/Naseeruddin-Shahs-Birthday-Special-July-20-2013/Movies/Hindi/NaseeruddinShah/2012/09/24/Giddh.html"/>
    <updated>2012-09-24T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anynewmovies.com/Naseeruddin-Shahs-Birthday-Special-July-20-2013/Movies/Hindi/NaseeruddinShah/2012/09/24/Giddh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-uPQiaBwrXY/maxresdefault.jpg" height="480" width="540" alt="Giddh"></td>
<td>
    <table>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-uPQiaBwrXY/1.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Giddh"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-uPQiaBwrXY/2.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Giddh"></td></tr>
    <tr><td><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/-uPQiaBwrXY/3.jpg" height="158" width="150" alt="Giddh"></td></tr>
    </table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>




<!--more-->


<p>In a remote rural town in India, live a young woman named Ahnami and her husband, Bhashya. Bhashya is a laborer who earns a daily wage, drinks alcohol with part of it, and gives the rest to his wife for their livelihood. On some days he does not make any money, and as a result acts as a pimp for his wife, so that they can feed themselves. These are the two who are attempting to spearhead a awakening amongst this town which encourages young girls not to marry, but give themselves up to be devdasis (prostitutes), forever made to appease and satisfy males. These girls cannot marry locally as all the local young men have been sodomized, and the only way they can lead a normal life is by escaping to Bombay via a daily bus service. But even on the bus there is a pimp named Veerappan, who lures the girls on the pretext of a better life, but sells them in brothels in Bombay&rsquo;s red-light areas. There is no other route for these girls as the local police are apathetic, and corrupt, and the townspeople are all afraid to speak up out of fear of reprisals and superstition.</p>

<br/>


<iframe width="640" height="480" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/-uPQiaBwrXY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
